Chapter 1199: Secret News (2)

Eradicate this world‽

Han Xiao and Kasuyi glanced at each other, seeing the surprise reflected.

With just a few of us, to go against a behemoth like the Celestial Star Alliance…

With such few side dishes, you intend to drink the whole night?

Han Xiao secretly swore, but since there seemed to be a lot of hidden secrets within, he patiently said, "You mentioned that this was the only way we can leave. Please talk in detail."

"I know you think that this mission is impossible, but in fact, this is not as difficult as you think… However, it is not simple either," the mysterious man rasped. "I believe that when you entered this secondary dimension, you should have been very shocked. You never thought that a space similar to the universe existed here, with an extremely powerful civilization."

"That's right." Han Xiao nodded.

"Hehe, it's not just you, but every outsider also reacted in the same manner." The mysterious man slowly spoke. "I understand your troubles, but your worries are superfluous. All that you have been… the Celestial Star Alliance, the tens of thousands of Saint class experts, including me, are all long-dead phantoms. Our world… has long been annihilated!"

Han Xiao was taken aback and asked doubtfully, "What exactly happened?"

"The current world you see here is based on a mutated time-space cycle Information Form," the mysterious man blandly replied. "You should have discovered some information regarding the World Reset program on the internet. This plan was not just a simple insurance but also a special scheme used by the Celestial Star Alliance to escape the end of the universe. But the plan failed. Due to some abnormal changes that happened within the Information Form, our timeline was intercepted, forming a closed cycle of spacetime, which is this world I live in. It will constantly end at a fixed point in time and be reborn at a fixed point in time. I'm the only anomaly that retains my memory within this cycle."

"…Thus, if we wish to leave, we must break the so-called closed spacetime loop?"

Han Xiao's brows were knitted tightly together.

Just based on the theory of the Spacetime Splicing Technology, this sort of scenario was possible, but the rhetoric behind it made it hard to believe.

The mysterious man glanced at their expressions, letting out a laugh before he spoke.

"Hehe, don't look at me like that. I'm not a liar. I know that your hearts must be full of suspicions. That's perfectly normal. Since I've invited you here, I intend to explain everything from the beginning…"

"It's alright. We have time." Han Xiao crossed his arms.

"Then prepare yourselves. No matter how shocked you are later, don't interrupt my narration. What you'll hear next will be the secrets and truths involving the entire universe…"

The mysterious man's tone turned somber.

"Please speak." Han Xiao straightened his expression, making a 'please' gesture.

After taking a deep breath, the mysterious man began.

"Everything has a definite life span, and the universe is no different. According to normal development, the universe will ultimately usher in its final destiny over time. It might be through overheating, a gravitational collapse, or a space rip. When time reaches a certain point, everything is bound to end.

"However, in that initial time and space, there existed a civilization that had developed to the extreme, far stronger than any of ours could ever be. In order to escape their fate, they chose to give a new life to the universe as a method to continue their existence… While they did not succeed in the end, it was not a complete failure. Under the construction, they had altered the basic rules of the universe. When the universe expands to a certain level, reaching the bifurcation of its ultimate destiny, it will actively collapse upon itself, swallowing everything and becoming a singularity point. The big bang will then occur and retransform into a new universe that will be empty but full of life… We call this 'The Great Reboot'.

"That Godlike civilization that gave a glimmer of hope to the creatures of the universe has long been destroyed by The Great Reboot, their names having disappeared in the long river of time. However, they left this transformation of the universe as their only legacy for their future generations. Nothing can measure the preciousness of this legacy, for without it, no other civilization could appear.

"As such, we have honored this civilization as the Savior Civilization. It was they who opened the iteration of the universe… and this universe they were in has become the anchor of this timeline, called the first iteration.

"However, The Great Reboot led to the final destiny of the universe being brought forward, so the development time for the civilizations in the subsequent iterations was shortened, not allowing any civilization to reach the heights of the Savior Civilization. They were just repeating the cycle of creation and destruction, unable to make any changes to the universe or leave any information.

"It was unknown how many iterations passed in this manner, until a variable suddenly appeared one day. The strongest civilization in that particular iteration made an amazing breakthrough in the field of the Information Form.

"They had managed to discover clues to the Savior Civilization and discovered part of the reason for the process of The Great Reboot. They believed that the tampering of the Savior Civilization at the beginning happened to result in a mutation within the Information Form, thus affecting the path of development for their universe… In their view, the universe is akin to a program that will rewrite the operation mode, whereas the Information Form is a sort of programming language.

"Thus, they attempted to utilize the Information Form to continue their civilization, but unfortunately, they failed in the end as well. However, they had managed to leave behind another legacy, which is a kind of existence known as 'Sanctums'.

"Those items might have been just their tinder library, but by chance, it managed to mutate into one of the underlying laws of the universe's operation, allowing it to survive The Great Reboot. It thus recorded all information that occurred within an iteration and stored it in an Information Form. A random part of that form would be extracted when The Great Reboot occurred to be integrated into the underlying laws of the new universe, allowing small changes to happen to the universe repeatedly, making future iterations more abundant…

"It might not be easy to understand, so let me give you an example. The five Super systems you see now are products of said Sanctum. In the ancient times, some universe iterations had certain Supers, while some did not have those, utilizing different systems. The Sanctums would record part of each Super system, so it randomly inserted these systems into one of the iterations of The Great Reboot to be permanently engraved into the universe's laws… This is how the five Super systems are formed, not appearing at the same time but continuing to be repeated through iterations and supplemented. Thus, you see that we have five Super systems, as does your universe. This is no coincidence.

"Another example… you might have noticed, but we do not have secondary dimensions. Our iteration is much earlier than yours, so our own World Reset plan might have been the root behind the creation of the secondary dimensions. The Sanctums incorporated our information into the laws of the universe during the next Great Reboot… so, we might have actually been the creators of the secondary dimensions!

"In any case, the appearance of the Sanctums allows for the subsequent iterations to jump out of this eternal loop as it brings about more variables. It continues to enrich the universe of the next iteration and can be considered a sort of inheritance. While it is miniscule, many droplets eventually form a pond.

"Broadly speaking, the later the iteration of the universe, the more likely it will be stronger overall and more advanced!

"Thus, we honored this civilization with the name of the Sanctum Civilization, and each iteration of the universe was known as the iteration of transformation.

"In addition to optimizing the effectiveness of the universe, the Sanctums also acted like recording tools at the beginning of each civilization, allowing the history of that iteration to be recorded to pass on to future iterations. The later generations will thus develop their civilizations to a certain degree, with the ability to open the Sanctums. The higher their skills and strength, the more information can be obtained from it.

"Thus, a relay of the Civilizations that cross iterations was opened!

"Generation after generation of Universal Civilizations have inherited the research of their predecessors, learning from their failures and constantly pioneering new paths. Even if they fail, they will still leave behind all of their own experiences in the Sanctums to allow their future generations to continue the research. Everything is to allow us to get rid of the ultimate destiny of the universe, placing our hopes in the future that a generation will discover a method to survive The Great Reboot and continue to prosper.

"As experience is passed on, subsequent iterations will have a higher chance of making this breakthrough.

"During my iteration, this World Reset plan was our result. While we did not manage to allow our civilization to continue in the end, it managed to create secondary dimensions for our future generations, giving you more possibilities.

"And this world you see is just a short cyclic timeline toward the end of the universe where I live, a failed restart, a phantom that should have disappeared a long time ago. And we… are just one link in this long chain."

Finally, the mysterious man stopped talking.

Han Xiao and Kasuyi remained frozen in place, their eyes fully widened as waves were set off in their minds.

The information contained within this tale was just too huge, so powerful that it had exceeded all of their imaginations.

"How true is this?" Han Xiao felt that this was truly unbelievable.

This story had given him a strong impact on his soul, and he could not help but doubt the veracity of this cosmic secret.

There was no relevant information about this in his previous life. The three Universal Civilizations as well as the World Tree Civilization had not revealed this in any manner.

Could it be that the three Universal Civilizations had yet to be sufficiently developed, so the secret of the Sanctums had not been cracked?

Could it be… that this was the true meaning behind the mission name [A Relay Across Iterations]?

If that was true, this was truly too spectacular. The painstaking research from generation to generation continued to pass on in this manner, akin to the relay of a torch.

Just thinking about it, he could feel an epic sense of history. The unyieldingness as well as the resilience of the generations before to go against the very heavens, their dignity of not intending to leave their fates to destiny!

Seeing their shock and surprise, the mysterious man did not explain further but instead calmly said, "I know that you guys are indeed suspicious of my words. After all, this has completely subverted your world views. However, in the future, when your universe iteration develops to the corresponding level, you will understand such things. For now… let's get back to business."

"Alright." Han Xiao calmed himself, suppressing his turbulent emotions.

Right now, there was no way for him to verify the authenticity of this statement, but he thought about Oathkeeper, who had gone to the Sanctums. When he returned, Han Xiao would proceed to the Holy Accord to obtain information about the Sanctums so that he could confirm if this secret was real.

If this was true, he had to consider the long-term impacts… The players in his previous life were unable to reach this level, so this was the first time he had experienced this, and he did not know what to do.

The mysterious man shook his head, pulling the topic back on track as he slowly said, "This spacetime here rests in an endless loop. The moment the World Reset plan is fully activated, a new cycle will begin. Because I'm an individual in this cycle of spacetime, even if I die, I'll be reborn and retain my memories, but outsiders do not belong to this spacetime and thus will be annihilated here.

"If you guys wish to leave, you have to break the loop before the end of this cycle. In this manner, you can regain your freedom, and I can also be liberated.

"I have met with outsiders in the fifty-ninth, sixty-second, and seventy-third cycles, the earliest being what you call the Primordial Ones. I helped them as I did you today, but they all failed to break the cycle and thus died here."

Hearing this, Han Xiao started to plan by himself.

This sort of spacetime loop had similarities to the Spacetime Splicing Technology, both of which would fix the timeline in a certain period. The difference was that the cause of this secondary dimension was far greater than that of the Spacetime Splicing Technology. It was many times more complex.

However, this was not the only method he had in his arsenal to leave this place. The teleportation function of the King suit should be able to work as it had similar functions to the Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device. While it was possible for him to leave, Han Xiao was more curious about the mysterious man's plan to destroy his world.

"Even if you want us to destroy the world, you can't possibly ask us to go to war against the other Celestial Star Alliance, right? Phantoms they might be, but in this time and space, their combat power is real."

"Of course not. The original World Reset plan was broken and only re-emerged after The Great Reboot, where Information Form technology was used to make us reappear. The principle is not very clear to me, and I only know that the implementation of this program is in the use of the Information Form technology. The artificial intelligence core, which we call the guardian, was bound to the Sanctums by the Celestial Star Alliance, allowing it to survive the destruction during The Great Reboot.

"But in the end, it failed and was changed. Although we reappeared, we have become phantoms and turned into a secondary dimension, trapped in a spacetime loop. The artificial intelligence core became the dimensional consciousness of this secondary dimension… You should have seen its clone when you came in."

Han Xiao thought about it.

So, the Supreme Guardian that they encountered outside the secondary dimension was actually a clone of the dimensional consciousness entity?

However, his combat information did not reveal this. It appeared like a living human.

The mysterious man continued. "The Guardian is the root of this spacetime cycle. It has no independent thinking, only preset procedures that rigidly protect this secondary dimension from any outside invasion. As long as you kill him, you can break the cycle, and only outsiders can achieve it.

"Because I'm part of the cycle, no matter how I flip over this world, the end result is that the cycle will restart. Thus, the Guardian will not interfere. There is no way for me to contact him as I'm inseparable from this world… but the existence of an outsider is a variable. Once you invade, the Guardian will inevitably rush in, and you have a chance to kill him here.

"In the program of the Guardian, there is still a portion of the Information Form technology from the World Reset plan. Any outsiders who die in the cycle of Reset will be captured by him, allowing him to use dimensional energy to create entities that are extremely similar to the original as clones. Thus far, three batches of outsiders have died, so he has several clones."

The more the outsiders that die, the more Beyond Grade As he can manufacture. A dimensional consciousness entity actually has such a powerful skill, even though it was caused by a mutation… Han Xiao was impressed.

The Celestial Star Alliance was indeed the hegemon of a previous iteration. Even a failed product was so powerful. The time for development for his three Universal Civilizations was only a fraction compared to the Celestial Star Alliance. Thus, in terms of technical levels, they were akin to a younger brother.

"It seems possible, but how can we make the guardian show up?" Han Xiao nodded.

"Because of the changes in spacetime, and in order to avoid risks, the underlying logic of the Guardian states that it cannot tamper with the reset content that was coded in, which resulted in the Guardian not being able to move as freely in this world compared to the outside. It can only descend near its vessels. For example, the Superpower Security Department of the Celestial Star Alliance has a Cosmic Treasure known as the Positioning Star Map, which is one of the automatically formed dimensional consciousness vessels, which allows it to monitor the entire dimension. I've created a sort of cloaking device that can escape its surveillance, which is why you have not been discovered.

"In short, as long as you're close to any vessels, the Guardian will appear and try to kill you. This is his core mechanism, and he cannot violate it. However, all these vessels are in the high security warehouses of the Superpower Security Department. Our plan is to attack the Superpower Security Department warehouse, get to the vessel to allow the Guardian to appear, and kill it."

"This difficulty is not low at all…" Han Xiao thought about it.

"I will provide help, and the resources of the Eye of Insight can also be utilized by you. Furthermore, I will not let the two of you work for nothing," the mysterious man replied. "We are both Mechanics, so I will impart a portion of my entire life's learning to you as a reward for helping me out."

He paused for a moment before he added, "Of course, only by breaking the cycle and surviving will whatever you've learned be meaningful."

Chapter 1200: Problem

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

While this secondary dimension might only be a phantom of the actual world, this was a treasure trove to Han Xiao. Not only could he obtain new Class abilities, he could also gather a lot more advanced technology that would be different from the current explored universe. For a Mechanic, this was the jackpot!

Han Xiao originally only planned to get some skills before returning. With a willing teacher to impart his Knowledge now, the efficiency would be twice the result with only half the effort needed.

Furthermore, this mysterious man had already undergone so many cycles. Even if his bodily condition was constantly reset, making training meaningless, his memory could still be retained. This meant that all the technology he had learned would always be in his mind. With such a terrifying background, it could only mean good things.

By the side, Kasuyi stared with wide eyes. "What about me?"

The mysterious man shot him a look before shaking his head. "You're not a Mechanic, so there's nothing I can teach you."

"Hey, that's not very nice!" Kasuyi was a little aggrieved in his heart.

It was obviously I who came first, be it forming the team or leading the way, but the benefits all landed at Black Star's feet instead. Why is that so?

The mysterious thought about it before speaking again. "If you really wish to have some technical data, it's not as though there's no way. Once the cycle is broken, everything here will vanish, and that includes any sort of material objects. Only information can be circulated. According to the principle of Information Forms, information that is transformed by outsiders can be retained. Since you cannot learn the Knowledge, you can use any recording machines brought from the outside to store this information…"

Hearing this, Kasuyi's expression got a lot better. He felt that this was more like it.

Even if he was not a Mechanic, he understood the value of this technology. He could hand it to his subordinates to bolster his organization or even trade it with the Arcane Church.

At this moment, Han Xiao's eyes narrowed, and he said, "Don't forget that your goal is the God's Trait Transformation. You shouldn't bother yourself with such trivialities. Leave the matters here to me instead. If I don't step into hell, who will?"

"You're being shameless again‽" Kasuyi's expression changed. "You want to swallow everything on your own?"

Han Xiao shot Kasuyi a glance. "When you came to me to form a team, you told me you owed me one. I haven't asked you for any compensation yet. Monopolizing this can be considered my compensation. Besides, you're also not a Mechanic. Why do you need this technology? At most, when we leave, I'll give you some other form of dividends. Do you mind?"

"Of course I mind! This is this, and that is that. The technology is not within the scope of our agreement."

Kasuyi definitely would not want to give up on this treasure.

Han Xiao suddenly stroked his chin, saying meaningfully, "Are you sure you want to fight? Don't forget, you're in your main body now…"

Hearing this, Kasuyi's expression slightly changed.

"And besides… if the plan to break the cycle fails, how are you planning to leave?" Han Xiao laughed.

Kasuyi was speechless and could only helplessly wave his hand. "Fine, I'll give up. I don't want this technology."

While he wanted this technology, in comparison, his life was more important. Since he had come over with his main body, if he pissed Black Star off, his path of retreat would be completely sealed. He thought for a bit before realizing that he had to compromise.

However, while Kasuyi gave up fighting for the technology, he did not intend to let things be. He looked at the mysterious man and said, "My partner has a special device that can allow him to teleport without restrictions. This task in the secondary dimension is difficult, so if you don't stop him, he can get away at any time. I suggest you only teach him a part of this technology and only give him the rest when we're about to complete the mission."

"Oh? There's such a thing?" The mysterious man turned his head toward Han Xiao.

Han Xiao glanced at Kasuyi, not surprised, as he calmly nodded. "That's right. I do have such an ability, and I agree with such a way of doing things."

Of course, he was aware of what Kasuyi was thinking. He was worried Han Xiao would abscond once he got his hands on all the data.

Han Xiao did not think that there was a problem with Kasuyi doing such a thing. If it was him, it was likely that he would have taken the same measures.

The two of them were merely temporary teammates. While they had some friendship, in the face of benefits, their relationship was insufficient to bring unreserved trust. People at their level would not easily put hope in others.

At their realm, as long as they were not close relatives or friends, no one would easily give in when faced with their own interests.

While Han Xiao was shocked to learn about the secrets of the universe, he would not change his behavior and purpose of arriving just because of that. After all, their universe iteration was just too far away, and even if he knew about it, he could not be of help for the time being. In the end, one still had to live in the present.

No matter how lofty one was, when it came to an issue that concerned personal benefits, one had to handle them from a practical perspective. The value of such technology was amazing, so there was no reason for Han Xiao to allow Kasuyi to easily share a piece of the pie. Regardless of whether he would work together with the advanced civilizations in the future, he had to take the initiative to obtain such benefits first.

That was especially so since he was a Mechanic. He was aware of the importance of not leaking his technology, so he did not hesitate to threaten Kasuyi… If the other party did not compromise, let alone mentioning their backup escape plan, he would not hesitate to attack on the spot.

As for Kasuyi's little trick, Han Xiao thought little of it. He did not intend to only take and not give. With the technology in his hands, he would fulfill the agreement to help break the cycle. He still had his morals to some extent, and he also had to provide some insurance for Kasuyi.

While such a method would offend the other party, if both sides compromised, the relationship could still continue.

Since they were all people with statuses, few of them were actually stubborn creatures. Negotiation of one's interests was a norm, and even if one had a grudge, they would not really throw aside all pretenses.

The mysterious man looked a little hesitant, but he finally said, "In that case, I'll teach you a part of the technology first. By the way, you should take advantage of this period to draft your action plan. In addition, the resources of the Eye of Insight are completely open to you. You can expand your machinery and manpower here…"

He could not determine if Han Xiao's teleportation ability was real or not. Since he was just an Information Form in this secondary dimension, if Black Star teleported him away, he would immediately die and achieve his freedom.

However, he knew that this proposal was tantamount to abandoning Kasuyi. The latter would never agree to it, so they could only do a trade in private. However, he did not know if Black Star would be willing to kill off any witnesses.

He actually wished for Black Star to use his teleportation ability to move reinforcements from outside. That would be the most beneficial to him, but no one would agree to this proposal either. If Black Star wished to teleport out, Kasuyi would strongly oppose it. Black Star would also not agree to the move in order to monopolize the technology.

All three parties had their own positions, so it was difficult to reach one best decision. The final result was to have a compromise that everyone could accept.

The mysterious man understood everyone's concerns and knew that their behavior would not change even if they believed in the secrets he revealed. Thus, he did not intend to deviate from his original plan.

"After speaking so much, you still haven't told us your name," Kasuyi said.

"You can call me Jayz."

"Speaking of which, why can you keep your memories?"

"I have no idea either. I was not like this in the beginning and only awakened around a thousand cycles ago. Before that, I was just resetting repeatedly like everyone else.

At this moment, a notification popped up on Han Xiao's interface.

_____________________

The first chain mission of [A Relay Across Iterations] has been completed!

You have received one billion experience.

The second chain mission has been opened!

Mission Requirements: Destroy the dimensional consciousness entity, breaking the spacetime loop, and bringing relief to Jayz, hereby obtaining his legacy.

Mission Reward: 1.5 billion experience, 1 Random Reward, 1 Character Summon Card, and unlocking of the next mission.

_____________________

Han Xiao scanned through and nodded.

The second chain mission has begun, and the rewards are higher… However, the technology from Jayz is my greatest reward. I estimate I'll have to stay much longer than expected in this secondary dimension…

With a thought, Han Xiao opened up the forums to take a look. The fourth Pro League was about to start, and it seemed like he would not have the time to pay attention to it this time.

After coming to an agreement, Han Xiao did not bother acting polite, asking Jayz to teach him some Mechanic class skills that he did not have. He conveniently pushed the coldly snorting Kasuyi out as well.

Very quickly, the sound of the interface rang.

_____________________

Jayz (Lv.367) has passed on the skill [Mechanical Force—Soldier Nest]. Current progress: 0.0001%

Jayz (Lv.367) has passed on the skill [Compressed Orb Innovation—Armed Body]. Current progress: 0.0001%

Jayz…

_____________________

Seeing the large number of notifications, Han Xiao was elated.

…

In the explored universe, somewhere in the Primeval Star River…

"I've finally succeeded!"

In a secret machinery factory, Manison gazed at the cloud of virtual data in front of him, unable to hide his smile of satisfaction.

Ever since the Intelligent Plague ended, Manison had spent most of his days in the workshop, attempting to imitate the Virtual Mutiny Virus.

After slogging his guts out for so long, he had finally managed to make some progress, creating a prototype virus.

While there were many functions still missing and it was far weaker than the original, Manison believed that this represented a correct direction in his research. As long as he continued to overcome all technical difficulties, he could recreate the complete Virtual Mutiny Virus sooner or later.

"Black Star, you destroyed the unique virus core, thinking that it would ruin my plan, but you did not expect that I would be able to restore this technology! Hehe, in terms of technology R&D, you're still too green!"

The corner of Manison's mouth curled up, and he disappeared.

He carefully collected this embryonic form of the virus, making multiple encryptions for experimental data before deciding to retain this technology as his hidden trump card.

However, he suddenly thought of the weird means that Black Star had used to snatch his two Felons a while ago, and his eyes once again narrowed.

"My current technology isn't enough. I must find a way to crack the weird Virtual Technology that Black Star possesses, or I will only be restrained…"

Manison opened his research schedule, and after reviewing it, he deleted a few unimportant projects before adding the new research goal of cracking Han Xiao's purification ability.

After finishing his work, Manison took out his communicator, and after checking the date, he announced the time of the next regular meeting in the chat group of the Beyond Grade A Association.

"Speaking of which, Black Star and Kasuyi have not attended the past two meetings, nor can they be contacted. I'm not sure where they've gone…"

Every meeting, Black Star would cause trouble for him, so without the annoying voice of Black Star in the past two meetings, Manison only felt as though his body was relaxed, finding his inner calm once more.

Furthermore, without Black Star taking the lead, the people in his area were all guarding themselves, so no one jumped up to make trouble. The past two meetings had gone quite smoothly, and Manison once again felt the joy of holding great authority.

While he did not know what Black Star was up to, Manison wanted Black Star to delay his return even longer. In other words…

Just don't turn up to meetings for as long as possible!

Chapter 1201: Technology Treasure, Start of Operation

Numerous days later…

You have mastered Mechanical Force—Soldier Nest!

You have mastered Compressed Orb Innovation—Armed Body!

You have mastered…

On his workbench was a compressed orb. Han Xiao controlled the robotic arm to complete the processing before picking up the special compressed orb and placing it flat on his palm. Mechanical Force shot from his finger to cover the compressed orb.

Hum!

The next moment, the compressed orb suddenly shrank to the size of a cell before being absorbed into his body by the Mechanical Force.

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes, sensing an extremely weak sense of burden on his body. With but a thought, a Mechanical Force arc wrapped this particle-like special compressed orb and zapped it out. The compressed orb instantly unfolded as it appeared, turning into a mechanical soldier amid the arcs of electricity. It looked as though Han Xiao directly shot a soldier from within his body.

"This is the ability to transform oneself into a military base…"

Han Xiao nodded secretly to himself. After several days of study, he had finally mastered this set of abilities.

The principle of all Class related Knowledge was the same; only the content on secondary dimensions was slightly different. This caused the basic strength of the Supers here to be incomparable to those in his explored universe. Han Xiao did not expect these skills to be very powerful either. The greatest advantages of Class-related skills was to bring about new directions of battling and more bonuses.

Because the Class Knowledge foundation was the same, he had no difficulty in learning it. With the help of the interface, he basically mastered all the Class skills taught by Jayz in just a few days. In his opinion, the more useful one was the ability to transform himself into a military base.

The level of burden is however not low. When a mechanical army is stored, the HP and upper limit of Energy will be reduced. While this upper limit is restored the moment the army is released, my HP and Energy will remain at the initial level instead of being restored…

The mechanism behind this ability was similar to that of Apostilization. To an ordinary Mechanic, even if an army was released in battle, because their current HP could not be recovered instantaneously, this would result in the Class becoming more brittle.

But this ability was tailor made for him. His strong resilience coupled with his high Energy-HP conversion meant that he could completely restore his optimum state during battle. As a result, the side effects of this 'Self Barracks' could be almost ignored, equivalent to getting a free meal.

Furthermore, with his own tankiness, the size of the troops his main body could carry was far beyond all normal Mechanics…

Indeed, developing the tankiness of a Mechanic was the path of Gods!

By the side, as Jayz watched Han Xiao experimenting with the abilities, he could not help but speak out with a weird expression.

"You've already learned it?"

"Isn't it simple?" Han Xiao did not think much of it.

"That's… that's right…" Jayz's face twitched.

He had thought that he would not be able to feel surprise again, but Han Xiao's incredulous learning speed managed to dig out emotional ripples in his dried-up husk.

Did I just meet a genius among geniuses, or did the Mechanics of subsequent iterations have such insane learning capabilities?

Furthermore, during the past few days, the two of them had sparred a little. Jayz had never seen a Mechanic with this style.

During his universe iteration, due to the lack of secondary dimensions, the strength of the Mechanics was not so overpowered, most of the time losing out due to their brittleness. Furthermore, logistics had to be done in advance to prepare the battlefield.

However, it was the first time he had seen someone like Han Xiao as a Mechanic, and he could not help but feel puzzled…

How is it that this guy could take more punches that the Pugilists themselves?

Could it be that the pursuit of a strong physique is now the mainstream route of development for the subsequent iterations of Mechanics?

This is really the case of 'if you live long enough, you'll see everything'…

Han Xiao naturally would not know what Jayz thought. After trying the new ability for a while, he turned to ask, "Next, should you pass down the techniques you have accumulated to me?"

Hearing this, Jayz calmed himself down before clicking on a virtual screen. He fiddled around a little, and soon, a dense list of technical projects was displayed on the screen.

"These are the technical materials I've compiled. You can copy some, and the rest will be sent to you when you're about to complete your mission."

Sweeping his eyes across the screen, Han Xiao was overjoyed.

Compared to his Class Knowledge, these technical materials were the highlight, representing countless new blueprints!

Within were more than just Jayz's projects. Throughout the thousand cycles, Jayz had been a wanted criminal at least nine hundred times. Relying on the cycle restart provided, he boldly invaded the database of the advanced civilizations and learned their advanced technology, which they had spent countless hours, energy, and resources collecting. His foundation was amazing, and he was willing to hand it all over.

Han Xiao quickly copied it with his own device. While this was only a part of it, it was already a huge technological treasure, enough for him to study for a long time.

There were many Gold Grade blueprints among them. When converted, it would be equivalent to saving a lot of Contribution Points from the three Universal Civilizations since there was no need to keep working for them in order to acquire blueprints.

As long as he managed to obtain the rest of Jayz technology and complete his research, his own background would rise like the speed of a supercar, leaving that Old Man Manison so far behind he would not even be able to smell his exhaust fumes.

"By the way, can you also obtain the Class Knowledge of the other four Super systems?" Han Xiao asked.

"I've collected such things before, but due to the clash between Classes, I could not learn it. I could only store it in the system. When the cycle resets, this information will be gone as well." Jayz shook his head. "However, if you want it, I can get it for you."

After so many cycles of resets, Jayz was just like a living textbook on war strategy. This was nothing difficult to him.

"Then I'll trouble you." Han Xiao nodded.

If he could obtain all the Class Knowledge of each Super system, he would have completed his Knowledge of the five major systems without the three Universal Civilizations knowing. While the content of the secondary dimensions would be lacking, the value was still huge enough.

It was just that this would be different from being taught by someone else, so he did not know if others could comprehend the Class skills on their own through just reading the content.

At this moment, Jayz slowly said, "Since I've already handed all I can to you, it's time for you to help me. Do you have a plan yet?"

Hearing this, Han Xiao nodded. "I have some ideas. I intend to borrow the resources of the Eye of Insight to build a mechanical army, first supplementing the combat power…"

Invading the Superpower Security Department was no easy task, and there were also many clones of the dimensional consciousness entity. At present, his army was insufficient, and Han Xiao intended to spend some time expanding his army.

Because this secondary dimension was merely a phantom existing as an Information Form, the mechanical army built with the Eye of Insight materials could not be taken away. They were one-off, built for this mission, so he would not have any war damages.

…

Meanwhile, in the explored universe, the opening ceremony of the fourth Pro League was less than ten days away. In this Version, countless foreign players who had joined the army went crazy trying to search for Han Xiao's figure.

During the previous few Pro Leagues, the Black Star Character Summon Card had proven its dominance, tankiness, and damage output, causing the foreign players to feel envious and jealous. Unfortunately, due to geographic reasons, they could not come into contact with Black Star, so they were unable to obtain the Character Summon Card, making it a signature of the China players.

But Version 4.0 changed everything. Players from all over the world gathered in a Star Field, resulting in countless foreign players joining the Black Star Army. Their dreams had now come true; they now possessed the opportunity to obtain the Black Star Character Summon Card.

However, at this critical juncture, Black Star went on the business trip and could not be found!

No matter how many times they inquired about it, they returned without success. Countless newcomers in the army were in pain. Seeing the date of the Pro League fast approaching, they had no choice but to change their target for their blank Character Summon Card.

While the effects they got were still good, many of them felt regret that they were unable to obtain the Character Summon Card of Black Star once. Everyone had the perception that the blank Character Summon Cards they had failed to be utilized to its maximum value.

Compared to the previous Pro Leagues, the competition system during this current version did not change much, but a few more entertaining games had been added. The fourth Pro League officially kicked off under the high expectations of the players.

Compared to the previous seasons, the smell of gunpowder in this version was much stronger. No club wished to see a country win the championship for the third consecutive season. China, which had already won the title twice consecutively, was thus constantly targeted.

…

In a flash, several months passed.

In the meeting room of the Eye of Insight, Han Xiao, Kasuyi, and Jayz were gathered together.

"Are we going to act now, Black Star?" Kasuyi asked.

Han Xiao nodded. "Yes. I've expanded the size of my troops. There is no need to keep delaying things."

In the past few months, he had borrowed the resources of the Eye of Insight to maximize the [Billion Mechanic Empire—Manison] skill granting a five-hundred-percent increase in the efficiency of creating troops. A few days ago, the size of his Mechanical Army had finally reached the storage limit of his bodily barracks, and thus, he stopped production.

"Very well, let's solve this matter fast, lest more variables appear. My God's Trait Transformation probably requires me to swallow the source energy fragments after the destruction of this secondary dimension," Kasuyi said.

He had not been idle these few months, constantly sensing the location of opportunity for his God's Trait Transformation. He finally obtained some gains.

It was no wonder the object of his senses was the entire secondary dimension. Kasuyi discovered that his opportunity was like the source energy fragment at the core of the dimension, so he became more concerned with breaking the spacetime cycle.

Han Xiao tapped to open a map. The screen displayed the location and topographic structures of the Superpower Security Department's warehouses, all of which were the results of Jayz's efforts in the previous cycles.

"The warehouse of the Superpower Security Department is within the headquarters, with many Beyond Grade As on standby as well as a large number of troops. The success rate of any frontal attack is extremely low. Thus, our first task is to infiltrate… The Heaven Concealing Apparatus can shield us from the Positioning Star Map, but normal detection methods are still effective against us, so we need another plan to infiltrate, which requires Jayz's help."

Hearing this, Jayz said, "I joined the Superpower Security Department for quite a few cycles, managing to control most of their authorities and passcodes. I can forge your information and let you sneak in, which is what I did for the outsiders previously, but there is a risk of exposure…"

The Superpower Security Department might be heavily guarded, but they could not withstand the continuous cracking from Jayz throughout the cycles. He was akin to a backstabber in the company, able to see through the flaws in the Superpower Security Department.

"Thus," Han Xiao said, "this time, we will not be using this method. The warehouse has been shrouded with a space stabilization device, and normal teleportation methods are invalid, but we only need to find a way to get people of the Superpower Security Department to send in the Throne linked to a King mechanical suit. Once it is inside the warehouses, we can bypass everyone and teleport directly."

"Nice, one step to success!" Kasuyi's eyes lit up. He loved such straightforward methods the most.

"All the items in the warehouse will be screened and isolated to remove any dangerous and useless items," Jayz explained. "It is divided into both intelligent and manual procedures, repeated thrice to prevent errors.

"But there are also exceptions. If the obtained item has been authorized by the department leader or director, it will be temporarily stored in the outer warehouse without being screened. If it's a secret order from the upper echelons of the Celestial Star Alliance, it can be stored directly in the innermost warehouse."

"So, you plan to fake the authority of the Superpower Security Department director?" Kasuyi asked.

Jayz shook his head.

"There's no need. I've kidnapped the upper echelons of the Celestial Star Alliance several times in the previous cycles. While I was killed in the end, I also obtained their authority cards. It's all in my mind, and it's not difficult to forge. So, I can send the Throne to the inner warehouses, where the dimensional consciousness entity also resides."

Kasuyi was suitably impressed. Being able to restart means you can do anything you want. What a lad.

Jayz slowly continued. "Every item in the warehouse will be stored separately. I'll send you the number where each carrier is located.

"However, once you teleport in, there will be an alarm. The supers who stay at the headquarters will come over to suppress you, so I have some technology here that can temporarily interfere with the phantoms of the Information Form, causing an effect of spacetime delay or even stagnation. However, the duration is limited, and it can only hold them off for a short while.

"You have to utilize the time to quickly kill off the dimensional consciousness entity's core. Don't get entangled with its clones. Once its program is disintegrated, the Information Form transformation technology of the World Reset Project will also be terminated, and this spacetime phantom will collapse as a chain effect."

Han Xiao nodded before adding, "To minimize resistance, we will need to show up elsewhere before teleporting. Thus, we should remove the Heaven Concealing Apparatus and let the Superpower Security Department track us with their Positioning Star Map so as to attract a group of supers to lure the tiger away from its den."

"That will do." Kasuyi expressed agreement.

The trio underwent another round of discussion, finalizing the finer details before splitting to perform their own tasks.

Chapter 1202: Sanctum Revivals and Misdirection

In the Superpower Security Department's screening office for Warehouse 001, the long track rotated, and a hexagonal mechanical device was transported in from the launch port, resembling a small shield.

Soon, this device was transported to the transparent safe in the center of the room. It possessed a variety of functions such as spatial stability anchors, electromagnetic interference, and biochemical disinfections. It could also withstand powerful impacts and high heat.

The two officers stood in front of the safe, operating a virtual screen to view the information about this object.

"This is an item sent in from the Leyton Star System. Its purpose is unknown, with no name attached. The object code is C57003A. It will temporarily be transferred to the headquarters' warehouse… Oh, there's the express authority sent in by an upper echelon here, and it has already passed the inspection and approval procedures…"

After comparing to see if the permissions and procedures were correct, the two staff members only conducted a basic inspection to confirm that the item was not dangerous before placing the item in a blank slot of the warehouse and pressing the 'Confirm' button.

Ka ka…

The next moment, four automated robotic arms stretched out from the wall, clamping onto the safe and putting it into the opening on the wall. The internal cargo pipeline moved quickly, delivering the safe to its destination.

The cargo pipeline network spread throughout the warehouses, extending in all directions through simple magnetic levitation tracks. Thus, the process of transporting at high speed was not only safe but clearly seen.

The warehouse of the Superpower Security Department was humongous, divided into multiple areas. Each warehouse was set up separately and built side by side, isolated from the outside world through high-strength transparent materials, resembling a high-tech prison. There was a booth in each warehouse, which was connected to the cargo pipeline to transport the contents directly without needing to access the warehouse.

Furthermore, there were space stability anchors, magic jammers, and automatic defense weapons in the warehouse. Not only was the security thorough, any changes would be quickly noticed.

Very quickly, the booth of an empty slot opened, and the safe was transported over with the Throne lying quietly in it.

…

Meanwhile, the Superpower Security Department was having an emergency meeting.

More than a dozen people with varied appearances sat at the conference table. The medallions on their bodies indicated their identities, with the lowest being the Deputy Directors at the Saint level.

Ever since they lost track of Han Xiao and Kasuyi, the Superpower Security Department had deployed more personnel to form a task force. There were nineteen Supers this time, with a total of five Supreme level experts, a luxurious lineup.

This was not only to capture the two people but also to figure out why the target could hide from the detection of the Positioning Star Map. Thus, the Superpower Security Department spared no effort to organize a large number of supers, wanting the plan to be foolproof.

"It's already been a few months, but we still haven't found anything on Black Star and Kasuyi. The two of them seem to have evaporated like steam! If we continue to allow such dangerous elements to move freely outside, sooner or later, it will lead to a catastrophe!" one of the upper echelons in the department exclaimed in dissatisfaction, continuously pounding on the table and glancing at Milton.

Milton's expression was gloomy.

He had initially led the team but had lost the target. Thus, the blame naturally rested on him.

He felt that he had just acted in accordance with the rules, but who knew that his target actually knew how to get rid of the lock from the Positioning Star Map? He could only take this slap to his face and look forward to catching them to redeem his pride.

However, over the next few months, the task force did not make much progress, and Milton naturally became the object of much dissatisfaction. They complained that he did not seize the opportunity at that time. While he wanted to refute that, he had nothing to defend himself with and could only sulk there.

Beep beep…

Just as everyone was fervently discussing, a communication request came in. It was from the department leader.

A virtual screen appeared on the conference table, and the department leader addressed the crowd.

"Everyone, the Positioning Star Map's effect has been restored, and we have managed to lock down the coordinates of Black Star and Kasuyi again. The reason for this is unknown, but this is our only clue in the past few months. You should be careful and make sure to catch them."

"Understood! Let's set off immediately!"

Just as his voice fell, Milton stood up abruptly with an expression of impatience, as though he could not wait to send Han Xiao to prison.

And this time, despite having the overwhelming advantage, he decided to act steadily. With the advantage of the Positioning Star Map, he planned out an ambush, aiming to catch the opponent by surprise. Everything was created to be foolproof.

…

Somewhere in the universe, a small spaceship kept at the low speed as it cruised. Han Xiao, Kasuyi, and Jayz were seated within.

Kasuyi watched the star map as he muttered, "We've already removed the Heaven Concealing Apparatus, so why are the pursuers not here yet?"

Han Xiao glanced and casually said, "Most likely, they're planning an ambush. After the previous lesson, they will not move so rashly any longer."

"In the past, there were nine of them. How many do you think they will send this time?"

"At least eleven or twelve? To be safe, maybe fifteen?" Han Xiao guessed.

Jayz interrupted him. "Around eighteen to twenty people, five of whom are at the Supreme level. I understand their mode of operations very well."

"Tsk, so many helpers…" Han Xiao smacked his lips.

Jayz did not deny it but instead explained, "The same will be true in the later stages of your universe iteration. Unless your advanced civilization regularly conducts a major cleansing, your numbers will only grow larger than ours. Those at the Saint level and above will have their data written as Information Forms, so even if they die, they still can be revived. Hence, the cleansings are actually quite limited in effectiveness…"

Hearing this, Han Xiao could not help but remember the Holy Accord Organization.

"You mean, as long as a Super reaches the Beyond Grade A level, they can be resurrected in some way, such as through the Sanctums?"

Jayz glanced at him, nodding. "The Sanctum focused on recording information that can optimize the universe, such as new Cosmic Treasures, advanced technology that's developed by advanced civilizations, and personal breakthroughs. This is all valuable information, so when one reaches the Saint level, which is the Beyond Grade A in your universe, you will be given attention to by the Sanctum and will be recorded.

"Furthermore, each Saint level is a unique existence within the universe. When your life level has undergone sublimation, you will be recorded as an Information Form. The projection will be transformed and imprinted within the Sanctum, so death is not the end for you. The Information Form allows you to achieve, in a sense, immortality as someone can use your biological Information Form as a medium to resurrect you and use the Sanctum to reshape your body and soul if they have a connection with the Sanctums."

Han Xiao was a little surprised to hear this.

Based on his understanding, the Beyond Grade A was a turning point, and once someone achieved this level, they would have the privilege of backing up the data in the Sanctum. Even if they died one day, there was still the opportunity to resurrect through the Sanctum. This was also the goal of the Holy Accord.

"Of the ten thousand Beyond Grade As here, a portion of them were probably revived in this manner."

"Some?" Jayz shook his head. "More than eighty percent of these people were revived from the Sanctums, and not just once!"

"Speak in detail." Han Xiao was interested in this, as such information was not available on the internet, being a classified secret.

"It's very simple. Because the goal of resurrection from the Sanctum is left to your descendants, the targets of resurrection for the advanced civilizations are their direct descendants and obedient allies. Thus, people join the advanced civilizations or other major organizations to work in exchange for this future resurrection. It is basically a resurrection agreement. In contrast, there is some uncertainty in leaving your descendants to revive you since the cost is great and the Sanctums are not so easily contacted. Once it fails, the entire information is lost, so everyone choses a reliable advanced civilization as their object of cooperation over time…"

"I see." Han Xiao was enlightened.

It was no wonder the Celestial Star Alliance's governance was so good, with the Beyond Grade As so well-behaved. It turned out that most of them were obedient babies who were revived after going through screening. As for those thorns, no one wished to help them revive, so they stayed dead.

In order to continue being resurrected, the majority of the Beyond Grade As had thus buried their ambitions.

Furthermore, as the advanced civilizations continued to revive their direct descendants and staunch allies, as time went by, there would only be more powerful people under their command, and their control over the universe would naturally increase.

Under the influence of various factors, there would be fewer troublemakers.

Thinking about this, a phrase jumped out in his mind.

Why does this sound like the Investiture of the Gods?

The three Universal Civilizations had yet to come into contact with the Sanctums, but when they developed to this point, would the future situation of the Beyond Grade As turn into something like this?

Han Xiao could not help but ask, "Are there any restrictions on the recovery of the Sanctums?"

"Of course there are, and many of them at that," Jayz whispered. "The first is that only those at the Saint level or above can be revived. You can think of the Beyond Grade A realm as a resurrection license.

"The second will be the paradox of personality. Since one's subjective consciousness is the criteria for distinguishing individuals, even if the body and memories are the same, if the subjective consciousness is different, they will turn out to be different individuals. While the strong can be revived in the Sanctum, are they still the original ones? This has always been a subject of controversy, where people think that it is more like a clone being brought back to life.

"The third is that individuals revived through the Sanctum will randomly lose some abilities, which seem to be directly related to the strength of your body. The stronger you were before dying, the more complete your abilities will be.

"The fourth would be the recovery of the Sanctum. Since you are a unique existence, only one of you can exist in the universe at one time. If you are not dead, then revival through the Sanctum is invalid.

"Fifth, you can only revive individuals in the same iteration. Even I don't understand this restriction. It is suspected that the recovery of the Sanctum is not its original ability but rather the ultimate plan of one of the iterations. In the end, mutations changed the Sanctum into this form… Thus, many iterations have treated the Sanctums as a breakthrough point. No one knows now how many functions the Sanctums have developed through mutation."

As he quietly listened, Han Xiao engraved all this into his memories.

From a certain perspective, the Beyond Grade As seemed to have the same characteristics as players, being able to be revived.

In this manner, controlling the Sanctums would be equivalent to controlling most of the lives of the Beyond Grade As?

I can always go to Oathkeeper to confirm my suspicions later.

Boom!

At this moment, the hull of the spaceship shook violently, and it was knocked out from its hyperdrive state. An ear-piercing alarm sounded.

"Wuwuwu! Warning! Warning! A space stabilization anchor has been detected. Hyperdrive state forced to terminate! An unknown energy source is approaching. Please watch out!"

The radar showed nineteen fluctuations at the Beyond Grade A surrounding them.

"Looks like you're right. There's indeed nineteen of them." Han Xiao raised his brows.

"It's a normal occurrence." Jayz did not care.

The three of them gazed out, immediately seeing Milton and his friends at first glance. They also saw that their spaceship had fallen into a space trap and could not escape.

At this moment, Milton's sonorous voice sounded through the public communication channel.

"Black Star, Kasuyi! Know when to give up. Leave yourselves some face!"

"Call me Void Overlord!" Kasuyi exploded in anger.

Han Xiao opened the hatch, and the trio flew out to the middle of the encirclement. Heavy auras pressured at them from all directions.

"Eh? There's another?"

Seeing Jayz, Milton frowned but quickly relaxed.

From his perspective, their prey had been forced to the point of no retreat.

He was full of confidence for this operation. With nineteen people, there was no chance they would fail.

After chasing them for several months, these wanted criminals could finally be arrested and brought to justice!

"Immediately give up all resistance and obediently follow us back to the Superpower Security Department for trial and to explain your methods of shielding from the Positioning Star Map. You might get a lenient punishment then."

Milton was confident and immediately started a psychological war, intending to weaken their resistance.

Han Xiao, however, revealed a meaningful smile before speaking in an inexplicable tone.

"There's no need to trouble you. We'll go there ourselves."

Hearing this, Milton frowned in puzzlement.

"What are you talking… Where did they go‽"

Before he could finish, three sets of mechanical suits unfolded, enveloping the bodies of the trio before they disappeared in a flash of light.

The next moment, all nineteen members stood in shock.

"Where did they go‽"

We set up a space anchor and transmission jammer. How did they even escape‽

Milton paused for two seconds before flaring up in anger, his veins throbbing.

To think that this bunch managed to run once more!

Utter humiliation!

He immediately took out the communicator and searched for their real-time coordinates on the Positioning Star Map, intending to lock onto their position before they shielded themselves once more.

However, the moment he saw the coordinates, Milton's angry expression warped into one of panic and disbelief.

The other party's coordinates were surprisingly at the headquarters of the Superpower Security Department!

This is… them surrendering?

Bullsh*t, there's something fishy going on!

Their true target was actually the headquarters?

Are they crazy?

Milton raged. He was unable to understand why these people were so bold.

Chapter 1203: Assault

Whoosh!

With a flash of light, a slightly swollen King mechanical suit appeared in the storeroom of the Superpower Security Department, instantly blasting apart the safe. The next moment, the mechanical suit was removed, revealing the figure of three people.

Han Xiao recalled his Throne, gazing around at the environment around them.

The trio were currently in a separate warehouse, their front being blocked by a transparent, high-strength material separation wall. Rows of warehouses could be seen outside, of which a small portion were empty whilst the rest had different collections.

"The switching tactics are still as easy to use as always." Han Xiao clicked his tongue.

"It seems like we've arrived. What now?" Kasuyi rubbed his eyebrows. He felt as though he was almost unable to hold back his accumulated Psychic energy any longer.

Jayz looked at the code of the warehouse before speaking. "This is No.117, and the closest dimensional consciousness entity carrier is in No.106."

At this moment, a harsh alarm suddenly echoed throughout the warehouse.

A new alloy partition wall was lowered in all the warehouses. The material was opaque, blocking out one's line of sight, and the defense strength was much higher.

"The alarm has been triggered, and the warehouse will be immediately blocked while the automatic defense robots will siege us. At the same time, the important collections will be transported away through the pipeline."

Jayz was not surprised. With a wave of his hand, a virtual screen appeared in front of him, and he quickly manipulated it before casually continuing.

"I just used the backdoor code to cancel the emergency procedure. There's no need to worry about the carriers being transferred now. However, the changes here will still inevitably alarm the staff at the headquarters, so we don't have much time."

"Then let's hurry up."

Han Xiao nodded, and spinning around, metal alloy fragments scattered around like flower blossoms as the wall of the warehouse was shattered with a kick.

The three swiftly moved toward their destination amid the harsh sirens.

Along the way, the floors and wall continuously slid open, revealing automatic defense devices within. Numerous turrets shot at the trio, firing small-caliber dark energy shots that resembled red chains, chasing after them.

Han Xiao maintained a thick psionic shield, and the dark energy beams were just like raindrops in the storm, falling on the shield with a crackle and creating ripples of red and blue on its surface. It looked harmless, but that was only because the strength of the shield was just too high. The missed beams that struck the metal ground of walls nearby caused everything that came in contact with it to melt instantly. Thus, everywhere they went, a huge mess followed.

Because of the lack of secondary dimensions, psionic energy could not be extracted directly, but the mechanical units that Han Xiao had brought in were equipped with psionic energy reactors. Using the regurgitation capabilities of psionic energy, he could use them to create controllable psionic energy seeds. Thus, Han Xiao's psionic energy tools here had an inherent advantage.

At this moment, the trio sensed two powerful individuals fast approaching. They only heard a loud bang, and two burly figures broke through the wall, exuding powerful Pugilist auras.

Locking onto the three, the Pugilists rushed forward, accompanied by angry roars.

"How dare you attack the headquarters of the Superpower Security Department! You've committed a grave sin!"

Jayz swept them with a glance before quickly explaining, "In normal circumstances, there are one to three Saint levels holding the fort daily as part of a shift system. These two are the guardians, so they're the fastest to arrive. It will take some time for the others to come from the headquarters, so don't waste time with them."

Hearing this, Kasuyi did not speak further, gazing at the two before letting out his stored inventory.

Boom!

A shockwave of Psychic energy shook from under his feet before an extraordinary Psychic force shot out. Most Psychic attacks were transparent, but this force was so condensed that it had solidified, distorting the surrounding space around it as it instantly swallowed the two figures.

This Psychic force was like a black hole exuding infinite gravitation, and just standing by his side, Han Xiao felt a weird spiritual attraction as though his soul was about to be dragged away. One could only imagine how the two Pugilists felt.

Puchi!

The sound of a balloon being pierced rang out on the spiritual level, echoing endlessly deep in one's soul.

Han Xiao focused and saw that the two Pugilists had fallen, violently convulsing. Their noses and mouth were like open faucets, leaking blood.

"Their consciousness was shattered by me. They won't be recovering for a while." After emptying his load, Kasuyi felt much more comfortable.

"Good job." Han Xiao praised.

It was totally worth holding back for a few months. Not only was the impact strong, the compression even allowed two Beyond Grade As to totally lose their combat capabilities.

If not for the fact that Psychic attacks were not very effective on the dimensional consciousness entity, Kasuyi would have saved this move to attack the Guardian directly. At this moment, Han Xiao and Jayz were carrying a full mechanical army, and their HP and Energy were suppressed. Only Kasuyi still had his complete combat power and thus could end the fight as fast as possible.

The headquarters of the Superpower Security Department had already gone into action. All the superiors urgently entered the encrypted communication channel, sharing the surveillance in the warehouse areas. Everyone was frightened as they watched.

No one expected that these criminals would be so bold as to directly attack their headquarters with some sort of strange teleportation means!

This was the first time since the Superpower Security Department was created that someone had dared to attack it!

Apart from feeling angered, everyone was deeply confused.

Why did this group of people lure the tiger away from its den and then attack the headquarters? Did they wish to steal something from the warehouse?

"No matter what the other party's goal is, we must never let them succeed!" Everyone had the same determination.

The experts on shift rushed to the warehouse at full speed. When they saw the two guardians of the warehouse arriving, they were overjoyed, but they did not expect them to not even last a second before they were knocked out.

Seeing this, everyone's expressions changed.

"Kasuyi has hidden himself too deeply. His combat capability is much stronger than we anticipated!"

"Even if we look at all the Psychics in history, he is one of the best."

Just as everyone was feeling jittery, the surveillance picture changed once more.

Boom!

They saw the No.106 warehouse being destroyed as powerful Supers appeared out of thin air. Without a second word, they rushed straight to the attacking trio.

This scene left them stunned.

"Why is there now another group?"

"Who are these people? I don't know any of them. Are they accomplices?"

"It doesn't seem like the case. They've started fighting among each other!"

"Damn it. Do they think this place is somewhere they can enter as and when they please?"

Everyone was stunned, their brains filled with question marks.

However, while they did not know the origin of the group who appeared later, they could identify them as allies since they were blocking the original offending trio.

…

The three of them continued to move forward, but before they reached No.106, they sensed eight powerful energy fluctuations appear out of thin air.

Jayz narrowed his eyes. "The Guardian and its clones are here!"

Clearing out any foreign variables was the core mechanism of the Guardian. At this moment, all that was left of it was a rigid preset program, so as long as an outsider was detected in a certain range of the carrier, the Guardian and its clones would attack the outsiders. This was its core mechanism and could not be violated.

"Their appearances can change at will. Even I don't know which is the main body. Give me some time to let me identify it, otherwise we can only try our luck."

Hearing Jayz, Han Xiao's eyes flashed, and he said, "There's no need. I have a method to lock onto the opponent's main body."

As his voice fell, Han Xiao liberated his body barracks. A large area of Mechanical Force burst out, and one by one, the mechanical army was born within the lightning. The mechanical army that was shot out directly from his body instantly shattered this warehouse area.

The lower limit of five million HP that he was suppressed to because of the barracks rebounded instantly, immediately regaining its original value of forty million, and his Energy also rose up simultaneously.

"Hu, this is much better…"

Being relieved of his burden, his entire body felt much more comfortable. All his suppressed strength had recovered.

By the side, Jayz also quickly emptied his inventory and prepared the area quickly.

The next moment, eight figures appeared in their field of vision, quickly approaching them.

Without another word, Han Xiao controlled the mechanical army to provide covering firepower. He saw the eight figures all using their own means to prop up different types of shield, causing energy shockwaves to burst repeatedly in the air around them.

The combat information instantly refreshed, and opening his interface, the corners of his mouth curled up as he pointed decisively at one of the figures.

"Found it. That's the main body!"

It was not difficult for him to distinguish the main body from the clones, as the interface exposed the enemy's information.

"So quickly‽" Jayz was stunned, almost unable to react.

We've just fought face-to-face, and I haven't even established a connection, but you've already locked onto the target? How is your efficiency even higher than mine?

Jayz could not help but think of the previous few batches of outsiders. Except for the first batch, the other two had fallen at this step as they could not distinguish the main body, thus becoming embroiled in a bitter battle where they were finally surrounded and killed by the Superpower Security Department directors.

This time, the outsiders are much more reliable as compared to the previous three, especially this Black Star. In his Universe iteration, he is probably someone who can call on the clouds and winds…

Jayz was secretly pleased.

"I'll leave the main body to you. I'll delay the clones!" He did not doubt Han Xiao's judgement, immediately controlling his army to wrap up the other seven.

He then threw out a special targeted device to constrain the dimensional consciousness entity within the carrier. While the opponent could not violate the core mechanism, he did this as an insurance to ensure that the entity would not escape.

Han Xiao did not hesitate either, absorbing part of his troops to turn into a medium sized Mechanical Deity, launching a fierce attack on the Guardian. Kasuyi cooperated on the side to attack the Guardian while holding onto the other seven clones, giving Han Xiao more room for battle.

The Guardian was originally the incarnation of the dimensional consciousness entity, and thus, it was capable of controlling a part of the dimensional energy. It only temporarily shaped itself as an entity in order to kill the outsiders. Due to the pre-set program, it possessed extremely high combat capabilities, at least in the Supreme realm, even having inexhaustible Energy.

Naturally, Han Xiao would not hold anything back and went all out, the Celestial Punishment Edge slashing away at the energy shield surrounding the Guardian.

Boom!

The eleven Beyond Grade As battling directly blasted the warehouses around them into pieces.

Junk and fragments floated in the universe, and it was unknown just how many Cosmic Treasures were destroyed.

Seeing that the warehouse had exploded, all the upper echelons of the Superpower Security Department almost felt their hearts stop.

"Argh! Kill this damned group of criminals on the spot! Don't even allow one of them to run!"

The department leader's eyes turned red with anger.

In outer space, Han Xiao was manipulating the Mechanical Deity to give the Guardian heavy hits. At this moment, he suddenly felt a sudden warning from his senses. He turned around to see seven to eight of the directors quickly approaching, with more than ten Saint levels close behind.

Before they arrived, various long-ranged attacks had already come pouring in, forming a floor of colorful energy within the universe as they attacked the Mechanical Deity from all angles.

Even if the data showed that Black Star had an amazing physique, the experts present did not believe that he could withstand the firepower of dozens of people.

Han Xiao only glanced at them, not even bothering to dodge as he threw out a strange prismatic device.

This device shook in midair, and a strange wave spread out, forming a huge spherical dome as it covered this area.

The next instant, the time flow in the field slowed down drastically, with all the members of the Superpower Security Department and their attacks suddenly stagnating. Only Han Xiao, Kasuyi, and the Guardian were unaffected by this slow motion; even Jayz was hit by it.

This was one of Jayz's special inventions, specifically targeting this secondary dimension, which could cause this phantom spacetime to be strongly disturbed and stagnate. Only outsiders and the dimensional consciousness entity were unaffected.

Without this technology, the plan to attack the Superpower Security Department would have been nigh impossible.

"What the hell is this ability ‽"

While their actions had slowed down, the Superpower Security Department present retained their acuity, and their anger turned into horror.

Rendered unable to move, watching the enemy ravage the warehouse at will caused everyone's heart to bleed. It felt as though they were husbands watching their wives cheat right in front of themselves.

Chapter 1204: Successor

The dozens of Beyond Grade As were suspended in midair. This scene was magnificent, but Han Xiao and Kasuyi had no time to appreciate them. Both of them focused on dealing with the Guardian.

The effect of the spacetime interference was limited, so now was the time for them to burst forth with explosive strength. If the Guardian could not be killed directly before the effect of the interference device ended, then Han Xiao would have no choice but to use the King and escape with the other two.

The more outsiders who died in this secondary dimension, the more clones the Guardian would have. Right now, they were the fourth batch, and the difficulty was already frightening.

The main body and its seven clones were not affected, still moving around freely. Even if Kasuyi took the initiative to contain the clones, he had limited Energy and could not deal with everything. From time to time, the attacks of the clones managed to bypass his defenses, falling on Han Xiao's Mechanical Deity body.

In order to maintain his damage output, Han Xiao did not evade any attacks, rather simply tanking them head on without defending. This was completely a trade damage for damage playstyle. With his own tankiness, the occasional attacks that came through not only did not cause much threat to him but also continuously accelerated the speed at which he stacked temporary attribute bonuses, making his damage output higher.

At this moment, he did not hold anything back, completely utilizing all his explosive abilities and even using his armies and the Mechanical Deity in a blitzkrieg strategy.

All his overload abilities were activated. [Legendary Battle Technique]'s true damage was triggered, and [Painful Revenge] allowed him to exert a powerful lethality, which could cause his melee damage to increase by 1.5% of his HP every time his total HP decreased by 3%.

This ability came from the leader of DarkStar. At the beginning when he obtained it, he was only a Calamity Grade with a total HP value of over a hundred thousand. However, he was now a Beyond Grade A hegemon with HP value over forty million, and even 1.5% of his total HP converted to damage would still be around six hundred thousand extra damage!

Furthermore, in order to continue to regenerate his Energy, Han Xiao had controlled his weapon within the Mechanical Deity to fire on his body, so his HP dropped and rose constantly, triggering the [Painful Revenge] skill again and again… Even if ordinary damage could be shielded against or reduced, his enemy could not cover against the lethality caused by [Painful Revenge]. The power of his every hit was far beyond what a normal Beyond Grade A could deal.

Coupled with his bonuses from the Machinery Faith, his level ten God's Trait Transformation—Machinery, [Fearless Heart], and [Polar Channel Flow—Blood Rage] along with all his Gold Grade equipment, not forgetting his post-explosive attributes obtained through the level 340 Promotion… even Han Xiao was unaware now terrifying his damage would be when he attacked with all his strength.

He only saw that under the concentrated firepower, the energy shield summoned by the Guardian basically exploded the moment it appeared, and its HP value steadily dropped at a fast speed.

It might have been a dimensional consciousness entity with inexhaustible energy, but the strength of its body limited its energy output. The speed at which it replenished its own energy shield could not keep up with the efficiency of destruction that Han Xiao wrought.

If it was a life form individual with consciousness, then it would naturally understand that it was not Han Xiao's opponent. However, the Guardian did not have any emotions and could only act according to the incomplete preset procedure it had, unable to violate its core mechanism to fight to the end.

The Guardian's advantage would be its flexibility. Within its territory, Han Xiao racial talents were frozen. He was unable to use his Void methods, making him unable to keep up with the Guardian's speed. While his Mechanical army was powerful, most of their long-ranged attacks were avoided by the Guardian.

"A lot of output is being wasted. It has certain characteristics of an energy life form, and its HP can be restored quickly. If this drags on, my success rate of destroying it before the jamming device fails will be about forty percent, which is a bit low… My [Gene Liberation] has not been used yet, but the Cooldown is rather long, so I'll only have time to use it once. The output of that needs to be maximized…"

Han Xiao kept pouring out firepower, as his eyes shifted around.

It seemed like he had to utilize his trademark skill…

The Mechanical Deity suddenly disintegrated, turning into a mechanical army that filled the sky. Han Xiao's body escaped, opening his arms in full to show off his 'weak' body, as though he planned to seduce the Guardian.

Sure enough, without another word, the Guardian took the initiative to rush over. In his default model, the strategy to combat a Mechanic was to attack them directly when they were exposed.

Han Xiao did not dodge but greeted him and allowed the Guardian to smash his hard pectoral muscles. A shock wave was emitted, but Han Xiao did not care for the HP lost in his blow. His arms circled and bound his target tightly as he grinned.

"Little kid, you still dare run? Come to papa."

He had not used this method for a long time. The main reason was because the explored universe knew of his reputation, so only a fool would respond to his provocation. Only in the face of a person who was unaware of his abilities could his trademark shine.

Without any hesitation, Han Xiao activated [Gene Liberation], at the same time giving instructions to his Mechanical army.

"Eat this! Heaven! Earth! As! One!"

Boom!

In an instant, endless psionic cannon fire drowned the two figures, and a dazzling light ball expanded, occupying everyone's sight.

"A Mechanic can battle in this manner‽" Jayz, who was unable to move, gaped at the scene, feeling that his knowledge had been broadened. "Do all youngsters these days play with such high stakes?"

By the side, Kasuyi, who was fighting with the clones, felt his right eye twitching. The energy fluctuations caused by the feedback made his heart beat fast, and he felt a strong threat to his life.

The tens of Superpower Security Department members had an expression of disbelief.

They were all wondering what sort of hatred and resentment these two groups actually had to fight so desperately with each other.

Didn't these two wanted criminals attack our headquarters? Why did they even concentrate on dealing with this group of mysterious Supers rather than sneak attack us while we're stuck in place? We seem to have become onlookers now…

As this thought flashed through everyone's mind, the ball of light caused by the energy reaction suddenly exploded, bursting out as a terrifying energy shockwave.

Boom!

The surrounding machinery and people were all swept away, revealing a large empty area.

As the light ball dissipated, everyone saw Han Xiao hovering alone at the center of the explosion, covered in blood, with a shattered shell of a body in front of him.

Han Xiao was expressionless and appeared as though it was a normal occurrence, but in fact, he was breaking out in a cold sweat internally.

F*ck me, that was a close shave. To think that my attack has reached this level. I almost gave myself a one-way ticket to heaven…

Because the random coefficient of [Gene Liberation] gave him the highest increase at twenty percent, the lethality that his army exploded with shocked him, the large fluctuations in his HP giving him multiple heart attacks.

The scale of my troops I control now is enormous, and their attack power is completely different from before. This trick should be used with caution in the future, or else it will one day be me perishing together with my enemy…

Han Xiao secretly sighed in relief.

With him even in danger of dying, the Guardian would naturally be more tragic, being killed on the spot. From fighting to going to heaven, it did not even have time to leave behind its last words… although it would not have said anything.

"You killed him just like that?" Kasuyi's eyes widened.

He had thought that it would be a vicious battle, but he did not expect Black Star's current lethality to be so terrible that the target would be eliminated so quickly. Such efficiency was frightening.

While he did not express it clearly, his tone said it all—it was actually so simple?

Hearing Kasuyi, Han Xiao knew what he was thinking and snapped, "You thought it was easy, but that's because I'm that good! If it was you, we would definitely have had to escape today."

Let's not bully him anymore.

Even if it was another pinnacle Beyond Grade A, it would be a situation where it would be a miracle if they could survive. Only someone as abnormal as him would be able to handle such a mission.

The communication between both of them happened in an instant. At this moment, the chain reaction caused by the destruction of the dimensional consciousness entity finally appeared.

They saw the remains of the Guardian automatically decompose into dust-like particles, disappearing in an instant. With it as the epicenter, the same signs appeared in the surrounding space. The affected area continued to spread in all directions, as if a singularity had collapsed and the entire dimension began to collapse as a chain effect.

This mutated Information Form phantom of the spacetime cycle was like an intricate instrument that was barely maintaining its balance. The dimensional consciousness entity was the core component of this entire instrument, so when the core met with a problem, the entire instrument would naturally stop operating. The error would probably also result in a chain effect of the entire instrument breaking down.

Only the two outsiders Han Xiao and Kasuyi, along with the objects they brought in were unaffected. The other materials belonging to this spacetime cycle were beginning to decompose. The first ones to go were the mechanical armies, as well as the seven Guardian clones.

Because the foundation of the spacetime cycle had been unraveled, the effect of the interference device was naturally rendered ineffective. When the members of the Superpower Security Department saw this scene, they all looked surprised, subconsciously moving to continue the encirclement.

However, one of the directors who was the closest to the epicenter also began to automatically decompose. Before everyone's horrified eyes, he turned into flying ash in merely the blink of an eye. His Supreme level strength had no way to resist this.

"What's happening? What did you guys do‽"

"Quickly run! You'll die!"

The crowd was so shocked that they no longer bothered about arresting them, instead turning to escape.

Jayz, however, stayed where he was, smiling slightly at Han Xiao.

Han Xiao felt a vibration from his communicator and took a look. The rest of the technical information had been sent by Jayz; he had upheld his end of the deal.

In addition, Jayz had felt behind another message.

"Black Star, our World Reset Plan was not a complete failure; at least we have left this legacy for the future.

"I know you have always been guarded against me, and I admit that I indeed have some selfishness to this. I don't need to hide it from you now. I poured all my knowledge into you due to the deal and also my experiment…

"Remember the mechanism of the Sanctums I told you about? Reviving a Beyond Grade A requires a medium with the target information… and you, who have inherited my knowledge, can serve as my medium now.

"If a day comes when you ever manage to succeed in communicating with the Sanctums, please try to revive me across iterations. Whether it succeeds or fails, it will be a precious piece of intelligence for you.

"However, even if the resurrection is successful, I will not retain my memory from this loop. It will be a brand new me, so this should be our last time meeting. While our time was short, I am happy to have met you… my successor of this iteration."

Looking up, Han Xiao saw Jayz with a relieved smile as his whole body gradually turned into flying ash, disappearing without a trace.

Seeing this, Han Xiao muttered, "Successor, huh?"

Chapter 1205: A New Calling

The message left behind by Jayz was full of expectations.

Han Xiao glanced at the technical information now saved on his communicator and suddenly felt a heavy weight.

The phantom of history had disappeared, so before the three Universal Civilizations could study the mystery that was the Sanctums, the technology he held would be unique. While it was only a part of the technology obtained by Jayz, it was still precious.

The meaning behind this was not just a personal benefit but also a method to change the development direction of the universe, and the initiative to change the direction was now in his hands.

Since this was 'A Relay Across Iterations', then according to his current situation, calling him the successor technically was not wrong… This technology had already made him qualified to control the development of the universe in the near future on a whim.

If he chose to undertake such a calling, how he dealt with this technology would become a problem.

"… No matter what, everything will have to wait until my research is completed," Han Xiao muttered.

Within the technical materials available, there was a huge portion that would be beneficial to the development of the civilizations. If he hid it away like a baby, then it would be wasted. The final place they ended up in should be toward the Galactic Society, to contribute toward the entire universe and change the lives of the galactic residents.

It was just that, with his temperament, it was impossible for him to make a contribution for free. He would only develop it to sell or exchange part of the technology for resources from the three Universal Civilizations. Regardless of which he chose, his status and the power of the Black Star Army would rise to a whole new level, becoming an unmatched giant.

As for Jayz's request, Han Xiao could not decide if he should agree.

These thoughts passed him by in a flash. The collapse of the secondary dimension was still occurring, and this situation was exactly the same as the decay and demise the other secondary dimensions faced.

The speed of decomposition slowly grew faster, as the scope of the chain reaction expanded in an exponential manner. Space was pulled and torn apart, while the stars dimmed one by one as they were extinguished. Replacing them was a weird light glow—that was the external manifestation of the thinning of the space wall.

The light spots suddenly split open, turning into holes in the space wall. The chaotic space stream outside instantly poured in, and the space storms raged and accelerated the decay of the dimension.

"Run!"

Seeing this, Kasuyi's eyes lit up, and he flew out along the hole in the space wall. Han Xiao did not stop him, following him closely.

The two of them returned to the chaotic space stream outside the secondary dimension world, and they felt that all of their pressures seemed to have vanished. Every breath they took was like a new lease of life.

"We're finally out."

Sensing the connection of the Void Dimension, Kasuyi breathed a sigh of relief. He hurried to refill his lacking Energy before he finally felt safe.

The two then turned to look at where they came from, only to see that the secondary dimension, which had been almost boundless when they first arrived, was collapsing inward as though it was an inflated balloon being released of its air.

Under their gazes, the secondary dimension was finally torn apart by the turbulent chaotic space stream, disintegrating with bursts of iridescent energy as it blended into the space storm.

Kasuyi's eyes suddenly brightened up. He released his Psychic energy in a direction, taking out a few pieces of source energy fragments as he smiled.

Han Xiao swept him with a glance. "You found your opportunity for transformation?"

"If I'm not mistaken, my senses point to the source energy fragments of this dimension. I've vaguely felt the entry point of the next level of God's Trait Transformation. So long as I go back and ponder for a while, I'll definitely be able to enter the next stage. It's all thanks to your help."

Kasuyi was satisfied.

He was now feeling fortunate that he had chosen Han Xiao as a teammate. If he had chosen someone else, the trip would likely have been more of a death encounter, but with Han Xiao around, he was in no danger at all.

While this guy is shameless, he's just too reliable!

"Congratulations." Han Xiao gave some perfunctory words before pointing to the core fragments. "He who sees it has a share. Pass me one."

"Hey, you really have a thick skin. You've swallowed all of Jayz technical information, yet you still dare to say this."

Kasuyi looked disgusted at him but still threw a piece of the core fragment to Han Xiao.

Right now, he was in a good mood, and so, he could not be bothered to squabble with Han Xiao. Besides, his senses told him that he only needed a piece of the source fragment, so he would not be stingy.

Receiving the fragment, Han Xiao played with it a little. Gazing at the item details, he shook his head.

While the secondary dimension was special, the source energy fragments were not unique. It would be impossible to re-cultivate a similar spacetime cycle loop. That place was a Space Wonder of its own.

However, neither of them left immediately. They stayed where they were, watching with their own eyes the complete disappearance of the dimension as it disappeared without a trace.

At this time, a notification popped up on Han Xiao's interface.

_____________________

The second chain mission of [A Relay Across Iterations] has been completed!

You have received 150 billion EXP, 1 Random Reward, and 1 [Character Summon Card - Jayz]

Character Summon Card - Jayz: [Mechanic—Insight] - You have obtained extraordinary insight and can summarize the laws of the world more efficiently, improving your ability of mechanical research. When using this ability, the skill [Universal Simulation] is strengthened, and when developing blueprints, the efficiency and success rates are higher. There's also a chance to generate black technology. Number of times used: 0/5

_____________________

"This is an ability related to R&D…"

Han Xiao nodded in his head.

Jayz's abilities in R&D were undoubtedly among the best, able to produce technology with specific effects such as the Heaven Concealing Apparatus. Han Xiao had a lot of combat abilities in his hands in the form of Character Summon Cards, so this time, the support effect of this Character Summon Card met his needs.

Scrolling down, he discovered that the notifications had yet to end.

_____________________

The third chain mission begins!

Mission Requirements: Succeed in entering at least one Sanctum and establish a connection.

Reward: 200 Billion EXP, 2 Random Rewards, 3 Fragments of the Related Sanctum, and unlock the next chain mission.

_____________________

"The next mission requires me to enter the Sanctums…"

Han Xiao squinted his eyes.

Based on what Jayz had said, Sanctums stored multiple iterations of materials, but it was not a public library where anyone could enter to view. Be it an individual or a civilization, there needed to be a certain action to allow them to connect with the Sanctum before they could obtain information from within.

Oathkeeper had mentioned before that there were six Sanctums in total, but no one knew if the different Sanctums had different methods needed for communication. Furthermore, Oathkeeper had yet to return even after such a long time, so it was estimated that this should be no simple matter.

Within the reward, they also provided Sanctum fragments. Han Xiao possessed quite a few fragments of the First Sanctum, and he originally thought that it was needed for entry, but now it seemed like it served another purpose.

After obtaining so many secrets, Han Xiao had already made up his mind. Even if he did not get the mission, he would still have chosen to go and visit a Sanctum once. This mission was an unexpected coincidence and gain for him.

As for the other mission, [Kasuyi's Invitation] also showed as completed. He obtained another 450 Billion experience and got six random rewards as well as three Character Summon Cards.

The Character Summon Cards were all from Kasuyi but with different abilities, one improving mental resistance, the other a Void Talent. The last was [The Ancient Ones], providing amazing burst damage.

Kasuyi's Favorability also went up by thirty points, and he obtained a God's Trait Transformation point. At the same time, he was also rewarded with a new Milestone, [Witness of the Old Times]. The introduction showed that due to his rich experience in life, his Intellect and Mystery attributes all improved by three percent.

The effect is pretty strong. It will be quite useful…

While he was browsing through the mission reward, Kasuyi's voice suddenly sounded in his mind, with mixed emotions.

"What are you going to do now?"

Turning his head, he saw a rather complicated expression on Kasuyi's face.

Having witnessed the disappearance of the final vestiges of the previous universe iteration, albeit a phantom, Kasuyi felt it a regret, yet he felt that this entire adventure was pretty dreamlike.

Han Xiao knew what Kasuyi was thinking, so he shook his head. "I'll withhold this technology for now and conduct my own research. Now is not the time to expose all these secrets."

"That's right. The universe iteration is still too far away from us. Those are issues that the three Universal Civilizations should consider. Although a Beyond Grade A is a powerful individual, we are small in the face of the big picture." Kasuyi sighed. "Anyway, the technical information is in your hands, so you're in control. What you do with it is your own business; it has nothing to do with me."

Han Xiao did not speak but instead stared meaningfully at him.

He only felt Han Xiao's meaningful gaze, but Kasuyi already understood what Han Xiao wanted to say. He spoke with a smile. "Relax. While I'm in the know, I will not cause trouble. Once I disclose this information to any outsider, I won't be able to stay out of trouble as well… Don't worry about me reporting this to the Arcane Church. I'm not that close to them."

For the operation this time, Kasuyi once again gained a brand-new impression of the strength Han Xiao had. He was frightened, and thus, he did not wish to face Han Xiao if possible.

Since only the two of them knew of this information, if anything leaked out, Black Star would know that it was Kasuyi who did it right away. In his opinion, having one less matter to worry about was better than one more. Unlike the Old Man Manison who always liked to make the headlines, Kasuyi preferred to stay low.

Moreover, he was not a direct subordinate of the Arcane Church, so he had no intention of reporting this. If he was so loyal to the Arcane Church, he would not have bothered to put on a show during the attack on Hila.

Han Xiao finally nodded before changing the topic.

"You've also seen what happened to the Beyond Grade As under the rule of the Celestial Star Alliance. The Sanctum is our lifeblood, and we cannot allow the advanced civilizations to monopolize this information, or else we will repeat the same mistakes."

Hearing this, Kasuyi's expression also turned solemn.

With this episode, he deeply realized that the Beyond A realm was a glorious yet despairing presence.

"You're right. The three Universal Civilizations will research this step sooner or later. Since we have discovered the meaning behind the Sanctums ahead of them, we should prepare for it."

"In order to avoid becoming like the Celestial Star Alliance, our Beyond Grade A Association itself must first gain control of the Sanctums," Han Xiao muttered. "Fortunately, we've now established an association. As individuals, we're unreliable. Only an association is qualified to assume this future so that future Beyond Grade As need not surrender their freedom and beg the advanced civilizations for benefits."

"In the beginning, when you promoted the establishment of the association, you really had some foresight," Kasuyi praised.

I never expected that the association would be so useful… Han Xiao grinned secretly to himself.

"Cough, in any case, I have some clues about the Sanctum in my hands. After some time, I'll begin to pursue these traces."

"If you need any help, just let me know," Kasuyi said.

If they were to wait until the advanced civilizations mastered the means of revival through the Sanctums like the Celestial Star Alliance, it would be too late for the Beyond Grade As to unite. On the road of development, many opportunities only came knocking once.

In this respect, both of them had no selfish thoughts. The Sanctums were the lifeline of the Beyond Grade As, and monopolizing them would only make them enemies of all Beyond Grade As in the universe, a target of public criticism.

Only when the association undertook such an important mission would it then be accepted by all. In this manner, the nature of the association would become extremely important, and the alliance between all members would be unshakable, not breaking due to internal factors.

Right now, only the two of them knew of this inside information, and both had the same goal. With this bond, it was equivalent to them signing a pact. For Han Xiao, his advantage was that Kasuyi who had always been neutral was supporting his faction, which would increase his influence.

While the two of them had reached a tacit agreement not to divulge what they saw this time, they both knew that there were some things that had already changed.

Based on the intelligence they received, they had already formulated a new plan, which would inevitably have an indirect impact, just like the butterfly effect. Unless both of them pretended that nothing had happened, the scope of the impact would only grow, and sooner or later, it would affect the entire universe.

With this matter resolved, both of them prepared to return. However, a movement in their senses made them pause. They looked over to see a huge group of Space Lice wandering aimlessly.

"Oh, a few months have already passed, yet these little cuties have not left."

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled as he thought of his previous idea of breeding these Space Lice.

Kasuyi had also completed his God's Trait Transformation and was more relaxed. He smiled as well. "I should get some specialties on the return trip back, so I might as well catch some and see if they can be raised in the Void Dimension."

Both of them shared a smile, a similar weird aura surrounding them.

Chapter 1206: Return

In the Black Star Army's Emerald Star Cluster Division, hundreds of spaceships were docked in the silver-white airport terminal, with all colors and varied models. From within these spaceships stepped out a group of crew members who obviously did not belong to the army. Stepping down, they looked around curiously, lining up in loose lines under the command of the heavily armed army members as they chatted.

"We've finally arrived. This is indeed the base of the Black Star Army. It's truly well-defended."

"Haha, my resume has undergone four rounds of screening and finally passed the review. We'll be members of the Black Star Army in the future."

"I hope that I can go to a position with good benefits…"

"Will we be able to see Black Star this time? According to the usual practice, every group of newcomers will have to enter the initiation ceremony where the Army Commander meets with us. Even his avatar will do!"

Everyone had some measure of excitement on their face. These people were all interstellar mercenaries who had applied to the Black Star Army.

Right now, the Black Star Army's sphere of influence had spread across multiple Star Fields. With various businesses bringing ample capital flow to them, the army had been actively hiring new mercenaries. This was especially so after Han Xiao was hired as the Special Consultant for the three Universal Civilizations.

After so many years of operation by Han Xiao, the army already had an irreplaceable influence in the universe. According to market research, if all free Supers in the universe had to join a faction, then 41.3% of them listed the Black Star Army as their first choice, surpassing even the three Universal Civilizations.

The Black Star Army could be considered as something like the 'Fortune 500' companies back on Earth. Furthermore, its potential was still being realized, and its prospects were broad.

Just as everyone was excitedly discussing their success, an army spaceship sailed into the VIP dock of the airport, attracting the attention of everyone present. There were two emblems on the hull of the spaceship, one being that of the army, while the other was a crimson snake on a wine-red background, which was the personal emblem of Hila.

With a hiss, the hatch opened, and a group of armed female warriors wearing crimson light armor walked out neatly as they stood on both sides of the gangway. The emblem on their chests indicated that they were the elite guards of Hila, known as the 'Tri-Headed Snake Rangers'.

As the Deputy Army Commander, Hila possessed a lot of authority, which allowed her to form her own personal guard like Han Xiao.

Ta, ta, ta!

The crisp sound of leather shoes striking the ground was heard as Hila walked out of the hatch.

She wore a pair of red sunglasses on the bridge of her nose, her ears decorated with serpentine silver earrings, and she had on a gorgeous red uniform that resembled a lady's business suit. It had gold threads as trimming as well as a black and gold cloak wrapped around on her shoulders, complete with a red fluff on the collar of the cloak.

Everyone's eyes immediately focused on her, admiration appearing on their faces.

"She's the second-in-command of the Army, the Goddess of Death, Hila. What a strong aura…"

Some of them revealed wistful expressions. "It would be great if I could work under her."

"Only the elite of the army are eligible to be selected as part of the personal guards. Even people like us were all rejected. You're still dreaming of it?"

At this moment, Hila walked with her guards to the front of the crowd, scanning everyone present. Her powerful aura suffused within the crowd, and the commotion gradually stopped. Everyone only felt a sense of oppression in their hearts, not daring to speak.

Seeing this, Hila spoke in a cold tone. "The Army Commander is currently absent, so I will preside over your enrollment ceremony. My time is precious, so I'll save the welcome steps and test your strength directly. The army speaks with strength, so this will be related to your position arrangement after joining the army. I hope you can last as long as possible."

Finishing all she wanted to say in one breath, Hila was too lazy to explain more, directly letting out her pressure and sweeping across the whole field.

Many of them felt a crushing sense before they could react, the pressure penetrating their body and soul. Everyone trembled and looked as though they would fall to the ground any time.

Flop, flop!

Group after group could not bear the pressure Hila was exuding and fell down. The longest could only support themselves for about thirty seconds, their faces flushed and gasping as though they were drowning.

Seeing this, Hila withdrew her pressure, looking at her watch as she lightly said, "Those who are in the top ten percent will be the team leaders. As for the others, Phillip will automatically assign positions based on your performance just now. You are to report to your respective departments immediately. The ceremony is over."

Finished, she turned around and entered the base with her guards, not sparing another glance at the crowd on the ground.

Generally speaking, the newcomers' joining ceremony would introduce to them the history of the army so as to cultivate a sense of belonging. Hila, however, did not care for such things. From disembarkation to the completion of the test, the entire process took no more than three minutes.

On the way, Hila took out her communicator and summoned Phillip. She asked with furrowed brows, "By the way, can you contact Black Star yet?"

"Not at all, hum…" Phillip lowered his head, tapping his fingertips as he felt guilty.

"Where did this guy go? To actually be out of touch for several months!"

Hila's expression was uncertain.

She knew that Han Xiao had run off to the secondary dimensions, and communication there was inconvenient. But even so, Han Xiao should not have been disconnected from Phillip.

Just a few months ago, Phillip had said that Han Xiao was completely disconnected and could not be reached by any means. Hila thus became vigilant and could not help but think of the Holy Accord Organization that he had encountered in the secondary dimension.

Could it be that the Army Commander had been attacked again?

Hmm… it did not seem to be surprising though.

In order to not cause any turmoil and suspicion to the outside world, she had asked Phillip to block off all news, maintaining the operation of the army on the surface while secretly investing resources to detect any traces of Black Star.

Han Xiao was the soul of the army. The moment he lost contact, the army would drop by a significant deal in the eyes of the Beyond Grade As. Hila could only temporarily carry this burden, halting her training and returning from the Underworld to helm the army.

No results were found even after several months, and Hila was getting worried.

She had decided that if there was still no information about him after three more months, she would call upon her teacher Ames to enter the secondary dimensions to search for Han Xiao.

Suddenly, Hila paused, and a strange look appeared on her face.

"You guys are to be on standby. I have something to do."

Her figure vanished, leaving her Personal Guards on the spot looking at each other.

…

At the same time, Hila's figure appeared in the Underworld, where Onicelu revealed herself.

"What is this about?"

"I discovered a group of weird creatures approaching the Underworld. They seem to be cosmic life forms that live in space storms. Monsters born within this environment are not easy to deal with, and I'm just afraid that they are species that feed on the secondary dimensions." Onicelu expressed her concern.

Hila frowned slightly. Right now, she was bound to the Underworld, so protecting it was her responsibility.

"I'll make them retreat."

She rose up, turning into a red meteor as she flew out of the space wall following Onicelu's instructions. However, she did not proceed further, merely waiting at the spot for the enemy's advancement.

The dimensional energy of the Underworld formed a spherical light film around Hila, which provided her defense whilst preventing her from being swept away of the chaotic space stream.

Not long after, a whirlpool-like wormhole appeared in the space stream, and huge Space Lice rushed out in alarming numbers.

"So many‽" Hila subconsciously clenched her fists.

She had been in the secondary dimension for a while, thus knowing that there were some dangers that could even threaten the lives of the Beyond Grade As. While she had never encountered any Space Louse, she instinctively felt the threat, proving that this group of monsters could not be killed casually.

While Hila was not worried about her safety, there were just too many for herself to handle. She could not guarantee that she could protect the entire Underworld.

"If only Black Star was here…"

Faced with this situation, Hila could not help but miss Han Xiao's mechanical army.

"Right now, I can only rely on myself…"

Hila revolved her Energy, preparing to make the pre-emptive strike.

But at this exact moment, a familiar voice rang out in her mechanical suit communication channel, freezing her movements.

"Hila?"

Among the Space Lice, Han Xiao, who was herding up these cuties, felt the fluctuations coming off from Hila and looked over. His eyes brightened immediately.

In a flash, he appeared before her, smiling.

"I've not seen you for a while. Did you miss me?"

"I miss…" Hila caught herself before she subconsciously spoke out and continued in surprise. "Why are you here? Where did you go this time?"

"I went over to the secondary dimensions to take a gander. The signal there is not good. Did you see the cuties yet? These were my war trophies. I intend to let them settle down around the Underworld to serve as a line of defense. Their combat power is pretty impressive…"

Han Xiao babbled on with the introduction, pretending that he did not see Hila's hesitation.

After losing contact for several months, he knew that Hila would definitely worry, but he did not intend to disclose his experience of the trip for the time being. Thus, he decided to hide the truth and simply gloss over it.

After listening for a bit, Hila still could not resist interrupting Han Xiao's words, "Do you know the impact your loss of contact has brought us? If it was not for me blocking the news, there would be a lot of people in the army that wavered…"

Han Xiao laughed. "You're the Deputy Army Commander. There's still you even if I'm not around. Nobody will be able to do anything. I have faith in you."

Hearing this, Hila's expression became a lot better.

She vaguely felt that Han Xiao was hiding something from her, but she did not want to ask more. The most important part was that he had returned.

Hila did not continue questioning him and turned her attention toward the weird looking Space Lice.

"When these groups of life forms join forces, can their battle strength truly reach the pinnacle Beyond Grade A level?"

"Their attack power won't be as good, but their defenses can indeed reach such a stage. They feed on chaotic space streams, so not only will they not attack the secondary dimension but also provide protection. They like the environment around a secondary dimension, so they usually settle down and use it as a nest, hence attacking all outsiders." Han Xiao nodded.

After catching a batch of Space Lice, he had split up with Kasuyi and headed home. Through the journey, he did research and discovered the habits of the Space Lice, which allowed them to coexist in harmony with the secondary dimensions. They were suitable for guarding homes and were simply natural bodyguards.

"Alright, as long as there's no danger, I have no issue keeping them here." Hila agreed after thinking. "My teacher came to look for you three times but was rejected by me. Remember to go see her."

"Ok." Han Xiao assented and asked, "Anything happen with the association while I was absent?"

"The same old. There has been no change, except for the lack of fighting between you and Manison. No one is moving for now. It's basically a formality."

"Those fence sitters only wish for me to get things done…" Han Xiao's mouth contorted slightly.

In the eyes of ordinary people, the Beyond Grade As were people of high authority and prestige, but in his eyes, they were a group of boring people.

He then rejected Hila's invitation to get abused before throwing the Space Lice at the Underworld and using the King to teleport himself back to the Army's Base camp in the Emerald Star Cluster.

…

With a blur in his vision, Han Xiao returned to his office and found Sylvia sitting there with her legs propped up on the table.

Seeing that someone had suddenly appeared in the room, Sylvia was taken aback. But after recognizing Han Xiao, she calmed down, and instead of standing up, she purposely struck her feet on the table once, huffing as she angrily said, "Oh, isn't this His Excellency Black Star? You still know your way back? I thought you had forgotten all about us."

Han Xiao did not show offence, rather walking up to Sylvia and patting her head. Feeling her hair, he smiled.

"Seems like you have worked hard these few months. It's been hard on you."

"Scram." Sylvia knocked his hand away before standing up and snorting. "I could not contact you, and there's a large backlog of issues that you need to handle. Hurry and clear them. I'm still waiting."

Having finished speaking, she turned to leave, but suddenly, she realized something just as she reached the door. She turned back, picking up the jacket she draped over the chair and the gold rimmed glasses on the table, rolling her eyes at Han Xiao again as she left.

"Tsk, what a huge grudge she has."

Han Xiao pursed his lips. He naturally would not be so petty with this balding baby.

This trip had been a great harvest for him. He not only learned a lot of secrets of the universe but also greatly expanded his knowledge. For him, returning to his universe felt like he had come to another world. But in the eyes of his officers, it was only a few months that he had disappeared. Except for a few, no one was curious about where he had gone.

Han Xiao reconnected to Phillip, encrypting all the data he recorded on this trip.

This technological treasure was too rich, such that even a pinnacle Beyond Grade A like him would take around a decade to finish studying it. While Awakening Points and Experience could speed up the research progress, it would be a waste to use them that way. After all, before the next Version arrived, it would be difficult for him to supplement those. Since it was not long until the Version 4.0 update, he could take his time to slowly digest it then.

He summoned a housekeeping robot to spray some air freshener in the room to remove the remnants of Sylvia's elegant perfume before sitting back in his chair to handle the backlog while logging onto the forums to check on the players.

After a few months, the fourth Pro League had entered the International League phase, and they were at the Quarter Finals. China had two teams qualifying this time, Dynasty with the most stable performance and Rivervale.

After three league matches, Rivervale was no longer a dark horse but rather a stable and powerful team.

The previous International League group stage that had just ended was the most dangerous one, with the crazy targeting of the Chinese clubs still ongoing. As a result, there was one less team that had qualified for Quarter Finals this time.

However, looking at it from another angle, even with the clubs of various countries trying to push them down, there were still two Chinese teams that had made it in. The results were gratifying.

Now the hope of the country fell on Dynasty and Rivervale. So long as either of them won the championship, it would mean three consecutive victories for China. None of the other countries in the top eight wanted to see such a result, but they were unable to encircle and suppress the Chinese players as much as in the group stage.

"Now that it has reached the Quarter Finals, it's not far from the end of the Pro League. There are at most two months left before Version 4.0 ends… I have to prepare."

Chapter 1207: Finals and Reorganization

In his past life, Version 5.0 represented the Calamity of the Supers. The Beyond Grade As of history revealing themselves, conflicts intensifying between the Supers and the ordinary citizens, the emergence of the Grade A players, and the unwillingness of the Super Star Cluster Civilizations in losing the war all combined to throw the universe that had just stabilized back into turmoil.

Under his own influence, there were too many variables, so he could not properly predict what the specific changes in the next version would be. The only thing Han Xiao could determine was that the importance of players would rise once more and become the focus of more factions. No matter how much reservations the factions had, they would introduce welfare measures to recruit more players.

While the army had greatly expanded its scale of players in Version 4.0, this was an opportunity and yet a trouble. Not to mention the potential confusion that the players would bring, the other factions would also attempt to poach the army's own players. As long as they were willing to fork out a sum of money, it will naturally have an effect. Han Xiao was not so arrogant and self-confident that no player would not succumb to such a measure. Moreover, the idea of being a big fish in a small pond might appeal to some players, rather than staying in the army and being a small fish in a big pond.

This was especially so for players who would reach the level of Calamity Grade. They would naturally have a huge impact on the Super employment market in the universe.

A true Calamity Grade would have the qualification to dominate an entire area on their own, so the majority of factions could not afford to employ them. However, even if the regular remuneration was reduced to a fourth or even a fifth of the usual rate, it would be enough to feed the players. While the strength of the players for their Calamity Grades would be at the bottom of the barrel, they were the cheapest Calamity Grades that some small factions would be able to afford.

The only way I can deal with the other factions is by continuing to strengthen the construction of the faction, increasing the status and attractiveness of the army during the Version update. Even with my personal influence, this will be a step-by-step process, but if I can take out some of the valuable civilian black technology, it will greatly speed up the progress. In the eyes of the public, it will seem as though I developed this…

The army's operations in the Flickering World were on the right track and had limited room for further development. To continue expansion, he could only target other Star Fields by developing branches.

The following few decades while the version updated would be a good time for him to lie low and develop. With the aid from the Association, the army did not need to participate in the war between the three Universal Civilizations and the Super Star Cluster Alliance, thus not being dragged down. They could all just sit this one out and reap the spoils later.

On the other hand, this was also conducive to the construction of the Association's community of interest. The final structure had to exist as a multi-faceted interest network, where the most powerful Beyond Grade As sold various resources and services while the weaker ones obtained support, maintaining a balanced relationship. With the size of the current Black Star Army, it was naturally qualified to become one of the facets.

Each term of office for the President was stated at fifty years. Han Xiao had already thought about it, planning to oust Manison when his term was up and sit in this position. With his current right to speak in the Association, so long as Manison did not make any underhanded moves, he was quite assured.

The moment he sat in the position of President, with his results of exploring the Sanctum, there would be no suspense when it came to future re-elections.

"The specific plan will depend on the actual situation…"

Han Xiao opened his memo, beginning to write out the prototype of the plan.

…

Because Han Xiao and Kasuyi's actions were carried out in secret, the time of their disappearance did not cause any alarm. After all, the risk of exploring the secondary dimensions was too great, so it was normal that the major organizations would not pay much attention to the duo's actions.

The news of Black Star returning quickly spread through the army, and players noticed, but the International League had already reached the quarter finals, and everyone had already run out of blank Character Summon Cards to use. It was with pity in their hearts that they refocused on the event.

Since the start of Version 4.0, China's major clubs had enjoyed the development benefits the Black Star Army provided them, making a lot of money in the process. The better their official guilds developed, the greater the support for the professional teams. At present, China's first-tier professional teams basically all belonged to the T0 and T1 tiers internationally, with outstanding strength. They had performed strongly during the quarter finals.

Because they met with such harassment, the Chinese teams were unable to obtain many points this time round. Both Dynasty and Rivervale entered the quarter finals at second and fifth place respectively. After three victories in the best of five, they both reached the semifinals, succeeding in occupying two seats. This meant that they would get at least a third place.

However, after three versions, the Chinese players had grander ambitions. No one was satisfied with just third place. In the eyes of the players, only three consecutive championships was worthy of being their goal.

The semifinals were decided through lot drawing, and this caused the Chinese players on the forum to be divided into two sides. One hoped that both Dynasty and Rivervale would not meet each other in the semifinals, and the other side hoped that they would meet.

If both Dynasty and Rivervale could defeat their opponents, that would of course be the most ideal situation. However, if both sides lost, then China would be halted at the semifinals. However, if both faced each other, this would be a sort of insurance to guarantee that one of them would definitely step into the finals.

Under the prayers of the two sides, the semifinals list appeared. The Chinese teams were not facing each other. Dynasty went against Team Thunderbolt Pythons from North America, whereas Rivervale's opponent was Team Kimchi from South Korea.

The Chinese players who supported having their teams meet in the finals got their wish, but for the players on the other side, they were all depressed, worrying about the possibility that both teams might be defeated. As the saying went, one would only know what they wanted after the matter had taken place. In the end, most players discovered that rather than having two teams meet in the final, they would rather have a shot at winning the championship.

Both teams tried their best, but Dynasty missed out on a round, being defeated two rounds to three. They failed to qualify for the finals, and the hope of replicating the scene of having two teams from the country in the finals was dashed.

Rivervale, on the other hand, performed wonderfully, qualifying with three rounds to one. There was a saying in Galaxy that every version would have a god-like respective class. The Mechanic class gradually began to exert its strength in the middle to late stages, and because of the limitation of level cap in each version, the Mechanic's feature of burning money to continuously increase strength was favored by professional teams. Rivervale's team was made up of Mechanics as the core, which explained their strength.

In the previous Pro League, Rivervale barely eked out a victory against Team Key in the semifinals, allowing China to dominate the finals. Though they failed to win the championship, they still received endless praise. This time, they really had a chance to obtain the championship, shouldering all the expectations of the Chinese players.

The date of the finals was set a few days later, and the forums were discussing this matter enthusiastically.

Outside of the players' field of vision, a new regular meeting of the Beyond Grade A Association was held.

…

A series of Beyond Grade A remote projections descended on the headquarters of the Beyond Grade A Association, walking into the round-table meeting room and sitting down, whispering to their neighbors.

Sitting in the President's seat, Manison looked at this harmonious scene, glancing at the empty Vice President's seat as he felt as though the air was fresh and the atmosphere relaxed.

At this moment, an untimely voice sounded outside the door, breaking his harmony and tranquility.

"Hehe, I'm back! Did everyone miss me?"

Hearing the familiar voice, everyone turned around to see Han Xiao, who had vanished for a few months, walking into the conference room with a smile that asked to be slapped.

"Oh, Black Star's back!"

"It's been a few months, but you look pretty good!"

"Where did you go these few months? To not even inform us."

Upon seeing Han Xiao, many people present smiled, beginning to chat and wave to him. Even the direct subordinates of the three Universal Civilizations also nodded in greeting, and the place became lively.

Han Xiao was quite comfortable in the Beyond Grade A circle, having a good relationship with most people.

He smiled in response to the crowd, walking to his seat and plonking himself down before turning to look at Manison and joking, "I heard that you've been very comfortable these few months. It's alright, I'm back now."

Manison displayed a passive expression as though he had not seen or heard him. The moment Han Xiao appeared, he had put on this poker face.

Seeing this, all the Beyond Grade As were full of spirits, their eyes jumping between both of them as they revealed expectant expressions.

A meeting without the Vice President spitting nonsense did not feel complete. The last few months' meetings had been too dull, causing everyone to feel drowsy and lethargic. With Black Star finally back, they could enjoy his repertoire again. No one allowed their minds to wander.

At this moment, Kasuyi also walked in, and after some greetings, he sat in his position. Everyone could not help but cast suspicious glances.

The duo had disappeared for several months and reappeared at the same time, which left a lot to their imagination.

Manison also looked at Kasuyi a few times before suppressing the doubts in his heart, not asking on the spot.

Surveying his surroundings, he coughed twice before saying, "Since everyone is present, let's start…"

Before he could finish, Han Xiao immediately raised his hands. "I have something to say."

Manison was interrupted in his opening speech, but he was not angry at all. He was already used to it. As long as Black Star was present, he would never have the chance to finish a sentence.

Everyone else's eyes lit up.

It's here. It's about to get nasty. Black Star is indeed our source of joy. He's so dedicated that he starts his job the moment he comes.

Han Xiao looked at everyone, seeing them anticipating what he was about to say. He then turned to Manison and spoke in a deep voice.

"Recently, I've been thinking about it, and I feel that Manison's Felon technology is not conducive to the unity of the Beyond Grade As. Having this living body transformation is going overboard, and I feel that Manison should take the initiative to abandon his technology, releasing the Felons."

Hearing this, Manison burst into flames.

This matter had long been tacitly understood by everyone.

You did not choose to talk about this a few months ago, and suddenly bring up this topic, this is obviously you causing trouble!

The request to give up his Felon technology was obviously a fantasy. Black Star knew that this topic would not produce any results, but he still chose to raise it. In Manison's eyes, this was just him deliberately picking faults in him.

"Black Star! Don't be an embarrassment! How long ago was this matter already‽" Manison hollered.

"What about it? We don't have any limitation of a prosecutive period whatsoever. If you can do it, why can't I say it?" Han Xiao waved his hands. "Ask everyone here, who has no issue with this?"

"That's right, transforming a living body is not right. While this was before the establishment of the Association, it's still okay to bring it up." Kant was happy to see that Black Star had managed to pick on something, and he immediately followed up.

Hearing this, everyone present also began to discuss the issue.

While it had already been a long time since the incident, Manison's Felon technology had always been a thorn in everyone's hearts.

Usually, everyone would tacitly not speak about it, but now that someone had dug it up, they would not mind throwing sh*t from the sidelines… The main thing was to provide firepower for Black Star. All those people wished to see the world burn.

Manison's eyelids twitched, and he boomed, "Enough! Black Star only knows how to fool around, but why are you guys also joining in?"

"This sentence is wrong. What fooling around?" Han Xiao crossed his arms, pretending to be serious. "So long as you are still doing this sort of unethical practice, we're qualified to blame you. Even if you cannot restrain your greed and do not wish to give up this technology, you still have to apologize."

"Apologize to whom? They were originally my spoils of war, and I have the right to dispose of them as I see fit. I've never heard of any reason to apologize to prisoners," Manison coldly said.

"Not apologize to them, but to us. You broke the unity of the Association, and the most important part is that you broke everyone's trust." Han Xiao spouted nonsense with a straight face.

"You're bullsh*tting…" Manison was just about to retort, but a silent voice sounded out at the side, from Kasuyi.

"Mechanic Emperor, your actions indeed are not beneficial to the unity of the Association."

The moment his voice sounded, everyone stared in shock.

The environment that was noisy and raucous turned silent.

Everyone stared at Kasuyi in unison, feeling a little surprised.

Kasuyi had always been neutral, and he did not help anybody. Besides, he had been long-time friends with Manison, but to think he would actually side with Black Star?

Manison was also left stunned.

Old Ka actually decided to help Black Star go against me. When did they get so close? Could it be that we are not friends who have played together since we were young?

The two only disappeared for a few months. What did they do together for their relationship to progress so quickly‽

He closely scrutinized Kasuyi's passive expression, feeling disbelief at this situation.

Chapter 1208: Birth of a Reign

"What is the meaning of this‽" Manison looked straight at Kasuyi, his tone unfriendly.

Kasuyi sighed, not avoiding his gaze as he softly said, "I meant it literally. I feel that Black Star is right. As the President of the Association, you are a role model. You should really give up on the Felon technology. While this may be a long time ago, before the association was created, we are now advocating unity in our realm, so the transformation of a living body is going too far and will make everyone uncomfortable."

Manison narrowed his eyes.

This seemed like a premeditated action. If Black Star and Kasuyi had hooked up in private, they would deliberately attack him today to demonstrate the strength of the opposing faction while attacking his prestige, further isolating him.

Of course, there was another possibility. Kasuyi might purely have problems with the Felon technology. Manison had known this old friend for many years. He knew that he did not like to offend anyone, so there should be reasons for him to say this face to face.

Moreover, Old Ka was not someone easily bought over. Manison did not believe that it would only take Black Star a few months to forge such a deep relationship with him.

Or it could also be possible that Black Star has something on Kasuyi… Ok, I'll ask him after this meeting.

Manison rearranged his mentality, looking away into the audience as he expressionlessly spoke.

"How I deal with my spoils is my own freedom. If everyone continues to discuss this topic, there will be no results obtained. Don't waste time, so let's have a serious meeting."

The Felons were his trump card. Everyone understood that it was impossible for him to compromise by threatening him.

But this move was undoubtedly part of Black Star's plan as he knew that Manison would not give up his Felon technology, and he wished to force him to make a stand. In this way, it could at least aggravate the dissatisfaction of most members against him, reducing his prestige as President.

Black Star's Spacetime Amber could only be regarded as placing people in prison, and it was also a safe method. However, the Felon technology was obtained by conducting human experiments on prisoners, which was much worse.

Even if Manison continued to argue his way out, the situation would just be more unfavorable toward himself. Thus, he directly put on a tough attitude, putting an end to the topic.

He put on this uncompromising attitude, and while it was not out of everyone's expectations, everyone was a little unhappy about it, like the fox that mourned for the dead rabbit.

Seeing this, Han Xiao decided not to press this topic.

Everyone had already stated their stance, so forcing his way through would not achieve any results but would only disrupt the meeting. Right now, his goal had been achieved, which was to lower the prestige of Old Man Manison. Furthermore, he managed to dig a trap for the latter. Manison was still unaware about the Sanctums, so Han Xiao was basically targeting the information gap.

Han Xiao turned to look at Kasuyi, flashing a tacit smile.

Kasuyi helplessly shook his head.

Him stabbing Manison this time was not just to help Black Star consolidate his position but also him thinking for the future. After discovering the Sanctums, his mentality and view of the Association had changed.

After thinking about it, Jayz had mentioned that the Sanctums could only revive someone who was dead, as each Beyond Grade A existence was unique. Thus, was a person transformed into a Felon dead or alive?

Most likely, they were still considered alive. In that case, if a Beyond Grade A was transformed into a Felon, as long as they were not liberated, would they never be able to be resurrected by the Sanctums‽

And here was an even more frightening thought… Was there anyone who would utilize the abilities of the Sanctum to set a trap, capturing newly revived Beyond Grade As to turn them into Felons‽

Kasuyi shuddered.

In the past, he could reluctantly accept this technology, but the concept of resurrection through the Sanctums subverted his viewpoint in life. If there were no expectations, he would not care, but now knowing that his own life could be continuously prolonged, he found it difficult to tolerate the continued existence of such a threat.

This was just considering from his own point of view. From an overall point, in the long run, the Felon technology would not be conducive to the Association's control and maintenance of the Sanctum's ability to resurrect or to the members' unity. Kasuyi was already able to guess several bad circumstances that could happen in the future. Now it seemed that Manison's path was absolutely unworkable.

It was foreseeable that, once Black Star managed to develop the ability to resurrect people from the Sanctums, the Mechanic Emperor, who had mastered the Felon technology would inevitably become the target of public criticism. Who would wish to resurrect a Beyond Grade A that knew the Felon technology? By that time, maybe even death would become a luxury for him. If most of the Beyond Grade As went to the extreme, they might work together to send him into the Spacetime Amber to prevent Manison from being resurrected by the three Universal Civilizations to squeeze out his Felon technology.

Kasuyi still had some measure of friendship toward Manison; he did not wish to see him fall into such a desperate state. It could be said that this was for the good of Manison. It was just that only he was aware of the severity. Before Black Star finished his research, the information on the Sanctums could not be disclosed to anyone.

As for whether Manison would listen or not, that was his problem. Anyways, Kasuyi felt that he had already shown his brotherhood.

Without Han Xiao fanning the flames, the meeting continued normally, but everyone present was absent-minded, their eyes constantly switching between Han Xiao and Kasuyi with different thoughts on what Han Xiao had actually offered to Kasuyi.

Sorokin was also quietly looking at the duo, feeling envious and jealous.

Kasuyi has also been roped in. Black Star's influence in the Association is getting larger…

He had always remembered the threat of Black Star having seen through his identity. To have his weakness in the hands of others, while he had always wanted to silence him, he feared the repercussions of his actions. Sorokin was reluctant to leave this shell of his.

According to Sorokin's calculations, the best solution was naturally to use other Beyond Grade As to kill off Black Star while he stayed out of the matter. However, with Black Star's social circle expanding, he had more friends than enemies, which meant there were fewer candidates for Sorokin to utilize.

There were only so many pinnacle-level Beyond Grade As in the universe. Every friend that Black Star made meant one less potential helper.

"Could it be that I'll have to be eaten to death by him like this? If I can discover other variables…"

Sorokin's eyes flashed with darkness.

A few hours passed. The regular meeting ended smoothly, and everyone left with their own thoughts.

Kasuyi disconnected the projection link. At this time, his communicator rang, and not surprisingly, it was Manison calling.

He could only sigh, picking up the call and calmly speaking.

"What have you called for?"

"Kasuyi, what's happening between you and Black Star? Does he have a bargaining chip in his hands?" Manison cut to the chase, asking about the meeting incident.

"…Nothing happened."

Manison frowned before continuing. "You went missing for a few months. Was it because you went with Black Star? What did you encounter?"

"What has it got to do with you?" Kasuyi indifferently replied.

Hearing this, Manison's expression changed.

He was admitting to it, but from his tone, it was obvious that he was not willing to reveal any intelligence related to Black Star.

It seemed like he had guessed wrongly. Kasuyi was really supporting Black Star, and their relationship had improved by leaps and bounds in the past few months, to the point he was willing to offend Manison for the sake of Black Star.

Manison felt the indifference and estrangement Kasuyi was exuding, and it made him uncomfortable.

This sort of feeling was like having a close companion being pried away by an opponent. The heartache of betrayal. He felt that his social circle was being invaded by Black Star. Everything that once belonged to him was gradually disappearing.

At this moment, Kasuyi said, "Is there anything else? If there's nothing, I'll end the call. I'm pretty busy right now."

Even if this was a private conversion, he was reluctant to engage in any conversation that could cause any leaks. He could only try to chase Manison away.

"Understood."

Manison was silent for a few seconds, suppressing his disappointment before actively disconnecting.

Kasuyi put down the communicator, his expression complex and a little sad.

During the Intelligent Plague, Manison had tried to go for wool but ended up shorn, landing himself in trouble. This caused Kasuyi to change the candidate choice from Manison to Black Star, which allowed such an opportunity to fall into Black Star's hands.

In Kasuyi's eyes, Manison had chosen short-term gains over the bigger long-term gains. If he had not proceeded so rashly, Kasuyi felt that he would still have called upon Manison to team up. In this case, Manison would also have had a copy of the intelligence in his hands, and he would not be in the dark.

A pity, there were no 'if's in reality.

"It's all fate. If I had teamed up with you, then you would be the one with the intelligence advantage now…"

Kasuyi shook his head, feeling sorry for Manison.

The undercurrent of the Beyond Grade A Association did not affect the activities of the players. A few days later, the fourth Pro League finals unfolded.

Ratings on the forums broke through all records. If Rivervale carried all the hopes of the Chinese players, then Thunderbolt Python carried the hope of all foreign clubs. Only they could prevent China from establishing a record three version winning reign.

Under the attention of the public, both sides were evenly matched in the first match. While Rivervale was stable, they were hit by the secret tactics that Thunderbolt Python had been hiding up till now. They suffered a loss, losing the first round to Thunderbolt Python, which raised the blood pressure of the Chinese players.

However, in the second and third rounds, Rivervale withstood the pressure and played steadily under the leadership of Frenzied Sword. While there were few exaggerated maneuvers, the team relied on the endurance advantage of the Mechanic class to eke out a small advantage and win both games to take the match point

In the fourth round, Thunderbolt Python tried their hardest, playing cautiously, but they were beaten by Rivervale again and again.

In the end, Rivervale won the round and the match, obtaining the championship. Ever since entering the quarter finals, Rivervale's record of their matches had mostly been a 3:1 victory. The stability of the Mechanic department was fully demonstrated by them, strong with few shortcomings.

Under the gazes of countless spectators, the last player of Thunderbolt Python fell in the ring.

The sound of the body falling resounded in the hearts of all the viewers like a drum. It was akin to a signal that announced the birth of China's reign of three consecutive victories!

Chapter 1209: Interviews and Predictions

The moment Rivervale defeated Thunderbolt Python, the Chinese players went straight into the forums to vent their inner ecstasy and excitement.

"Congratulations, Rivervale! Congratulations, China!"

"Three consecutive championships, what a lad!"

"Hahaha, continue to harass us. We'll still win!"

"Congratulations to North America for being Runner-ups! XP"

Ever since the preliminary rounds, the Chinese players had been suffocating. Their teams had constantly been targeted, but now they finally exhaled and vented their indignation.

Starting from the second Pro League, Long Sky, Dynasty, and now Rivervale had each brought a championship trophy to China. As the saying went, good things would not go beyond three generations. Three consecutive champions, in the eyes of the players, meant that their achievements were truly remarkable and glorious.

The official staff of the Rivervale club quickly posted an announcement after their team won the championship. In just three minutes, the number of replies to the post broke through a million, all of which were congratulatory notes. With their popularity, they instantly rose to the top of the 'Trending Posts' list.

The congratulatory messages were not limited to the Chinese players. They also attracted a large wave of foreign fans. Among the players all over the world, there were many spectators who had been supporting the team's achievements regardless of nationality.

While China was busy celebrating, the foreign teams were feeling uncomfortable. They had failed in their targeting, and the teams that had participated met with a lot of cynicism, loss, and helplessness.

We've exhausted all means, but we failed to stop China from obtaining the championship. What else can we do? We can only accept reality.

In his office, Han Xiao could not help but smile as he read through the forums.

"Three consecutive championships… truly a feat."

No country in his previous life had achieved such a reign. Even the most dominant North America in his previous life had only won three separate championship titles. Now, with his own influence, the Chinese team, which had struggled in his past life, had achieved a good record and become a hegemon. He also felt some pride.

As the main faction of the Chinese players, the benefits were naturally obvious. It was foreseeable that the attractiveness of his faction would increase once more, which would be extremely beneficial to his own plans. In the next version, the success rate of other factions trying to poach his members will decrease even further.

Han Xiao was naturally happy, and he suddenly recalled his original plans during the national war.

"Oh, now is the best time to send the rewards…"

Because the Golden Alliance had won the national war, Han Xiao thus decided to purchase Planet Milton, which was the main battlefield and give it to the Golden Alliance as a reward. Now was the opportune moment.

While the three Universal Civilizations were still at war with the Super Star Cluster Alliance and could not confirm the ownership of Planet Milton, it did not prevent him from releasing the news to the outside world. Just based on the status of the Black Star Army, no matter which organization obtained Planet Milton in the end, they would not prevent such a small business from happening. This way, it would be equivalent to him placing a bid on Planet Milton.

…

For the next ten days after Rivervale won the championship, the forums were still as bustling as ever.

During this period, the Galaxy Times also stepped up its production, producing a new program. The past three champion teams of Rivervale, Dynasty, and Long Sky were invited as guests, giving rise to an unprecedentedly grand occasion.

Han Xiao was also watching, his screen constantly being barraged with bullet comments. Two hosts, a man and woman, were seated on one side. The team players, headed by Frenzied Sword, King Admiral, and Hao Tian, were seated on the other. The interview had already begun.

"… Since the first Pro League, we've witnessed the rise of Rivervale step by step. The team has continued to mature, and after four versions, you've finally won the highest honor. Captain Frenzied Sword, any thoughts?" the female host asked.

Frenzied Sword carried a proud smile on his face as he said, "First of all, I would like to thank the club for investing in me. After the first Pro League, Rivervale decided to rebuild the team up from scratch, and they gave me a lot of authority. It can be said that without their support, there would not be the present me. Next, I would like to thank my teammate. Everyone put in a lot of blood, sweat, and tears to achieve the current results. Without our tacit cooperation, we would not have today's glory.

"Next, I would like to thank Dynasty, Long Sky, and the other Chinese teams. Without their efforts in the previous two leagues, we would not have been able to obtain the honor of having three consecutive championships. This is the result of the hard work of all the Chinese teams. Everyone has won glory for the country.

"Lastly, I would like to thank the Black Star Army. Though a bit strange, if I were to be honest, I feel that the Black Star Army has played an irreplaceable role in the course of our championship titles. It might even be one of the main factors."

The male host nodded. "There are indeed such sayings on the internet. Many people think that the achievements of China's three consecutive championships is inseparable from the unique faction benefits offered, which means that there is a factor of luck involved. Do you feel the same?"

Frenzied Sword spoke in agreement. "I would think so. The players who have experienced four versions like me will understand. The Black Star Army started off small in its early stages. It was us who painstakingly built it up from scratch, which has brought us long-term gains.

"Being able to join such a promising faction at the very beginning is part of our luck, and it does indeed provide a lot of convenience. There's no need to deny this… Of course, the team's contribution is also equally important. Those who wish to get work done must first sharpen their weapons. In this respect, our faction allowed us to develop well, and we used these resources to give a glorious answer sheet."

Hao Tian added, "Frenzied Sword is right. The Black Star Army does have a part in the honor of our three consecutive championships."

In Version 1.0, he was one of the 'four pillars' under Han Xiao, so he naturally agreed with Frenzied Sword.

To mention an NPC faction during a championship interview seemed a little weird, but most players in the Chinese teams would not feel that way. After four versions, the Black Star Army had given them a strong sense of belonging, making them feel like they were part of a larger family.

Seeing that the topic had reached this point, the female host turned over her card as she said, "Speaking about the Black Star Army, just a few days ago, Black Star himself publicly stated that he would buy the Planet Milton and give it to the subsidiary Golden Alliance as their base. This has aroused a lot of conversation. What do you think of this?"

Hearing this, everyone turned to look at Maple Moon. She was, after all, the recognized plot digger among the professional players, and everyone felt that her answer would be more reliable.

Maple Moon thought for a bit before answering. "I feel that, although the behavior of our Army Commander was a little sudden, it's not at all surprising if you think carefully about it. You have to remember that during the national war, there were quite a few NPC spaceships from the various organizations watching us on Planet Milton. With our existence in the universe, it is impossible for Black Star not to pay attention to our national war.

"While the NPCs do not know what we're doing, they can also make basic judgments. From the perspective of the Army Commander… I think that while he might not understand why we are fighting, in his eyes, it is likely to be a conflict between us Immortals. He didn't want to manage this, but because the Golden Alliance is under his command, and there were also teams that were subsidiaries of the Super Star Cluster Alliance, there was an environment of faction conflict.

"Therefore, when he saw his affiliated organizations defeating all the other enemies, he might have been pleased. Then when he saw us staying in the battlefield of Planet Milton and establishing a player Main City, he might have thought that we were reluctant to leave this place, so he generously decided to purchase it to reward his subordinates."

After Maple Moon's analysis, many of the viewers suddenly realized that the cause and effect were quite clear, and the screen immediately flooded with a barrage of comments.

"Indeed, a professional player good at digging out plots. This idea is actually pretty clear. I can understand it immediately."

"What do we need to analyze anyways? All we need to do is scream 'Army Commander, you're impressive, awesome'!"

"Even when fighting a national war, our faction still gives us benefits. Only the Black Star Army have such good treatment, right? This is too good!"

The national war was a player's spontaneous activity, so there was originally no reward. However, because of Black Star's generosity, they now had something to celebrate.

Moreover, even if the guild alliances of the other factions won the national war, they probably would not get such benefits. Only the players of the Black Star Army would have such treatment. Was this not too fortunate?

The eyes of the guilds in the other factions were all green with envy.

Seeing this, Han Xiao laughed in satisfaction. He liked this sort of player with an excellent brain who gave his army a sense of existence.

The two hosts asked many questions, giving the players of the three teams much free room to talk. The interview ended in a happy atmosphere before entering the last link of the program, reviewing the course of this version and predicting the next version's start point.

The male host slowly said, "Version 4.0, we've witnessed many historical events, such as the establishment of the Beyond Grade A Association, Black Star's Godlike Battle, the Intelligent Plague outbreak, Black Star being awarded the Galaxy Medal and being hired as a special consultant by the three Universal Civilizations. There were also conflicts between the three Universal Civilizations and the Super Star Cluster Alliance, the Black Star Cup, and the participation of the Flickering World war… There were so many achievements…"

Many of the viewers were wrapped up in their memories, recalling the rich experiences from the past few years.

The hostess then added, "We've experienced a lot in Version 4.0. The opening of the World Server has given this version a special meaning, but the universe is still under turmoil. It's difficult to predict what will happen in Version 5.0, so we can only make an educated guess based on existing intelligence.

"Right now, it's the early stages of the Flickering World War. We don't know how many years will pass between Version 4.0 and 5.0. In our opinion, the next version will likely be at the end of the war, letting us participate in the final decisive battle. It will likely be a time skip of more than ten years…"

Hearing the hypothesis of the Galaxy Times, Han Xiao shook his head. "They're wrong this time."

From the viewpoint of the players, the Flickering World War was akin to the Crimson Tide. They thought it would be a multi-version timeline, but they did not think that the Main Storyline of Version 5.0 would be the Calamity of the Supers. In the past, players were also involved in the conflict in such a confused manner.

But it was no wonder they would think this way. The players were currently not at a high level, so there was no way to obtain too many clues. There were also sudden factors involved in the Calamity of the Supers, which basically no one could predict.

Now that there was a butterfly effect at play, the trend for Version 5.0 would be even more confusing. Even Han Xiao himself could not accurately predict what would happen, let alone the players.

While thinking about it, Han Xiao flicked his finger across the edge of the desk, and the blue virtual screen popped out.

He glanced at the date on the upper right corner before exhaling.

"Only twenty-seven days left before the game will undergo an update. Version 4.0 is ending…"

Chapter 1210: Oathkeeper Returns

Nearly a month later, it was the day when the version would be updated. There was a sea of people in Black Star Palace's lobby. Countless players gathered there, chatting in twos and threes as they waited to go offline.

Bun-Hit-Dog wandered through the crowd, turning on his recording function as he enthusiastically took pictures of the scene in the hall as an assistant followed him.

In Version 4.0, Bun-Hit-Dog's business had made significant progress, becoming an important co-reporter of the club, so he founded a studio. He no longer single-handedly edited videos, instead recruiting some employees to be responsible for all aspects of affairs. The most important task was to help him collect material.

These employees all have their own work accounts. Their IDs were prefixed with the studio's name. This assistant beside him had the ID of 'Bun-Hit-Dog: Little Wheat'. At first glance, he looked like a happy little fat man.

"Boss, why are we shooting in the base? Can this even be used as material?" Little Wheat was curious.

"Are you stupid? Who knows what the army will become in the next version? If there are changes in the future, all of this would become historical data. It's completely possible to produce a nostalgic video!" Bun-Hit-Dog instructed.

"Boss, you really have foresight!" Little Wheat gave a thumbs up.

"Humph, your business opportunity level needs to be improved. Take a good look and study hard." Bun-Hit-Dog grunted.

Not far from the two of them, a group of professional players formed a circle, having a discussion.

"I'm going to retire," King Admiral said, which immediately drew everyone's surprise.

Frenzied Sword had always treated King Admiral as his idol, and he replied in disbelief, "We've just won three consecutive championships. Why are you retiring?"

"That's right. Right now, China is at its peak," someone added.

"Haha, it's precisely because we've won three consecutive championships that I can retire with peace of mind. I originally had this idea after getting champion the last version, but I stayed on because I wanted to achieve it again with Dynasty." He thoughtfully waved his hand. "I'm not young anymore, and I can feel my performance beginning to decline. Now is the right time for me to retire. My application for retirement has also been handed over to the club's superiors, and they respect my choice. In the future, it will be Second Prince who leads as the captain of Dynasty. I have to give others a chance."

Hearing this, everyone turned to Second Prince.

Second Prince had always wished to suppress King Admiral and steal his position of Captain. However, now that his wish was coming true, he surprisingly did not reveal any happiness. He was silent and depressed.

King Admiral glanced at him before smiling. "Didn't you always want the Captain's seat? Now you've got it, why are you not happy?"

Second Prince moved the corners of his mouth, showing a wretched smile. "Nonsense, I'm obviously very happy. I finally chased you away, haha."

Everyone present shook their head. They could tell that Second Prince was being insincere. He was obviously sad and disappointed, but he was still stubborn to the very end.

Ever since entering the team, Second Prince had been competing with King Admiral on the field. While he liked to trash talk, he had always treated King Admiral as his best buddy in his heart. He had a competitive nature and hoped to surpass King Admiral, not to obtain the Captain's position in this manner.

Upon thinking that he would never be able to fight with King Admiral side by side in the future, Second Prince felt an empty spot in his heart.

"Relax. Although I'm retiring, I'll still be working in the club. I'll likely take on the position of coach." King Admiral patted Second Prince's shoulder as he smiled. "As such… this means that I'm still above you. You don't need to miss me."

While he did not say it directly, the implied meaning was there.

A younger brother will always be one. You want to step over me? Dream on!

Second Prince changed his face faster than an opera face-changer did as he barked out, "Who's missing you? Hurry and resign and get lost. You irritate me!"

Everyone immediately withdrew their gazes, unable to bear this 'tsundere' moment.

"Speaking of retiring, I also have similar thoughts." Long Sky's Sleepy Winter sighed. "I should be the oldest player here, and I have almost reached my limits. Now is the best time to retire, since we've already achieved something big. I feel that it's time to allow the newcomers to step up. Isn't Rivervale doing well as a newcomer superstar?"

"We're only so-so. That's right. Since we won this time, it's our turn to treat everyone." Frenzied Sword scratched his head in embarrassment.

The group of professional players were there to discuss their respective careers. Li Ge was secretly happy, wishing that all of his competitors would retire. He seemed to foresee the rise of his Temple of God.

Time passed slowly, but it did not take long to finally arrive at the time for the Version update. White lights flashed as the players went offline one after another. The hall of the base suddenly became desolate.

…

Version 4.0 update initiated.

Saving data… Saving completed!

Player forums closed.

Update Duration: Unknown. Please wait patiently.

In his personal machinery factory, Han Xiao withdrew his gaze from the surveillance of the main hall of the base, calling up the interface to take a look.

"The players have gone offline."

Han Xiao sighed, quickly adjusting his mentality.

This time, it would take much longer for his farm to harvest, so he had to properly fertilize his land beforehand.

The fourth Pro League had brought him another wave of experience at the end of this version, but his reserves were still quite lacking. His current experience upgrade cost was too huge, such that it was crippling even with the massive amount of experience the Celestial Star Alliance storyline had given him.

In this version update, Han Xiao decided to first focus on the God's Trait Transformation—Machinery, raising it to the max before moving onto his Void Branch.

The God's Trait Transformation had changed on the tenth layer, adding prerequisite missions. The Mission Completion Card was tested to be effective, so Han Xiao planned to do more missions with random rewards during the Version update to obtain more Mission Completion Cards. This could save him a lot of God's Trait Transformation points.

The main source of God's Trait Transformation points was in creating Gold Grade equipment from blueprints. There were many Gold grade blueprints in the inheritance left by Jayz, which was a large source of points for himself. Han Xiao decided to first study that technological information.

With this technical inheritance, there was no longer a need to go to the three Universal Civilizations to acquire blueprints, and there was no need to perform missions for Contribution Points. This saved a lot of time and energy, also allowing the three Universal Civilizations to misjudge his technical background, thinking that he did not have many Gold-grade blueprints. This was killing many birds with a stone.

"In the next few decades, there'll be another batch of new Beyond Grade As. I wonder how many of those under me will be promoted…"

Han Xiao stroked his chin.

In his eyes, the officers who had a chance of promotion would be Aurora, Feidin, Hadavy, Jotina, Lothaire, and Lagi.

Among them, Aurora had no bottleneck to speak of. It was just that her normal development was slow. However, with the Holy Light Seed as a leek field, it would greatly accelerate her development process. For Feidin and Lothaire, they were just that talented, with the possibility of a breakthrough. As for Hadavy, Jotina, and Lagi, they all had deep accumulations, which granted them a chance to grow further.

Evans' training career was still too short, and a few decades would not be enough for him to grow. The 'New EsGod Cultivation Program' would take some time.

As for Karlot, he belonged to the late bloomer type, and this timing was far from the peak of his previous life. However, because of Han Xiao's own influence, his maturity might have some changes.

"It's still more reliable to focus on cultivating Aurora, allowing her to reach Beyond Grade A so that the spirit of Germinal will resurface in us…"

Han Xiao sneered in his mind.

…

Within a certain base of the Holy Accord, a secret hall had been redesigned as a huge laboratory. In the center of the room was a circular mechanical base with a diameter of about fifty meters. It was covered in complex patterns, energy transmission pipes, and magic circuits. At first glance, it looked like some sort of ceremonial venue.

In its surroundings, many members of the Holy Accord Organization wearing white lab coats were intensively debugging the various instruments. Law and Fay were present to supervise.

"How much longer till the agreed period?"

"There are three minutes left to enter the preset time range. The receiving device has been warmed up and can be activated at any time."

"The Information Form stabilizer has also been set up. All procedures are ready."

Looking at the time, Law had a solemn expression, his palms full of sweat.

It was the day of appointment confirmed by Destiny's Child. According to the information passed down by the organization, the flow of spacetime within the Sanctums was special, only briefly coinciding with the main universe at random points. If the time node was missed, it would take a long time. The layout of the current venue was just to allow Oathkeeper to return, and everyone present was testing this out for the first time, not knowing how effective it would be.

Everyone's spirits were taut as the time ticked by every minute. It finally arrived at the determined time node.

"Begin!" Law immediately shouted.

The next moment, all the instruments were activated in sequence. The circular mechanical base in the center of the room came to life, and the energy loops on its surface lit up in sequence from bottom to top.

Ohm!

A loud noise sounded in the room, as the space above the pedestal produced a distortion visible to the naked eye.

This continued on for more than ten seconds before a gate of light appeared in the sky, spitting out a figure before disappearing in the blink of an eye.

Everyone hurriedly looked up, their faces overjoyed. On the ground was Oathkeeper, who had been missing for many days.

Law and Fay rushed up to help Oathkeeper, only to see him in a daze, as though he had just woken up.

"Leader, you're finally back. How do you feel?"

Oathkeeper looked at the two with a dazed expression, only remembering his identity after a while. His eyes gradually focused, and he slowly recovered, covering his forehead as he mumbled, "It feels like I've had a long dream. There's a strong sense of illusion within the Sanctums, just like being in a dream. I've discovered many amazing secrets, but only a small part of the fragmented information remains in my memory. Let me sort it out…"

He clutched his forehead as he struggled to recall what he had seen in the Sanctums. He vaguely remembered the shock that permeated his soul, but the relevant memory had faded quickly, leaving only fragments in his mind.

After a long period of time, Oathkeeper gradually restored the information he obtained, and a look of horror flashed across his face.

Fay noticed the shocked emotions on Oathkeeper's face and asked, "Have you recalled something?"

"… No, I cannot."

Oathkeeper took a deep breath, suppressing his turbulent emotions.

The Great Reboot, Universe Iterations, the function of the Sanctums… all of this information flashed through his brain. All of this knowledge subverted his worldview, and he intended to keep it a secret, not prepared to share any of the information he discovered in the Sanctums.

Throughout the universe, I should be the only one who has obtained this information at the moment. Its value is immeasurable, akin to the advantage of prophecy. The future course has to be drastically altered…

This thought flashed past his mind.

At this moment, Law surveyed the surroundings, and not seeing anyone else, he asked, "Leader, did our plan succeed? Have you resurrected them?"

Hearing this, Oathkeeper seemed to recall something. Turning his hand, he discovered a peculiar golden imprint on the back of his hand. In his remaining memories, this was a one-time use Sanctum imprint, which would allow him to resuscitate the historical Beyond Grade As using the Sanctum as a medium.

"It should have succeeded…" Oathkeeper paused, surveying his surroundings before raising his tone. "Empty the venue immediately and follow me to welcome the return of the Primordial Ones!"

Chapter 1211: Revived Primordial Ones

Because of certain considerations, Oathkeeper did not choose to activate the Sanctum Resurrection Brand in his base but moved to a certain unmanned planet in the desolate universe belt, bringing along a group with him.

Several Holy Accord spaceships were suspended in the planet's orbit. Law and Fay were heading a group of technicians to manipulate various detection instruments. The monitor was aimed at the surface of the planet, showing Oathkeeper standing in the center of the picture.

Amid the sandy yellow desert, Oathkeeper glanced at the Sanctum Resurrection Brand on the back of his hand as he took out a palm-sized, disc-shaped device with the other.

The fragmented memories in his mind showed that this brand was more like fuel. In order to activate its function, he needed to prepare a switch, a device capable of converting Information Forms. If there was no technology in the area, then this brand would only be ornamental.

This disc in his hand was part of the Holy Accord's Esper Ability technology. Researchers had developed an information state disturbance device through analysis and research on Destiny's Child. This was not black technology but rather a by-product that was accidentally made. It was just a coincidence that it could act as a switch for the Sanctum resurrection.

Oathkeeper pressed the button, and the disc began to buzz. The next moment, as though hot oil was being poured on cold water, a fierce reaction took place.

The Sanctum brand suddenly shone, separating from the back of Oathkeeper's hand before turning into a dazzling ball of white light, quickly expanding to cover a large area in front of Oathkeeper.

The surrounding energy fluctuations spiked, and Oathkeeper subconsciously took two steps back. At this time, the technician in the spaceship exclaimed in the communication channel.

"The reading of the information state disturbance has broken through all historical records! Oh my god, it's still skyrocketing!"

"An abnormal phenomenon has been detected, being matched to relevant records in the database… Suspected to be an [Information Form Projection] or [Reality Distortion]!"

"Warning! Time and space coefficients in this area are rapidly declining in stability. There is a cosmic energy surge, but there seems to be some kind of force to constrain the fluctuations here without spreading!"

Oathkeeper was vigilantly staring at the light cluster in front of him, his body tense and prepared for a quick response.

After a period of time, the light clusters transformed from the Sanctum Resurrection brand split and turned into luminous individuals with different shapes. At the same time, the light slowly faded, and the individuals turned from virtual to real, forming many different biological entities.

Seeing this, the noisy communication channel suddenly ground to a halt.

Including Oathkeeper, every member of the Holy Accord held their breath, their eyes filled with incredible and ecstatic looks.

Those people were exactly the characters that were recorded in their minds.

Each of them was actually one of the Primordial Ones, with known names and identities!

"Success!"

Law and Fay were overjoyed, while the technicians embraced and cheered each other.

Many of them were the descendants of the Primordial Ones, so seeing that their ancestors had been revived, how could they not be happy?

At this moment, these Revivors recovered their wits, surveying their surroundings.

"Where are we?"

"Why am I here? Shouldn't I be at war?"

"Eh, aren't you already dead? I was the one who even scattered your ashes. Don't tell me you faked your death…"

After clearly seeing the people around them, some of whom were even opponents who had faced each other on the battlefield, many of the Primordial Ones rushed to distance themselves, vigilant and confused.

The Beyond Grade As that were resurrected in the Sanctum only retained the memories of their past, at the final moments of their deaths. To them, it was as though they had woken up after a sleep, and they hardly felt the passing of time.

At this time, Oathkeeper walked over, immediately attracting the attention of everyone. Many of the Primordial Ones were shocked, only now realizing that there was one more person at the scene.

They all watched as Oathkeeper slowly lowered his hood, revealing his face as he spoke in a tone full of complex emotions.

"I have accomplished the original Oath. Congratulations on your rebirth."

After seeing his appearance clearly, the many Primordial Ones were stunned. They all recognized Oathkeeper.

"It's actually you!"

"Our original idea actually came true‽"

"We have been resurrected?"

Everyone was stunned. Shock, ecstasy, and disbelief covered their faces.

The objects to be resurrected by the Sanctum required a corresponding medium. Thus, the people chosen in the first batch by Oathkeeper were all the original founders of the Holy Accord, which were only a portion of the Primordial Ones.

These people served different civilizations during the exploration era, thus engaging in endless killing because of their factions. However, they formed secret associations in private, striving for a common goal.

But as the exploration era war continued, the Primordial Ones died one after another, reducing the number of members in the Holy Accord. The Holy Accord Organization at the end of the exploration era thus became almost an organization in name, left without hope, but never did anyone think that their originally envisaged road would finally come true!

"What did you do‽"

Everyone was curious, coming up to ask.

"During that time…" Oathkeeper slowly let out a breath, recounting his experiences in the years after.

At the time when only he remained in the Holy Accord Organization after the exploration era, he took a low-key approach, no longer participating in any events, only devoting himself to the development of the organization, gradually restoring the dying Holy Accord. The vitality had grown to the scale it is today, and they had always regarded the original Oath taken as the purpose of the organization.

While Oathkeeper casually spoke, everyone could understand the difficulty involved. This operation had gone against the currents and saved them all.

This spirit of living up to one's words really deserved to be praised.

For a while, most of the people in the field were moved, patting Oathkeeper on the shoulder again and again with gratitude.

"Good work. Thank you."

"It was nothing. I was just abiding by the original Oath." Oathkeeper waved his hands, donning his hood once again.

"How did you revive us though? Is it really the effect of the Sanctums?"

"Not really. Luck took up a majority of it, and this method may also only work once…" Oathkeeper narrowed his eyes and spoke, not revealing the true mechanism of the Sanctums.

Everyone had some doubts about this statement, but their level of suspicion was not high. After all, they were still impressed by Oathkeeper.

The most important thing was that there was no way they could identify it, as only Oathkeeper had been to the Sanctums, so no one could not refute this.

After a while, the emotions of most of the Primordial Ones had calmed down. Various questions rose up in their minds.

"What year is it now? What happened to the exploration era war?" someone asked.

Oathkeeper sighed.

"The exploration era war has long ended. The Federation of Light, the Crimson Dynasty, and Arcane Church are now the hegemons of the universe. You've lost touch with the times and need to catch up on information."

Hearing this, everyone nodded, feeling an itch in their hearts, as though they could not wait to understand the modern universe.

At this moment, a tall figure who had always been standing quietly by the side suddenly spoke.

"Does my civilization still exist?"

Everyone turned over and their expressions changed. They recognized this person, the [King of War] Pangon Filet, a well-known war addict.

Following this question, everyone became aware of some thorny problems. Their original excitement turned stale as the atmosphere became more tense.

Their primary goal was to revive themselves in the future, but everyone's goal of resurrection was not the same. Some just wished to escape the war, while some wanted to achieve their ambitions. Others wished to live forever.

There were some people whose civilizations were destroyed in the exploration era. Would they want revenge? Some people belonged to the current advanced civilizations in the universe today. Would you then return? These were all issues left over from history.

When the common goal of resurrection was achieved, people would then lose the basis of their unity, destined to part ways.

After understanding this, everyone's position slowly changed, shifting into various factions as they guarded against each other.

Oathkeeper was not surprised at all. He had long anticipated this and did not try to force it. He just replied indifferently.

"As for the situation of the various civilizations, you can check the information for yourselves when the time comes. Anyway, I only brought all of you back to life to keep my Oath. I don't care what you do, and I will not retaliate either, so long as you don't betray the Accord… It's just that you all still lack understanding of the current era. I recommend that you stay with me for now and learn about the situation."

"Will do." Pangon nodded.

Seeing this, no one voiced any disagreement. No matter what their relationship would become, at least, everyone right now was a founder of the Holy Accord, with many descendants in the organization.

Furthermore, they had just resurrected and were no doubt weak. It seemed like their strength had declined, so they restrained themselves at this moment, unwilling to cause trouble.

One of the Primordial Ones addressed Oathkeeper. "What about you? Since you've revived us, what do you intend to do in the future?"

"The Holy Accord is the result of my efforts. I'll continue to develop it. If there's anyone that is willing to stay and help, that would be good, but I will not force you… Right now, our advantage lies in the fact that we're hidden. None of the Universal Civilizations have any data on us. As long as we don't reveal ourselves, it's easy to live in freedom, without the control of any faction," Oathkeeper calmly replied.

"Other than us, there's no one that knows of our resurrection?" Another asked.

Oathkeeper was about to reply when a figure flashed past in his mind.

His expression changed, and he hesitated a while before answering dully. "No, there's someone who knows."

Everyone was shocked.

"Who is it‽"

Oathkeeper helplessly answered, "His nickname is Black Star, a Beyond Grade A. He's only been around for a few decades, but his power and influence are top notch in this era. I'm not sure where he heard of my goals. Maybe the organization has a traitor."

"It's a newcomer."

Most of the Primordial Ones had never heard of Han Xiao's name and did not pay too much attention. As the first batch of characters to be promoted to Beyond Grade A, they were naturally arrogant.

Oathkeeper explained, "However, Black Star has no malicious thoughts, and I even made a few deals with him. He could be considered our ally at the moment, and he has also provided help for us to complete the resurrection."

"So, I guess we owe him one. It seems like this little kid's pretty good." Everyone nodded.

While they had never met, this younger generation named Black Star was technically their savior, so they had some positive feelings for him.

"… Thus, I plan to explain the resurrection to Black Star and seek his help. Right now, among the Beyond Grade A, there are few people who have the same influence as him. Since he's friendly toward us, the resources in his hands can also provide a lot of help to us."

Oathkeeper explained as he schemed in his heart.

He had already concealed the mechanism behind the Sanctums, and now he had a new idea, which was to use this method to recover more Beyond Grade As, thoroughly mastering this channel. He could see the significance of this to the Beyond Grade As.

He could use the cooperation with Black Star on the premise of occupying the advantage of intelligence. While it was put as cooperation, in Oathkeeper's eyes, he was just using Black Star's resources. After all, Black Star did not understand the importance of the Sanctums. Therefore, he could fool the other party into thinking it was a one-off thing.

Before entering the Sanctums himself, Black Star would always be hidden from the truth.

Oathkeeper estimated that this method could fool Black Star for a long time. The Holy Accord had prepared for many years before entering the Sanctum, so in his opinion, even if Black Star was powerful, it was not a place that one could casually enter.

He had agreed to tell Black Star about the news of the Sanctums, but that was limited to the information his organization had previously, not about his own experience in the Sanctums. Oathkeeper did not intend to violate the transaction, but he did not mind telling Black Star half-truths either.

He did not have any negativity toward Han Xiao, but he had always been on the passive side due to the 'traitor'. He did not know how much intelligence Han Xiao had obtained, which made him depressed.

Right now, he finally got some exclusive information of inestimable value, so naturally, he chose to conceal it.

The resurrection plan has succeeded. It's time to talk to Black Star. I have to hold him so he would divulge the news…

A light flashed through Oathkeeper's eyes.

Chapter 1212: Oathkeeper: I'm Stunned!

The mission [Return to the Historic Stage] has been completed!

You have received 1 Legendary Point.

Legendary Point: [The Awakener of the Primordial Ones]—Because of the activities organized by the Holy Accord, a group of Primordial Ones have been resurrected from death. You secretly helped with this, and you are one of the leaders behind the return of the Primordial Ones. Your behavior is likely to have a profound impact on the entire universe.

+25 Beiger Kellarmir Favorability

+25 Tripp Sunstrider Favorability

+25 Pangon Filet Favorability

In his personal machinery factory, Han Xiao, who was buried in research, suddenly received a huge information dump from his interface, causing his expression to light up.

"The mission has been completed. Does it mean that Oathkeeper has succeeded?"

At this time, it was only a few hours after the players had gone offline. Han Xiao did not expect to obtain such good news right off the bat.

Oathkeeper had finally shown a response after losing contact in the Sanctums.

The mission reward for [Return to the Historic Stage] included one Legendary Point and twenty-five points of Favorability for all the resurrected Beyond Grade As.

Looking through the list, Han Xiao discovered the names of all these people were astonishing, easily identifiable through the internet.

"People such as [King of War] Pangon, [Mage God] Beiger, [All-Knowing One] Tripp… all of them are famous Primordial Ones."

As the first batch of people to achieve Beyond Grade A, the characteristic was that their nicknames were relatively fierce compared to his generation, who had been deprived of many of the good nicknames.

Han Xiao discovered another advantage to having this mission reward statement, which meant that he immediately knew who was resurrected.

A portion of them were exactly those that had appeared during the Calamity of the Supers, which meant that the Holy Accord had played a part at that time.

Han Xiao counted the names and suddenly scratched his head as he mumbled, "The numbers don't seem to tally…"

He remembered that the past number of resurrected Beyond Grade As was far higher than the current number.

At present, the notifications he received about Favorability were all from Primordial Ones. In the previous World Tree War Version, the Holy Accord not only brought over resurrected Primordial Ones but also others from history.

What was the reason for the fewer number of people resurrected…

Han Xiao suddenly had a thought.

Jayz had revealed the mechanism of the Sanctum Revivals last time. With this important information, he finally understood why the trajectory behind the movements of the Holy Accord in his previous life.

The Holy Accord had revived a group of Primordial Ones before Version 5.0, but some of them should have had differences, so they parted ways and ran out to induce the Calamity of the Supers. However, they did not reveal the secret of the Holy Accord. The remaining Primordial Ones continued to linger inside the organization, under Oathkeeper's leadership. It was likely that Oathkeeper discovered the secret behind the Sanctums, so he wished to grasp the lifeline of the Beyond Grade As and developed in secret.

During this period, the Holy Accord must have obtained news results, allowing them to revive more Beyond Grade As and used some method to persuade the rest to join in this plan, so the total number of resurrected this time was not the same as his previous life.

The Holy Accord thus developed silently like this until the World Tree version. It was only because they would be affected if the Universal Civilizations were destroyed that they exposed themselves and took part in the war, which shocked the explored universe.

"Oh, then it makes sense…"

In this manner, the nature of the Holy Accord in his previous life was similar to that of the Beyond Grade A Association today, with similar goals in preparing for the futures of the Beyond Grade As.

"I estimate that this should be the storyline in my previous life…"

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

While it was just a guess, it felt that he was not far from the truth.

Oathkeeper already knew of the true mechanism behind the Sanctum Revivals, so he and Kasuyi were no longer the only insiders. The plan he had set might have to undergo some changes, reaching a deeper level of cooperation with the Holy Accord.

Among them, the attitude of Oathkeeper was important. Han Xiao had limited knowledge of him and thus did not know how he operated.

Right at this moment, Han Xiao's vision was filled with black flames, and it condensed into a familiar figure.

Speak of the devil, I was still wondering when he would come knocking, but I didn't expect him to be so quick… Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

Very quickly, Oathkeeper's mental projection took shape, nodding at Han Xiao.

"We meet again, Black Star. I've returned from the Sanctum."

"It seems like you are planning to fulfill our deal today." Han Xiao's eyes flashed, and he deliberately pretended, "Has the Sanctum Revival succeeded?"

Right now, he did not know how much intelligence Oathkeeper had gotten, so he did not wish to show off immediately. He planned to probe Oathkeeper with his words to see the knowledge of the other party.

"It has succeeded and was pretty smooth." Oathkeeper nodded.

"Oh, I didn't expect this idea to actually work. How many were revived?" Han Xiao put on an interested expression.

"Dozens," Oathkeeper replied in a clipped tone. It was obvious he did not wish to reveal this intelligence to Han Xiao.

"Oh, the number is decent." Han Xiao was naturally aware of the figures, so he did not feel curious when Oathkeeper did not want to mention it. He then changed the subject. "What's it like in the Sanctum?"

Oathkeeper pondered for a while before replying in an uncertain tone.

"It seems like being in a dream, with foggy consciousness. I felt like I experienced many things, but it seemed at the same time only a moment had passed. The only clear impression I had was that I was within a boundless world with countless light clusters floating in my range of sight. Most of them would avoid me, as if there is some repulsive force in my body, but I can see different images within each light cluster…"

Hearing this, Han Xiao stroked his chin in deep thought.

Based on what Jayz mentioned, the light clusters could very well be Information Form entities that contained different contents. A light cluster could represent a civilization or a Beyond Grade A or even a period of history. Nothing was set in stone.

"Is there danger inside?"

"I doubt so…" Oathkeeper hesitated.

Han Xiao remained silent for a few more seconds before smiling. "Let's talk about the resurrection method for the Beyond Grade As of the Sanctum first. We agreed in the beginning that you would reveal all related information the moment the plan is completed. You won't go back on your words, right?"

"Of course not, our understanding of the Sanctums is like this…"

Oathkeeper inwardly exclaimed that his chance was finally here.

Based on his plan, he recounted the relevant information previously accumulated by the Holy Accord, but he did not correct his erroneous guesses and concealed the reproducibility of the Sanctum Revival, deliberately describing it as a one-off method.

His explanation was also very simple, deliberately distorting the concept that the resurrection was due to a projection of the Information Form, instead describing it as a 'cutting out' of the target information from the Sanctums, thus making it disappear. This categorized the Sanctum Revival as a one-time function.

Oathkeeper did not even disclose the source and purpose behind the Sanctums, leaving out information on the Universe Iteration and the Great Reboot, intending to make Han Xiao mistakenly believe that the Sanctums could only perform resurrections.

Oathkeeper babbled a lot of nonsense, which was totally different from what Jayz said. Han Xiao felt that something was wrong when he heard only half of it.

Their versions were totally different, so one of them had to be wrong. According to the situation of the Celestial Star Alliance and Jayz motives, the latter was more credible than Oathkeeper.

Thus, did Oathkeeper make a mistake himself, or was he lying?

Considering the behavior of the Holy Accord in his previous life, he was likely a scammer!

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes, giving off a playful vibe.

He did not immediately refute but waited till Oathkeeper had finished speaking before he sighed and changed the conversation. "I'm curious, you just said that the existence of the Sanctum was related to the Information Form and that recovery is done through it. Does that mean that the Sanctums have recorded all Beyond Grade A information?"

"It should be the case…" Oathkeeper cautiously answered.

"Then I'm really confused. Why would the Sanctums store Beyond Grade A information?"

"Oh, I'm confused about that too." Oathkeeper tried his best to control his tone.

Han Xiao pretended to think and frowned. "I feel that the Sanctum does not appear to be a natural phenomenon but likely a product of someone or some civilization. Its role should not remain at just resurrection Beyond Grade As… What do you think?"

"I don't know about this either. This shouldn't be made by a civilization. The three Universal Civilizations should not have such capabilities, and it would be even weirder if it was in the civilizations before. It should be some sort of Space Wonder…" Oathkeeper had no choice but to follow the conversation, secretly only inducing but not refuting directly lest he revealed flaws.

Hearing this, Han Xiao stroked his chin, pretending to seriously analyze the issue. He slowly said, "Let's assume the Sanctum is a Space Wonder in the Information Form, with the function of recording the information of the Beyond Grade As… Then, when those Beyond Grade As are resurrected, will the information be refreshed? If that's the case, while you might have clipped out the original record in the Sanctum, a new and updated copy would be placed within the Sanctums, so you still can clip off another copy when you next enter, right?"

"This…"

Oathkeeper was struck dumb. This analysis was justifiable, not allowing him to be able to explain.

If he objected, there was no basis since he had only been to the Sanctums once. This Black Star was truly a cunning fox and would immediately suspect him.

But if he did not object, he would make Black Star feel as though the Sanctum Revivals could be repeated indefinitely, which would run counter to his own intentions.

This annoying man was too difficult to fool!

After thinking about it for a while, Oathkeeper could not come out with a rebuttal, so he could only reply in the depressed tone. "I did not think that far."

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes and spoke in a teasing tone. "So, you were lying to me just now. It seems like I need to re-evaluate our agreement."

"Cough, cough, I really did not think of this possibility. How could I be lying to you?" Oathkeeper hurriedly defended himself.

"Hehe." Han Xiao let out two mirthless laughs, putting his hands behind his back and walking around Oathkeeper before saying, "If I'm correct, those resurrected Primordial Ones have experienced a drop in strength and have also lost a few of their abilities, right?"

"That's right, they… wait! How did you know‽"

Oathkeeper widened his eyes.

Only a few of these Beyond Grade As had discussed this in private, and those Primordial Ones would not have had contact with Black Star. In just dozens of minutes, how did Black Star learn about this?

"I know more than you think." Han Xiao leisurely strolled as he continued. "I'm not sure if you have heard the terms 'The Great Reboot' and 'Iteration'?"

Oathkeeper paled in horror, taking back two steps abruptly as he stared at Han Xiao in disbelief.

"How do you know of such things‽"

His entire being was dumbfounded, his mentality torn to shreds. He lost control of his ability for a moment, and the remote projection fluctuated violently as if he was about to disintegrate at any time.

Oathkeeper was once again mind blown!

Only he had entered the Sanctum this time, so there was no possibility of a traitor. How did Black Star know of all this?

Who betrayed me, or who did I betray?

Could it be that Black Star has placed eyes on me, allowing him to observe everything that I do‽

In that case… did I really betray myself‽

In his shock, Oathkeeper lost his wits and shuddered. Han Xiao's image in his mind became even more mysterious and unpredictable, making him extremely awed.

How much did this fellow actually know? He even helped to analyze my bullsh*t just now. Turns out, he was just laughing at me!

As he admired Oathkeeper's distraught look, Han Xiao dealt the finishing blow.

"I paid out in good faith, and I hoped that you would treat me honestly, but it seems like you don't really treasure my friendship at all."

He was actually unsure how much information Oathkeeper had, but he felt that everyone who entered the Sanctum would obtain the basic concept of the Iterations. This was just Han Xiao scamming him, but it had a miraculous effect in scaring the guy out of his mind and soul.

This is good. In this manner, the initiative is firmly held in my hands.

Han Xiao maintained his posture of being almighty, looking down at Oathkeeper.

"Why, you think I don't know what you're thinking? You intend to monopolize all the exclusive intelligence, so as to fleece me into giving you resources to aid your growth, right?"

Oathkeeper was shaken.

All his schemes were seen through by Black Star. At this moment, he felt as though he was naked in front of him, his secrets laid bare.

He had guessed the possibility of failing to scam Black Star, but he had never expected that Black Star would break him in this manner, directly smashing out all his hidden secrets and shattering all his lies.

At this moment, Oathkeeper stood there in a daze, only thinking of finding a hole and burying himself within.

Chapter 1213: Intention to Cooperate

"How did you…"

Oathkeeper was filled with question marks, finding it difficult to control the stormy waves of emotions.

He had not even gotten familiar with all the top-secret intelligence, and he had already heard it from a second person. It was just as though he had chatted with a random girl on a dating site last night, and his girlfriend called him the next hour to lash out at him.

Without any warning, his privacy was intruded, and this feeling gave him goosebumps.

Han Xiao held out his palm, interrupting his words. "I said before, I have my own sources. You only need to remember two things. First, I have far more intelligence than you. Second, our goals are roughly the same. As for the details… you don't need to ask so much."

Oathkeeper shut his mouth, his brain whirring as he tried to guess Han Xiao's intelligence source.

Under the sudden mental impact, he had temporarily lost his senses. He had almost thought that the problem lay with himself, but after recovering his senses, his reasoning told him that this possibility was slim, and it was likely because of other reasons.

The Great Reboot and Iterations were top-secret information, only known to those who had been in contact with the Sanctums. The only more plausible reason he could come up with was that Black Star had interacted with the Sanctum under certain circumstances and thus had learned of this intelligence by chance.

Beyond Grade A Supers had a very low probability of coming into contact with the information generated by the Sanctums, thus obtaining random revelations. The earliest information about the Sanctums in the Holy Accord was obtained in this manner as well, which was the basis for the establishment of said organization.

But when Oathkeeper thought of the previous exchanges he had with Han Xiao, he felt that things might not be that simple. Black Star must have had some means that outsiders were not aware of.

He could not think of an explanation that could convince himself, so he felt that Han Xiao was veiled in mystery.

At this moment, Han Xiao put his hands behind his back, putting on a profound image. "Your little thoughts can't be hidden from me. I don't like others trying to fool me, and I hope this is the last time, otherwise… Since we've all laid our cards down, I think we can be more honest with each other."

Oathkeeper could only reluctantly push down his inner turmoil and carefully ask, "How do you plan to go about it?"

"Firstly, I hope that you will tell me the actual intelligence. This is the basis for our mutual trust." Han Xiao raised his eyebrows.

Hearing this, Oathkeeper struggled for a few seconds before speaking truthfully on the intelligence without tampering.

He knew that he had already lost the initiative. Black Star had likely acquired the most important secret, so it did not matter if he revealed it. He did not dare play tricks anymore.

Han Xiao patiently listened and smiled. "You know how to admit your wrongs. Not bad."

This time, Oathkeeper's recount was the same as Jayz, obediently telling him the true mechanism of the Sanctum.

Having finished speaking, Oathkeeper paused for a while before saying, "I've told you all that I know. Now that you know the true situation of the Sanctum Revival, you should also know what this means for the Beyond Grade As. You will not try to monopolize it, right?"

Han Xiao did not directly answer but changed the topic to ask, "Do you think that the Sanctum will be monopolized by anyone?"

"What do you mean?" Oathkeeper could not understand Han Xiao's sudden question.

Han Xiao took two steps as he slowly explained, "Let's put it this way. The existence of the Sanctum is independent and should not be controlled by anyone, just like a public library… Since we can borrow the functions of the Sanctum as such, others will definitely be able to. Have you ever thought about what will happen when the advanced civilizations like the three Universal Civilizations master a stable method of Sanctum Revival?"

Oathkeeper thought about it before speaking uncertainly. "They will continuously resurrect their direct lines, maintaining the scale of their high-level combat power and using this as a bargaining chip to recruit allies."

"That's right, and in the long run, this is inevitable. What will happen is that once the advanced civilizations master the method to enter the Sanctum, they will begin a period of rapid development, widening the gap between the strength of a civilization and the free Beyond Grade As. By that time, the Beyond Grade As will come to a forked path in their destinies."

Han Xiao looked at the pondering Oathkeeper.

"Imagine, if there was no Beyond Grade A Association, no Holy Accord, no stable Beyond Grade A group that can stably perform Sanctum Revivals. The Beyond Grade As will be forced to sell themselves to a civilization. Those who choose to be free will not be revived by the civilizations, while those who are disobedient will be eradicated. In this manner, there will only be the obedient Beyond Grade As left in the universe, quietly being dogs for the advanced civilizations. They will forever be trapped in faction disputes, having to kill each other with no choice…"

He explained the situation of the Celestial Star Alliance in a hypothetical manner. The more Oathkeeper listened, the more frightened he became, realizing that the situation Han Xiao spoke of could likely happen.

"That's right. This possibility has to be guarded against. I did not expect you to see that far. You indeed have foresight!"

Oathkeeper let out a gasp of amazement.

That's not the case. You thought I was predicting, but I'm actually spoiling it for you!

Han Xiao secretly grinned, but he revealed a solemn expression on the surface as he heavily spoke again. "In order to prevent such a future, we have to let the Beyond Grade A Association master the method of stably reviving all the Beyond Grade As, so I said we have a common goal. This is for the entire class; every Beyond Grade A is a beneficiary, and no one can monopolize this."

His words went straight to Oathkeeper's heart, which coincided with his thoughts. A burst of heroism rose from his heart as he recognized Han Xiao as someone similar to him.

"So, you're proposing to cooperate in this manner?" Oathkeeper's eyes lit up.

Han Xiao nodded.

"We'll do it this way. You are in control of the Holy Accord, while I'm in control… well, about to control the Beyond Grade A Association. We'll unite a part of the Beyond Grade As together and produce different resources. As long as we become strategic partners, we can work together to complete this important task sooner, allowing the Beyond Grade As to completely unite to rewrite their fate."

Oathkeeper helplessly shook his head. "Actually, I have no choice. You're the second insider, so we can only cooperate… but who is going to control the channel, the Holy Accord or the Beyond Grade A Association?"

Hearing this, Han Xiao laughed.

"Naturally, both of us will control the channel. The Beyond Grade A Association will be the main force on the surface, striving for the recognition of the advanced civilizations, while the Holy Accord will take in those Beyond Grade As who wish to stay hidden as secret insurance. After all, the advanced civilizations will not easily accept the fact that the Beyond Grade As can constantly revive themselves. They are likely to do something to the Association, so it's best to hide a portion of Beyond Grade A strength under the surface and prevent them from seeing our full strength."

If possible, Han Xiao would have wished to have the Association monopolize the Sanctum Revival, but now that Oathkeeper was an insider, he could only form a partnership with him instead of doing things separately. There was not much conflict of interest, and their goals aligned.

Furthermore, it was not a bad thing to allow the Holy Accord to stay hidden. Both sides could form a mode of complementary and mutual assistance. Beyond Grade A could go to the Holy Accord if they wished to stay hidden, whereas if they wanted a place in the universe, they could proceed to the Beyond Grade A Association. They could switch at will, just like staying at the office or going out to the field.

Oathkeeper nodded in acceptance.

Seeing this, Han Xiao made his tone a little more serious. "We'd better finish this business before the advanced civilizations come in contact with the Sanctums. Do not reveal the truth of the Sanctum Revival to anyone. Only the two of us should know."

Kasuyi was also in the know, but Han Xiao would naturally not reveal this detail, or else it would reveal too much about his process. He would rather leave the mysterious impression of himself on Oathkeeper.

"Oh, I naturally will not reveal anything." Oathkeeper knew of the importance behind this matter and solemnly nodded.

The two of them discussed specific cooperation projects for a while, reaching a united direction.

Oathkeeper also divulged his method of entering the Sanctums, claiming that the method used for all six Sanctums were different. The Holy Accord only knew of the method to enter the Third Sanctum, which consumed Primal Esper Ability Entities as keys to enter and would need to recollect them from scratch.

As for the ideation behind the method, Oathkeeper said that it was a vague revelation obtained by some of the Beyond Grade A members during the exploration era, while the rest was derived from Destiny's Child. He mentioned how Destiny's Child was special and might reveal the keys behind each Sanctum. However, the possibility was very low and completely random.

Han Xiao was more interested in the First Sanctum, but at present, entering the Third Sanctum would be the faster route. The Holy Accord had prior experience, and with its resources, it would greatly shorten the time needed for Han Xiao to gather the keys again.

However, if one wished to resurrect more Beyond Grade As, then they would need to collect related information, and the descendants of the Beyond Grade As were the easiest targets.

"That's right. Since we've decided to cooperate, I hope to meet with the revived Primordial Ones."

"Why do you need to see them?" Oathkeeper subconsciously replied. He still did not completely trust Han Xiao.

Han Xiao smiled. "I remember you told me that you cannot force the revived Primordial Ones. There should be many of them who wish to occupy a place in the universe and re-develop their own organization. In this case, the Beyond Grade A Association is the best backer for them. I hope to get in touch with them and convince them to support me after joining the association."

The first batch of Primordial Ones definitely had their own goals. Being previous Beyond Grade As who could call on the winds and rains, forcing them to remain anonymous was basically impossible. Some of them would do things in the universe like what happened in his previous life, shocking the galactic society and becoming the fuse of the Calamity of the Supers.

With the Beyond Grade A Association now, Han Xiao felt that he could absorb some of them to strengthen his own faction.

With the association intervening, the situation of the Calamity of the Supers could also be greatly changed… Han Xiao thought.

Hearing this, Oathkeeper thought for a while before he eventually nodded.

"I'll arrange for you to meet with them as soon as possible. However, you have to be mentally prepared. They died early and have not experienced the generations of changes in the Beyond Grade A realm. They are not as low key as I am and might be a little… arrogant."

"It's alright." Han Xiao's lips curled. "I specialize in treating such negativity."

Chapter 1214: Times Have Changed

After sending away Oathkeeper, who was still dazed, Han Xiao relaxed and let out a sigh.

"Huff, acting is pretty tiring, but I've managed to pin him down."

The Holy Accord was a powerful force, completely hidden in the dark during his past life. However, he had now established a stable relationship with it, indirectly holding a secret power in his own hands. Furthermore, he would also know the whereabouts of the Revivors, which was an important move in this game to complete the key layout.

In this manner, he could interfere in the Calamity of the Supers event to become a chess player, rather than passively waiting for the situation to occur like in his past life.

This was only the general layout. There were still other more specific issues, such as the impact of the Primordial Ones revealing their identity, the shockwave it would cause upon entering the Beyond Grade A Association, and so on. Since he would be the President, such details had to be dealt with.

"It seems like I have more things to do during the Version update. Visiting and helping all these old people integrate into the present times gives me the impression of a neighborhood committee member…"

Han Xiao shook his head and chuckled.

Based on what Oathkeeper said, the Primordial Ones were taken from the warring era, and their blood and fire had yet to dissipate. They were basically a rebellious generation. Now that they had been put into an era that did not belong to them, most of their mentalities had yet to be adjusted.

If he wanted these people to accept and support him, it was not enough to just use his mouth. They had to be convinced. It was best for them to accept severe beatings of the society, allowing them to recognize their reality and understand the meaning of 'the new will constantly replace the old'.

However, the other party was still a future partner, so it was not good to be too violent. It was better for him to first be courteous, only giving them 'education' if they failed to behave.

In this regard, Han Xiao was quite confident. The Primordial Ones were the first generation of Beyond Grade As, and while he could not rule out the fact that there might be super geniuses who had reached the peak of Beyond Grade A, that number would not be huge. The average strength of the Primordial Ones was likely to be the same as the modern Beyond Grade As, and this was because of the long fighting that they did. Otherwise, their strengths might not even match up to the Beyond Grade As of today.

However, he did not have a complete advantage as well. There was a problem that could not be avoided, namely because he was still second place in the Association. Old Man Manison was holding onto his position tightly, which could mean that some of the Primordial Ones would end up supporting Manison.

However, the problem was not too big. Anyone with a discerning eye could see that he himself was thriving potential stock, whereas Manison was old stock that was bleeding internally. The choice was simple.

"As for the specifics, it's best to talk about it only after contacting the Primordial Ones. I'll wait for Oathkeeper to arrange it. Before that, I'll study their characteristics…"

As the saying went, 'know thyself and your enemy, and you'll win all your battles'. Han Xiao took out the Revivor name list, and based on the information on the internet and his memory, he began to construct a data model for these Primordial Ones.

…

In the spaceship of the Holy Accord, Oathkeeper dismissed the remote projection. As soon as he opened his eyes, he saw the Primordial Ones looking at him.

"How was it? What did Black Star say?"

Everyone was concerned about the attitude of the other insider.

"I've already communicated with him and reached an intention to cooperate. He mentioned that he will not disclose any secrets. Furthermore, he commands the Beyond Grade A Association and has expressed his hope to get your support. You can check the information about the Association through the internet. Finally, he has proposed a request to see all of you," Oathkeeper recounted.

"He wishes to see us?"

Everyone looked at each other, and many of them showed off weird smiles.

"That's good as well. We would like to see what sort of intentions he has for helping to resurrect us."

There was no love without reasoning in this world, so no one believed Oathkeeper's description of Black Star, thinking that Black Star wished for more than just an increase in the number of Beyond Grade As. There should be some ambition and scheme involved in his plan.

In their eyes, Black Star likely wished to use them. While they had positive feelings toward him for his kindness, they did not intend to be used by him.

Everyone had on relaxed expressions as they talked about it.

"Black Star knows of our resurrection. Do you think he wishes to use this as a threat to force us into doing something for him?"

"Hehe, if he really thinks of it this way, he'll soon find that his thoughts are wrong. Want to use us? Laughable!"

"He might have asked to meet because he wishes to foster a good relationship with us. It's just as well. We can take this opportunity to pull him down a peg, dispelling his thoughts about trying to use us."

"There's also that Beyond Grade A Association. He seeks our support on that matter. In my opinion, we can totally set up another organization. There's no need to listen to the orders of another. Even if we wish to join it, we don't need to support Black Star or any others. Why don't we just aim for the top by ourselves?"

"I checked up Black Star's deed on the internet, and it's actually pretty ridiculous. He broke the record for the fastest promotion to the Beyond Grade A realm, and he has even repelled the attacks of more than a dozen Beyond Grade As."

"Oh? To think that the Beyond Grade A strength of this era has regressed so much, that more than a dozen people failed to kill a newcomer who has only been promoted for a few decades. Tsk tsk… it seems like each generation is inferior to the last."

"Don't look down on them. If it wasn't for his capabilities, he would not dare to have designs on us."

By the side, Oathkeeper quietly listened to their idle chatter, with no intention of correcting their misguided notions.

It was too common for the Primordial Ones to look down on newcomers, especially since they were the 'founders' of the Beyond Grade A realm. Their statuses were lofty, with the mentality that the descendants today were able to achieve what they had because of them, the trailblazers.

But from his viewpoint, this bunch of fools would need a lesson in order to quickly adjust their mentality.

This is also for all of your own goods…

Oathkeeper shook his head as he secretly sighed.

…

After half a month, on a certain barren planet in the Ancient Star Desert, six figures stood on the ground, Oathkeeper and five other Primordial Ones. Because they did not wish for Black Star to know the total number of people resurrected, they selected five people as representatives who had the best combat power.

The other Revivors did not show up but stayed in a fleet that was two days' distance away, remotely monitoring the area.

"He should be here soon. Let's listen to what he has to say first. Don't just scare him the moment he comes," Beiger said.

"Just follow the previously discussed plan. No matter how the discussion goes, let him see our strength and dispel any unnecessary thoughts," Pangon lightly replied.

By the side, Oathkeeper closed his eyes and rested his mind, as though he did not hear anything.

Before long, a comet flashed through the dark outer space and fell quickly. It was Han Xiao, who was using his fleshly body to cross the starry sky.

"I'm not late, right?"

Han Xiao landed in front of everyone, having an inkling of the situation as he glanced at the six people present.

Oathkeeper took the initiative to introduce them. "No, you're not. The five here are the representatives elected by the rest. Let me introduce them to you…"

But Han Xiao however cut him off, taking out his fluent ass-kissing techniques as he smiled. "Everyone here is a Primordial One, with a reputation that resounds like thunder. How could I not know all of them?"

His words were comfortable to the ears of those present. As the saying went, one would not hit a smiling face. While they had discussed showcasing whose fists were stronger today, since Black Star was their savior and even boasted good manners, the five also followed suit and greeted him, showing their friendly intentions.

While Han Xiao was speaking, he was secretly calculating.

[King of War] Pangon, [Mage God] Beiger, [Purple Emperor] Lady Lust… these five were all experts in this batch of Primordial Ones, with different attitudes in his previous life. They were deliberately elected as representatives likely because they suited with the different goals among the Primordial Ones. Pangon represents the Avengers, Meiji represents the Liberals, and Beiger represents the Careerists who pursue power… It seems like the issue of differences among the Revivors has become prominent…

After everyone exchanged greetings, Pangon then spoke. "You actually came with your main body?"

"It's our first meeting. I had to show my sincerity. It would be too disrespectful to arrive in my avatar." Han Xiao smiled.

"I admire your guts. Not bad at all." Pangon's tone was indifferent.

Oathkeeper coughed a little to catch their attention. "Let's first get to business. Black Star is now our partner, and he has requested this meeting, expressing his intentions to provide resources to help you quickly integrate into this current era."

Hearing this, Han Xiao smiled and nodded. "Everyone has just been revived, and your thinking has stopped during the exploration era. I estimate that you might not be adapted to the current era, so I would like to help you. However, I would like to know the goals you have after being resurrected, so as to facilitate the arrangement."

"Let me be clear. If the goals for some of us are not within your line of interests, then what are you going to do?" Beiger asked with interest.

"It will depend on the situation, but you can be rest assured that the possibility of engaging in armed conflict is not high. The Beyond Grade A Association that I belong to specializes in resolving such problems. I will not prevent you from pursuing your own goals, unless this goal will harm everyone," Han Xiao replied.

"Really?" Pangon coldly said. "The Federation of Light destroyed my homeland, so I'm going to avenge them. What do you think of this goal?"

"Avenging your own civilization is a justified matter, but the premise is that you do not bring us a negative influence, or else the association will not sit idle… However, I would like to say something. I don't recommend you performing such suicidal goals." Han Xiao waved his hands.

"I just want to remain free forever, without being restricted. The Beyond Grade A Association you speak of seems to also have a lot of rules." Lady Lust raised her brows.

"The rules in place are mainly just to protect the interests of everyone. Fundamentally speaking, the Association is just a neutral group. Everything can be settled through negotiation. As long as you do not deviate from the interests of the group, you can enjoy the greatest degree of freedom. No one will force you to do something, and with the change in the universe, the Beyond Grade As grouping together is an inevitable trend. Only by seeking shelter can you obtain freedom," Han Xiao answered as he sized up Lady Lust.

This Beyond Grade A had an exquisite appearance, with gorgeous makeup, purple lipstick painted on, and purple eyeshadow. Her hair was bunched up high, and she gave off an awe-inspiring aura. Among the women Han Xiao saw, her temperament resembled Urranrell the most, a 'superwoman' who would not take no for an answer.

The group constantly asked questions that they were concerned about, with Han Xiao answering them one after another, explaining how the Association could help them with it, but no positive response was received. The five did not agree with this proposal at this time, and in contrast, they were more inclined to create their own group.

During the discussion, Han Xiao could feel that the five of them were scrutinizing him, as though they wished to see through his tricks.

Suddenly, Pangon interrupted the questioning as he said, "I've always been curious. What is the motive behind you helping us?"

Hearing this, everyone immediately focused their gazes on Han Xiao.

Han Xiao remained impassive. "I've already told Oathkeeper. The Beyond Grade A realm requires more manpower. Only then can we obtain our own independence."

Pangon shook his head. "This is not enough to persuade me. You are holding onto the intelligence of our resurrection and information on the Holy Accord. Was it never your intention to threaten us?"

"There's no need. We're mutually benefitting in this." Han Xiao took out the signature fake smile that Sorokin used to give.

"I really hope that is the case. I'll advise you to dispel any unrealistic thoughts as soon as possible, or you will regret it," Pangon warned.

"You're overthinking it." Han Xiao laughed in return.

At this time, Beiger also spoke. "We've heard from Oathkeeper that you wish to obtain our support. Let us make things clear first. While we're thankful to you for resurrecting us, personally, I will only respect the strong."

"Oh, can I understand that as you inviting me for a spar?" Han Xiao's brows furrowed.

"If you wish for me to support you, it's best to show some skills to convince me. If you don't mind, I really wish to try how capable you are." Beiger narrowed his eyes.

Han Xiao swept a glance at the rest. "Do all of you think the same?"

"Beyond Grade As ultimately speak with their fists," Pangon coldly replied.

The rest also nodded, staring at Han Xiao with a playful look on their faces.

After being in contact, they discovered that Han Xiao was courteous and talkative, without the air of an expert. It was inevitable that they would doubt and underestimate his combat power. They could not help but embrace the attitude of testing him out.

"I have no issues, but who is going to spar with me?" Han Xiao smiled.

"You can pick any one among us five. It doesn't matter to us. Since you also helped us, we won't go too heavy on you."

Beiger sounded casual, but he was actually very confident in all of their strengths.

Hearing this, Han Xiao turned his head to see Oathkeeper rubbing his nose in embarrassment and immediately understood.

He shook his head with a smile, and facing their gazes slowly spoke out. However, the content of his words froze everyone's expressions.

"That's not too good. No matter who I choose, it will only make people think that I'm picking on a soft persimmon, which will offend them… How about all of you come at me together? This will save me from the rumors that I only bully the elderly."

The silence became palpable.

The five did not expect that Black Star, who had been so flexible and friendly, would suddenly make such arrogant remarks. Their eyes widened and showed emotions such as disbelief, uncertainty, and anger.

"Are you looking down on me?" Pangon's expression sank, and a dangerous light shone in his eyes.

"No, no, you're mistaken. I'm not targeting you."

Han Xiao kept his smile, glancing around, before slowly stating.

"I'm saying that all of you here are all weaklings!"

Stop trying to pretend to be wolves in front of me. Wake up. Your glory days have already passed. The times have changed!

Chapter 1215: Old Trick

The other Primordial Ones who were watching from a screen in the fleet were all stunned. Disbelief and unhappiness appeared on their faces.

"Did I hear that correctly? He wants to challenge all five of them at once?" Someone was very confused.

"Isn't he too arrogant? I thought he'd have more self-awareness based on the way he spoke earlier."

"Hehe, looks like he's indeed quite ambitious. He's thinking of intimidating us." Someone snickered.

"I heard he defeated a dozen Beyond Grade As at once. Did that make him overly confident?"

"Possible, he might think we're on the same level as the modern Beyond Grade As… Hehe, does he really think he's strong just because he bullied some kids who grew in the peaceful era? He's probably never seen what true strength is."

"His tone is so arrogant. Pangon and the others are definitely insulted. A show is about to begin." Someone gloated. "Wait and see, they'll teach this guy a lesson, especially Pangon… He's got a bad temper."

"Hope he can still be this cocky later," someone said with a mocking tone.

All of them were waiting to see the show.

What Han Xiao said was targeted at all the Primordial Ones, including them, so they were insulted too. Although they did not look like they were, they were more than glad to see Han Xiao get embarrassed.

…

On the other hand, the six of them including Oathkeeper heard what Han Xiao said and their expressions changed.

You said we're outdated, that we're not letting go of our old honors? That's hurtful!

"Arrogant!" Flames of rage appeared in Pangon's eyes. He was furious.

When had they ever been looked down like this ever since the era they dominated the universe?

This was the first time anyone had dared to talk to them like this!

Even Oathkeeper felt somewhat awkward.

Feeling the intense atmosphere, he was secretly worried for Han Xiao.

Oathkeeper hoped that Black Star could teach his buddies a lesson, but Black Star wanting to fight all five of them at once was beyond his expectations. He was shocked and was worried Black Star might lose.

Black Star is too confident. Is he going to win?

Oathkeeper was a little regretful. He felt Black Star only made this proposal because he did not know the strength of these Primordial Ones well.

In his eyes, although Black Star was strong, he was not that strong. Despite having caught up with the recent news, his image of Han Xiao was still the same as before he entered the Sanctum.

I would've given Black Star some hints beforehand if I knew this was going to happen. These five guys are not just ordinary Beyond Grade As…

This time, Beiger narrowed his eyes and confirmed it. "Are you sure you want to fight all five of us at once?"

"What, you guys aren't willing to?" Han Xiao's eyes scanned past everyone's faces and saw each of their expressions clearly.

"There's no need to." Lady Lust frowned calmly. "If the five of us fight you together, it won't prove anything even if we win. Are you just afraid that fighting us one on one will damage your reputation? I can promise that our spar will be reasonable. We just want to test what you're capable of. No matter the result, we'll consider it a tie. Are you satisfied with this?"

"You are quite thoughtful for my sake." Han Xiao smiled.

"No matter what, you've helped us. I…"

Before Lady Lust finished, Pangon interrupted her and coldly said, "Don't represent me. I'm going to fight him alone."

Hearing this, Han Xiao maintained his smile and said, "Just come at me all at once. Defeating you guys one after another is too troublesome."

The five of them were deeply insulted.

We gave you an out. Not only are you not taking it, you're even crossing the line further.

You need a damn beating!

Beiger gave Han Xiao a meaningful look. "You chose this yourself."

"Like I said, I alone am enough." Pangon turned to look at the others and looked like he would fight them first if they argued with him further.

Knowing Pangon's personality, someone said, "Consider us securing the perimeter for you on the side."

Pangon thought about it and did not argue. He stomped the ground heavily. An enormous shockwave expanded out, creating a ripple like tide on the ground.

Bang!

He shot up the sky and flew into space like he could not wait any longer.

The others were not surprised and followed behind. After all, he was a Pugilist, and Pugilists were not known for being sensible and logical. The others were used to Pangon's personality.

Han Xiao glanced at Oathkeeper, who was looking worried, and then flew up as well. At this time, a notification popped up on the interface.

You have triggered the hidden mission [Fists Speak the Loudest]!

Mission Introduction: The revived Primordial Ones appreciates your help but aren't convinced of your strength. You've decided to display your strength to earn their respects.

Mission Requirements: Earn the respect of the Primordial Ones through actions.

Reward: Depends on the results of your actions. The higher the rating, the better the reward.

Tip: This is a Series Mission. Your actions will affect the following missions. Please act with caution.

Yo, here it is. This should be in the same mission chain as [Return to the Historic Stage].

While he looked at the mission, he flew into space. The five of them were already in position. Four of them stood in different directions and drew out the battlefield area, while Pangon stayed inside opposite Han Xiao.

"Can we start now?" Pangon's tone was irritated.

"Anyti…"

Before Han Xiao even finished, Pangon had already lost his patience. Golden red flames erupted from within his body as he turned into a meteor and charged toward Han Xiao.

Usually, when Pugilists were in a friendly spar with Mechanics, they would always actively back away some distance so that the Mechanic could let out part of their army. However, Pangon had already developed the habit of using everything to his advantage as much as possible through countless large-scale galactic wars, exploiting every edge he had, even in spars.

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes, stood in place, and opened the secondary dimensional army box. However, before the first batch of mechanical troops even appeared, Pangon had already bashed onto his chest.

Boom!

As his fist landed right on Han Xiao's chest, Pangon was surprised to realize Han Xiao did not even dodge it. Hence, he quickly turned a normal attack into an ability. Thick Pugilist flames rushed into his fist and entered Han Xiao's body, turning into an erupting shockwave.

This was a control type ability, using Pugilist flames to trigger the atoms in the opponent's body to tremble. As long as his Strength was superior, he would be able to temporarily immobilize the opponent.

Pangon was very experienced in dealing with high-level Mechanics. He knew that getting this close to a Mechanic was an extremely rare opportunity, and he was not going to waste it. Tons of combos flashed past his mind. He decided on using the combo with the highest explosive damage instantly, and his body immediately moved following the muscle memories. Once Han Xiao was immobilized, he would be able to instantly deal a ton of damage.

However, just as he was about to use the combo, a slap suddenly landed on his face.

Paa!

This slap was powerful and heavy, Pangon's eyes widened, and his brain was trembling. He could almost hear the sound of the bones on his face cracking.

Before he recovered from being stunned for an instant, a thunderstorm of melee attacks suddenly arrived. Countless heavy attacks landed on his body every second, shattering the gold and red flames on his body part by part, continuously creating ripples and dents on his muscles. Pain swarmed his nerves like a tsunami.

Pangon instinctively raised his hand to protect his vital spots. He was still in shock.

Wait a minute, as a Mechanic, not only did he not back away after I, a Pugilist, got this close to him, but he even actively fought back to have a hand to hand combat with me?

Never mind him fighting back, but what's with this power? It's outrageously strong!

After getting bashed by Han Xiao for a few seconds, Pangon finally found an opportunity to twist Han Xiao's arm and pull it toward him, locking Han Xiao in his place.

"Don't you think you can run!" Pangon said. Pugilist flames flowed in his body. His muscles suddenly bulged, and his strength increased in an instant.

He was prepared to stop Han Xiao's attempt to escape his body lock.

As long as he could lock Han Xiao down for just two seconds, he would be able to lash out with an even stronger ability and deal even more damage.

Each and every part of a high-level Pugilist was a weapon. Although Pangon was a little lost and stunned by Han Xiao's attack from earlier, with his countless Pugilist abilities and talents, he still had an incomparable edge in close range combat.

However, the next moment, he was shocked to realize that not only did he not feel Han Xiao trying to escape, but Han Xiao even grabbed his waist and locked him down instead.

"What fighting style is this?" Despite being very knowledgeable, Pangon was still puzzled.

"What, you want to learn? Sadly, you won't be able to even if I teach you." Han Xiao laughed.

At this time, the first batch of mechanical troops that had flown out of the secondary dimension fired at the two of them without hesitation. In their preset programs, the most prioritized tactic was to fire at their master unconditionally once their master locked a target down. Han Xiao did not even have to control them to do so anymore.

Seeing this, Pangon's expression changed drastically.

Isn't this the 'die together' tactic? F*ck, this man is even more ruthless than me!

Although his physique was tough, he did not want to take a psionic bath with the enemy!

Pangon became the one who was trying to get away, so he hastily let go of his body lock on Han Xiao and tried to step back. However, his waist was tightly held by Han Xiao's shockingly powerful arms, and he could not escape quickly enough.

"Stop wasting your energy. I'm quite surprised really. You guys knew I'd be visiting half a month ago, yet you didn't study me online properly. If you even studied my battle recordings just once, you wouldn't have been so stupid as to rush into my face like this… Are you guys really that arrogant, or did Oathkeeper cut off your internet?"

Han Xiao was almost speechless.

He really did not plan to use this tactic at all. He thought as long as the Primordial Ones searched his information online, this old trick of his would no longer work. No matter what, if they at least saw his 'Indestructible Body' nickname, they would be more or less more cautious.

However, to his surprise, Pangon rushed into his arms right at the start. Even Han Xiao did not underestimate the Primordial Ones and constructed their data models beforehand so that he would come prepared. This only proved how little these Primordial Ones thought of him.

Don't blame me then. You asked for this.

"Eat this!"

Boom!

The blinding light from the explosions of a round of focus fire psionic attacks instantly devoured the two of them.

The bombardment lasted for about three seconds. A golden-red meteor hastily fled the explosion area and rolled a long distance in the cosmic space before finally stopping himself.

Pangon's clothes were ragged. Large areas of burnt skin could be seen on his body. Some places even showed signs of carbonization.

Han Xiao flew out of the explosion area too. He sized Pangon up and sighed.

The time for the army to gather was too short, so the number of mechanical soldiers he summoned in the first batch was too few. The damage dealt was far from enough. After all kinds of shields and resistances, the damage done by that round of focus fire could only slightly injure Pangon.

Han Xiao had already seen Pangon's attributes from the combat information. Pangon's Energy Rank was about 71,000, and his attributes were about the same as when Han Xiao was level 300. Before Han Xiao's Promotion, he might have had quite a tough time dealing with Pangon, but now he could thrash him in any way he wanted.

However, he also knew that these Primordial Ones were not at their peak. Losing part of their attributes and being in the weakened state since they had just awakened were just two of the reasons. Another important reason was that their equipment did not revive with them. For example, Pangon's nickname came from the set equipment he used when he was active in the galaxy, which was exactly called 'King of War'. It was built by the civilization he was in and consisted of three Universal Treasures—the shield, spear, and the armor. Without this set of equipment, he was about thirty percent weaker.

This was even worse for Mechanics who revived. They would have lost all the machines they had and would have to build from scratch. It was tragic. After all, not everyone had as fast production speed as him and the Mechanic Emperor.

Seeing this, the four others who were securing the battlefield on the side were astounded. Their expression turned from unconcerned to serious.

"Did you see that? The strength this guy just displayed?"

"Hmm. To think a Mechanic whose physique is supposed to be weak has such high power and agility. Either his Energy Rank far exceeds Pangon, which means his foundation is much higher, or the modern Mechanics have taken a very new path of not focusing on machines but their physique instead!"

"I think the latter is quite likely…"

While the four of them chatted in the communication channel, the situation in the battlefield changed again. After losing a small round, Pangon became cautious. Before clearly understanding the situation, he did not dare rush close to Han Xiao. He did not know what to do for the time being.

Han Xiao, however, did not continue to attack. Golden Mechanical Force spread out from his body like a net catching onto all the machinery around him and pulling them toward him. Within the blinding cluster of Mechanical Force lightning bolts, the enormous Mechanical Deity appeared.

The next moment, the Mechanical Deity swung the Celestial Punishment Edge one round and unleashed an arc of silver blue psionic energy.

Swoosh!

The energy blade quickly expanded. Even the four people at the edge of the battlefield were targets in this attack. With flashes of light, magic arrays, Esper Abilities, and psychic means of defense appeared. Beiger, Lady Lust, and so on blocked this powerful energy blade attack in their own ways.

At the same time, Han Xiao's provocation sounded in the public channel. "I said I'm going to fight all five of you, and I'll do it. You guys want to watch on the side? Don't even think about it!"

Beiger and the others exchanged looks and joined the battle without hesitation.

Seeing Black Star's strength, the few of them no longer minded fighting Han Xiao together. If they really let Pangon fight him alone, Pangon would most likely lose. Furthermore, Han Xiao attacked them and forced them to fight. Not fighting back would not be suitable.

The few of them did not reject the idea of fighting one enemy together. This was the complete norm during the exploration era. The result of caring too much about these things was death. The Primordial Ones were all used to fighting one opponent together. They were not obstructed by such unnecessary morals.

"Finally. Come, let me give you guys a beating of love to help you see reality!"

Seeing this, Han Xiao grinned. Mechanical Deity swung the Celestial Punishment Edge, stirring up a tide of dark blue energy and charged toward the five of them.

Chapter 1216: Confidence Destruction Lesson

Boom!

The flashes of psionic explosions flickered in space. Mechanical soldiers charged out of the secondary dimension rapidly into the battlefield.

Five different colored clusters of energy were flooded by the sea of machinery, passing through the countless mechanical soldiers like asteroids. Flashes of light from different abilities flickered between the tiny gaps of the mechanical army from time to time.

There were four classes among the five of them, only no Mechanic. Mechanics without their inventory were tremendously weaker, so no Mechanic was chosen to be a representative by the revived Primordial Ones.

Psionic Prime led dozens of Apostle Weapons to fight. With the bonuses from Han Xiao's Mechanical Force, the highly synchronized Apostle Weapons gave them a lot of pressure.

The Mechanical Deity stood above all in the battlefield, swung its Celestial Punishment Edge around and chased after the five of them. The weapon was enormous but quick like lightning, releasing extremely powerful psionic energy blades together with Getta Hadoken combos one after another, dealing massive damage.

Pangon got special attention. Han Xiao loved bullyin… ahem, educating cocky, headstrong Pugilists.

Since the opponent this time was not Old Manison, who knew him all too well, Han Xiao had to maintain his image. Hence, he was more reserved and did not bombard them with private messages.

The five of them fought for quite some time. Despite fighting the five of them alone, Han Xiao did not show signs of defeat for the time being. In fact, not only was he not losing, he even had a slight advantage.

Pangon, Beiger, and the rest of them were far from their peak strength, but they were not completely trash. Although they were at quite a disadvantage, they could still hold on for now by working together.

However, all five of them felt distressed. This was the first time they had fought a Mechanic of this style. They did not know what they should do.

In their knowledge, the best tactic against Mechanics was simply getting close. When they first saw that Black Star came with his original body, they were quite surprised and felt Black Star was way too incautious. Only now did they realize just how wrong they were. Black Star's style was the complete opposite of the impression they had of Mechanics—one was as fragile as a piece of paper, while even the supposedly psychological weakness of the other was extremely tough. He was basically indestructible!

The strategy of rushing toward him was basically useless. But if they targeted his army, his inventory was way too huge. Soldiers were still swarming out of the secondary dimensional army box every second. God knew when it would end.

It seemed like the only strategy they could use was to deplete his energy by stalling the battle. However, the destructive power of the Apostle Weapons, mechanical army, and the Mechanical Deity was too strong together. There was hardly any room for them to make any mistakes. Plus, their energy was also getting consumed at a quick rate.

If this carried on, the five of them were uncertain if they would be heavily injured and unable to fight first or Black Star's energy would dry up first.

"Does this guy even have a weakness?" Beiger was appalled.

"It's shocking to see such a horrifying man in this era!" Lady Lust marveled.

"If only my weapons were still…" Pangon clenched his teeth as dozens of his bones were shattered by an energy blade once again.

"Save it. You got beat up by a Mechanic at close range as a Pugilist, have you not embarrassed yourself enough?" someone asked.

"Alright, stop quarreling and think of how to fight him. If we really get defeated despite fighting him as five, just image how shameful that'll be for us," Beiger said.

The five of them dodged and guarded against the mechanical army's attacks while trying to find Han Xiao's flaws. However, they were unable to find an opportunity to turn the tables. Instead, they fell into a more and more passive situation.

With the bonuses of [Fearless Heart] and [Legendary Battle Technique], the attacks of the army were extremely powerful. Among the five of them, only Pangon had True Damage Reduction. The rest could not endure many rounds of focus fire.

If not because a Psychic and Beiger were continuously refreshing their shields, someone would have already been heavily injured.

Most importantly, the few of them were absolutely shocked to realize that Han Xiao was becoming stronger as the battle carried on.

Beiger dodged the attacks of a few Apostle Weapons by using an illusion spell before saying decisively, "The battle is now going according to his tempo. Things will only get worse if this carries on. Let's try again. The five of us all attack his main body together. I don't believe his physique doesn't have limits. There's no other way for now other than this anyway."

"What do you plan to do? His body is hidden in the Mechanical Deity, protected."

"Have you forgotten about the Space Forbidden Spell I have mastered? I can pull the target out of the Mechanical Deity for a short period and create an opportunity."

The few of them quickly came to an agreement. Beiger did not delay any longer and started preparing for the spell with a hand gesture.

An exquisite enchantment array illuminated on his neck. A wave of space repelling force expanded from him, and the mechanical soldiers around were all pushed far away.

Right after, he raised his hand and used a group teleportation spell, teleporting the other four to beside him.

His spell casting did not stop. He instantly created a new magic array. Ripples suddenly appeared in cosmic space not far away. Han Xiao, who was supposed to be inside the Mechanical Deity, suddenly appeared at the location Beiger had selected out of nowhere.

Han Xiao only felt a flash before his eyes, and the location he was in changed. He instantly saw the round of focus fire the five of them had prepared that was rushing toward him.

"Yoho, cute combo."

Han Xiao still had the time to tease them. He opened a new gate of the secondary dimension beside him. He pulled it and dragged out rows of Spacetime Amber balls, which were stacked into a transparent wall in front of him.

The next moment, the tsunami of long-range attacks from the five of them crashed onto the amber barrier. Like a water pillar falling onto a leaf, the attacks instantly slipped toward all directions, leaving Han Xiao who was behind the barrier completely unharmed.

"What is that?"

Seeing this, the pupils of the five of them constricted.

At this time, Han Xiao's laughter sounded in the public channel.

"This kind of time swap spell is quite interesting. I have something similar too. Do you guys want to see it?"

As soon as he said that, Han Xiao disappeared and returned to the Mechanical Deity using Void Hyperdrive. Before the four of them could respond, he instantly used Void Swap and changed his location with a target.

Whoosh!

Pangon's sights flickered. He was petrified to realize that he had appeared inside the Mechanical Deity. Before he could react, the parts of the Mechanical Deity around him suddenly disassembled into mechanical troops. They surrounded him and fired at him instantly.

While the headstrong boy was being beat up, Han Xiao appeared beside the four others.

Looking at their shocked expressions, he smiled and activated Void Prison.

The next moment, the movements of the four of them became extremely stagnated like they were in a pool of mud. They were all inside the Void Prison, and only Han Xiao could move freely.

Then, he activated Apostilization to maximum power. The countless mechanical troops gave him tons of attributes. His right arm bent like a bow. Energy circuits lit up on his mechanical suit, and psionic energy expanded like a ripple.

"Getta Hadoken—Star Penetration Hammer!"

Han Xiao launched his fist right forward. The fist covered in blinding psionic energy landed right on Beiger's cheek. Under the slow-motion effects of the Void Prison, the shaking of Beiger's face could be seen clearly.

Boom!

A dark-blue shockwave erupted, and Beiger shot out, rolling.

Han Xiao did not stop there. His mechanical suit operated at maximum capacity as he continued to smash the other three of them like an afterimage crisscrossing between the three of them.

Kacha!

After being trounced for some time, the few of them were finally freed from the Void Prison. They hastily backed away, every part of their body hurting.

Pangon did not get captured. He barely escaped the mechanical army's encirclement. However, having faced so many attacks in such a short time, he was covered in blood and quite heavily wounded.

Han Xiao stood in place and did not chase after them, but the five of them stood far away from him with fearful and heavy expressions.

"Hiss!"

Beiger held his bleeding cheek. He was filled with shock. Not only did the tactic not work, but they even got beaten up by Han Xiao instead. Han Xiao was able to injure the five of them one after another, among whom Pangon was the most heavily injured.

This astounded the five of them. They did not know what other special abilities Han Xiao had, and they did not dare to get close to him anymore. They were afraid of falling for his abilities again.

Seeing that Han Xiao was sizing them up, the five of them focused all of their attention. The last bit of underestimation in their hearts disappeared completely. They anxiously waited for the next round of Han Xiao's attacks.

However, at this time, Han Xiao stopped the movements of all of his army. He scanned over them one by one, smiled, and said, "How about we end it here? I believe you guys already have a thorough understanding of my capabilities. If we continue the spar, it might not be a good idea. I agree with Lady Lust's suggestion. No matter the results, we'll call it a tie. There's no need to go all out."

Hearing this, the five of them were stunned for a moment. Seeing that Han Xiao did not look like he was faking it, they finally relaxed.

They exchanged looks and saw some bitterness, shame, and embarrassment on each other's faces.

The few of them knew very well that Black Star did this so they would not lose so much face, but this made them feel even more hurt.

What kind of tie is this? The five of us clearly fought one opponent but still got thrashed!

We don't feel comforted like this at all, only ashamed!

"… Someone as strong as you would have been unique even during the exploration era. We underestimated you."

Beiger sighed and had a complicated expression.

Having experienced it personally, Black Star's combat capability far exceeded their expectations and completely convinced them.

Even without that flashy combo, the few of them could see that Black Star's strength far exceeded theirs just from how powerful his mechanical army was.

Having thought of this, the few of them looked more or less disheartened. They could no longer stay proud.

The new generation surpassing the old generation did not feel good. It almost made them wonder if they really were outdated.

Pangon was the most embarrassed. The wounds on his body were still hurting like hell, but compared to the wounds in his heart, they were nothing. This hard to accept result made him doubt himself unavoidably.

Han Xiao looked at them and said with a smile, "I might have used a little more strength than I intended to. I hope you guys don't take it personally."

"Ahem, it's just a small matter. We don't mind it at all." Beiger was a little embarrassed. He still remembered that he had said something similar to Black Star not long ago.

"Can we continue to discuss what we were discussing before now?" Han Xiao shrugged.

"Yes, yes, let's head back down and continue."

The attitude of the few of them changed completely. Their tone now included respect and admiration.

Although they were not used to this change mentally, Beyond Grade As respected the strong; strength was the foundation of their position. Therefore, of course, the few of them were not going to act proud like they did before in front of someone who could crush any one of them in a duel.

Seeing this, Han Xiao smiled. When he returned to the planet surface, he instantly saw that Oathkeeper was staring at him.

"Why are you looking at me like that?"

"…Nothing."

Oathkeeper suppressed the shock inside him and tried his best to make his tone sound natural and calm.

The strength Han Xiao had just displayed shocked him too!

Unlike the other Primordial Ones, Oathkeeper knew that Han Xiao was very strong, but he did not expect him to be this strong!

Before today, Oathkeeper felt that he had a fifty percent chance of beating Black Star. However, after witnessing Black Star's fight with his own eyes, he doubted his judgement severely. Black Star was much more powerful than the rumors!

Fake news was awful!

Oathkeeper could not help but feel glad that he did not choose to kill Black Star back then, or he would have probably been the one who was killed.

…

At the same time, the remote surveillance room in the Holy Accord organization spaceship far away was completely silent.

The Primordial Ones who were watching the battle were astounded. Their eyes widened with shock, and they were at a loss for words.

After more than ten seconds of complete silence, someone finally said with disbelief, "Five against one, and they lost‽"

As soon as he said that, the rest erupted.

"Is this the strength of the modern Beyond Grade As‽"

"From the way it looks, it seems he didn't even use his full strength at all. The five of them could not even make him go all out!"

"What's his Energy Rank? Eighty thousand? Ninety thousand? Or above a hundred thousand‽"

"Maybe he was right. We're outdated. The times have really changed…"

The Primordial Ones present felt that everything they once knew was shattered. In the start, they felt Black Star was only acting strong and arrogant, but now they discovered that he was really strong. It felt like a loud slap on their faces.

Luckily, they were only watching behind the curtains and did not have to be concerned about losing face. In their eyes, it was a clear loss. They did not consider it a tie at all.

Thinking back on what Black Star said before the battle, their confidence was crushed. Their sense of superiority as the Primordial Ones got completely shattered.

Looks like he really did not overestimate himself. This is a lesson to help us see reality…

The people present had no choice but to accept reality. The arrogance, pride, sense of superiority, and other feelings they had after being revived dissipated rapidly, turning into caution, humility, and caution.

The only problem was that this lesson was way too impactful. The mindset of some of them even slipped toward the other extreme…

"Black Star is only the vice president of the Beyond Grade A Association. The net says there are quite a few Beyond Grade As who are on the same level as him, so they should be just about as strong… Tsk, the modern age is scary!"

Some of the Primordial Ones who were originally planning to have a fresh start on their own were now discouraged. They seriously doubted if they were qualified enough to start again.

Originally, the goal of reviving for some of them was to avoid the exploration era war and come to a peaceful era, rely on their own strength to form a new organization, and gain power.

However, Han Xiao's performance today gave them a misconception that people as strong as Han Xiao were everywhere nowadays.

Not only did this spar shatter their confidence, but it also made some of them so scared they buried their ambitions.

With the little strength we have, being in a hurry to mess around is probably suicide. We'd better train a few more decades and not reappear in the world before we catch up with the times. We can't humiliate ourselves like that!

Chapter 1217: Elderly Killer

Beiger, Pangon, and the others returned to the barren planet. They had fought in space earlier and consciously avoided this planet. Some of the aftershocks had also been stopped by Oathkeeper, so the planet was unharmed.

Han Xiao carried on the topic they were discussing earlier with the others. This time, the atmosphere was clearly much better. Beiger and the others were now seriously listening to his suggestions.

As the saying went, 'as long as your fists are big enough, you can make people sensible and calm.'

"… You guys are absolutely not in a state to reappear in the universe. After all, your strength has decreased after reviving, and you're now behind the era. It's best for you guys to think of ways to make up for that. In my opinion, you guys should spend more time training in isolation. Learn new technology and new knowledge," Han Xiao said.

This would not be convincing at all before the spar, but now everyone agreed with it strongly. They thought that they could only revive once, so now that they had finally been revived and had an opportunity to make up for their regrets, satisfy their ambitions, and reach new heights, they treasured it very much. They all wanted to make sure they did everything correctly.

The opportunity was extremely rare, these Primordial Ones were all very patient. They could wait.

"Black Star, you have really helped us antiques learn something new today. Not many would have been your match even in the exploration era." Beiger sighed.

They had lost a lot of face in the spar earlier, but they did not hate Han Xiao for it. At this level, no one would be that stupid.

They were not enemies. Although Han Xiao's words were harsh, they were the truth. As someone who not only saved them but was also much stronger than them, Han Xiao's words clearly carried weight.

"I've always suggested that you join the Beyond Grade A Association. Although the present is more peaceful than the exploration era, it's still shaky below the surface. Beyond Grade As are not in a safe position. You can search up the Tragedy of the Pinnacles online. That's a cleansing operation the advanced civilizations carried out against us. They've always been trying to control our numbers, so staying together is the certain trend." Han Xiao started promoting the association again.

This time, other than Pangon, who decided to take the 'revenge before life' path, the other four all started to take Han Xiao's suggestions seriously and considered taking this path.

Seeing this, Han Xiao continued. "There are more benefits to joining the association. You guys have only just revived, so you have nothing but your own strength. There's no organization or force under your command, and starting one from scratch will take a lot of time. Furthermore, the various Star Fields' territory is already split up by the various forces. Even with the strength you have, you'll still meet many obstacles… However, if you become members of the Beyond Grade A Association, you can instantly lend intelligence, resources, military forces, and so on from other members. If you want to start your own organization, we will also come together to help and provide assistance, helping you to become a part of the profit network…"

The others nodded. They were tempted.

The universe was too vast. Without manpower or money, nothing would be easy to achieve.

During the exploration era, their various civilizations provided the things they needed to them. They were used to having power. They would not be able to adapt if they had to start from zero now.

Lady Lust pondered for a while and said, "We're willing to support you, but you're only the vice president and can't be completely in charge. Furthermore, since you're this strong, the president definitely won't be much weaker…"

"Hmm, that's true. We appreciate what you did for us, but we have to think on our own behalf. Comparatively, isn't it better to support the top man in power?" Beiger asked.

Han Xiao smiled.

"Now that is something you guys don't know about. My path is different from the president's. He's very ambitious and aggressive. He wants to tie the association with him on a path with no return, which has already enraged quite a number of people. There's no chance he'll be reelected. Furthermore, he's old now. Who knows he'll just be gone one day? Hence, there's no future in supporting him. I, however, have a lot of friends and have basically already obtained the president position in the next election. Plus, there's a very high chance I'll be reelected multiple times after that. Investing in me is the best choice. I'm not just exaggerating. You guys can search it online all you like… By the way, I've defeated him too."

Although he had only beaten the Mechanic Emperor once and lost more than he had won overall, saying he had defeated him was not wrong. After all, the Mechanic Emperor was not there, so it was not like he could object it.

"I see."

Just like that, Old Manison's image was damaged once again.

The few of them discussed it for a while. Han Xiao gave many suggestions and described the current situation of the universe to them. Beiger and the others all listened carefully and learned a lot.

After Han Xiao finished talking about the intricate relationship between the three Universal Civilizations, he stopped, changed the topic, and said, "By the way, I'm very interested in the exploration era, but what I know is limited to the information on the internet. You guys are all from that era, so could you tell me more details of the situation of that era?"

He had not just gone there to set things up for the Calamity of the Supers but also to exchange information with the Primordial Ones. Seeing that the time was right, he brought up the topic.

"You've asked the right people. Who alive knows more about that era than us?"

Han Xiao had always been the one speaking while they listened. Seeing that Han Xiao had brought up a topic they were much more familiar with, they immediately became interested. They started talking about their glory days in the past all the way from the dark ages to the days of intense wars, bringing up anything that came to their minds.

Han Xiao listened, nodding and asking questions from time to time. He obtained quite a number of secrets about the exploration era war from them, as well as the information about some Primordial Ones.

"Speaking of which, do you guys know this Soul Emperor guy?"

…

"Rovell Sissock? I fought him a few times on the battlefield. That guy's quite capable, but I died earlier than him. I don't know what happened to him afterward," Lady Lust said.

"He was killed in action." Beiger shook his head. "By me."

"You killed him?" Han Xiao was immediately interested.

"Hmm, to be more details, I participated in an ambush on the Soul Emperor, along with two others. But I dealt the final blow."

Yo, now isn't this an interesting coincidence?

Han Xiao was very curious about what expression Sorokin would have when Beiger joined the association.

Hmm, given how Little Soro is, even if there's a tsunami in his mind, he'll probably still have that signature fake smile… Should I give him some stimulation by then?

Han Xiao suppressed his wicked thoughts and asked, "Are you sure he's really dead? His soul Esper Ability is rather special. Maybe he shifted his soul without anyone knowing."

"You're saying he faked his death?" Beiger was surprised for a moment. He thought for some time, shook his head, and said, "I wouldn't know about that then. Anyway, I didn't notice anything strange at that time."

"I'm just guessing. If he remained alive till now like Oathkeeper, and you see him again, will you be able to recognize him?"

"Hmm… I'm not sure. If he didn't change, my soul detection spell would recognize him. By the way, Soul Emperor is also the previous master of the Soul Flame. Oathkeeper should sense it if they met… but that also depends on if he changed his soul frequency or not. Everyone's soul frequency is unique."

Hearing this, Han Xiao rubbed his chin and pondered.

Sorokin was an expert in the soul area. He should not have left such a flaw… but that might not certainly be the case. After all, Sorokin had lived all the way till now. He would never expect to meet the Primordial Ones whom he once had contact with.

No one in the present could prove that Sorokin was the Soul Emperor, so these revived Primordial Ones became the most solid evidence…

Tsk, if Beiger recognizes Sorokin right on the spot when he joins the association, things will get very interesting.

"Black Star, I have a feeling you're trying to say something. Do you know something? Is the Soul Emperor really alive?" Beiger could not help but ask.

"Who knows?" Han Xiao shrugged. He had yet to decide whether to expose Little Soro yet. It was not the time to obtain the most benefits from doing that yet.

He paused and said, "By the way, there was a pair of sisters during the exploration era who possessed the vital and death energy respectively. What do you guys think about them?"

"Nerkese and Eros… They were very strong. They created the Underworld. Not many people dared to mess with them." Pangon finally found an opportunity to say something.

"What's the Underworld?" Han Xiao acted like he had no idea.

"That's one way of reviving too but with more cons. You'd become the vassals of the two sisters," the few of them explained.

The Oathkeeper listened for a while and said hesitantly, "Many Primordial Ones were looking for a way to revive back then. We chose the Holy Accord, while some placed their hopes in the Underworld, but…"

Lady Lust shook her head. "I'll say it. Those two sisters got lost on the path of searching for the meaning of life and death. They were very unreliable. We once invited them to join the Holy Accord, but they rejected us. Afterward, we lost contact with them and don't know what happened to them. They probably died."

Not just died, you might not believe this, but they committed suicide…

Suddenly, his body turned stiff as he realized something.

When Onicelu explained the Underworld to him back then, he did not know much about the Sanctums, but thinking about it… was the act of the two sisters leaving Information Form Esper Ability seeds behind the equivalent of snatching the information of their own Esper Abilities out from the Sanctums? Was that why these two Esper Ability seeds passed down their life knowledge?

The Great Mechanic Han was baffled. The more he thought about it, the more he felt it was not as simple as he thought.

Could the reason for the two sisters to suicide be that they found out about the Sanctum being able to revive them and wanted to attempt to revive themselves right after committing suicide to prove their theory and confirm that their path was right? Maybe they failed in the end and only left the information of their Esper Abilities behind but not themselves…

Linking this with the situation Kasuyi was in, could the impact of God's Trait Transformation missions have played a part?

Before they completely died, the word 'heritage' was mentioned among their last words… Could they have been pointing at not only their Esper Ability seeds but also The Great Reboot, the Eons of the universe‽

Thinking deeper, could Nerkese and Eros be revived through the Sanctums by using Hila, Aurora, or the Underworld as the medium? If that failed, would it mean that they were still alive in a certain way?

Han Xiao felt the more he thought about it, the more complicated it seemed.

Suppressing the shock and doubts he had, he skipped this topic and continued chatting with the others.

The few of them chatted for a while. Seeing that it was about enough, Han Xiao interrupted them and said with a smile, "Let's call it a day for today. I've already relayed my suggestions. We can be considered friends, so don't hesitate to come to me if you need anything in the future. Keep in touch."

Hearing this, everyone nodded, expressing their friendliness.

Han Xiao bade farewell one after another and then equipped the King mechanical suit before disappearing.

Beiger and the others exchanged looks after he left.

"Let's get going too. Black Star is right. I'm going to focus on training from now on. We've acquired such an amazing opportunity. Let's use it to find breakthroughs and hope to recover to our peak strength," someone said.

"Hmm… I don't plan to leave for twenty… no, forty years. I'll be staying in the Holy Accord."

Hearing their discussions, Oathkeeper smiled with comfort.

His buddies' mindsets were finally fixed by Black Star.

My efforts were not wasted…

…

Han Xiao teleported all the way back to Black Star Palace, which was multiple Star Fields away, and opened up the interface immediately. He saw the mission notification that had been flickering for quite a while right away.

[Fists Speak the Loudest] Completed!

Your actions have earned the respect of the Primordial Ones. The results were excellent. This will cause unknown affects to the future.

Grade: Unbelievable

+20 Lady Lust Favorability

+20 Tripp Favorability

…

+20 Pangon Favorability

You have received 240 Billion EXP, 8 Random Rewards, and 3 Blank Character Summon Cards.

You have received 10 Awakening Points.

You have received a [The Third Sanctum] Ability Fragment.

You have received talent [Elderly Killer].

[Elderly Killer]: When facing opponents older than you, your basic attack will increase over time up to 15%. At the same time, your CHA will increase by 40%.

"This…"

Han Xiao was speechless.

The rewards were very rich. Very rarely did missions reward Awakening Points directly, and he even got a new talent.

The effect of the talent was quite good, giving him bonus basic attack damage just like [Fearless Heart]…

But what kind of name is this‽

I beat up a group of Primordial Ones, so I became an 'Elderly Killer'‽

Also, I can understand the bonus attack damage, but what's with the increased Charm? Did they feel I looked cool fighting? Are they going to cheer for me while I beat them up? Are all elderlies masochists?

Other than these things, the triggering mechanism was quite perfect for him—among the current Beyond Grade As, no one was younger than him…

What a weird talent. Plus, it seems to go against the traditional virtue of respecting the elderly…

Han Xiao shook his head. He went through the reward one more time and closed the interface to ponder about the impact of the things he did this time.

"I beat up the Primordial Ones, getting rid of their pride. This way, they should keep a low profile for a very long time. The Calamity of the Supers will be delayed because of it… I can be less worried for some time now."

Han Xiao let out a deep breath.

He had a lot of things to do such as study the treasure trove of technology, expand the army, collect the Sanctum fragments, and many more. Time was what he lacked most. The later the Calamity of the Supers broke out, the better it would be for him. It would be best if the signs of it only showed after he became the Beyond Grade A Association president. His position would be very firm if that was the case. Furthermore, guiding the direction the Calamity of the Supers took would be easier.

Currently, the three Universal Civilizations were fighting with the Super Star Cluster Alliance. The universe was unstable, but this was the most stable time for Beyond Grade As. There were no exterior conflicts for them, so they could grow stronger while keeping a low profile. The association would also be able to build a more complete interest network… All things aside, it had only been a few years since the founding of the Beyond Grade A Association. There were way too many things that had to be done.

It's time to focus on growing for some time… Han Xiao thought.

…

At the same time, Manison and Sorokin, who were in different places, both suddenly felt chills down their spines.

"Weird, why do I feel as if something bad has happened?"

Sorokin was troubled. Dozens of speculations flashed past in his mind.

The response of Manison, however, was much more direct and immediate.

"That little b*stard Black Star is definitely plotting against me again!"

Chapter 1218: Flames of War, Gaud's Movements

Time is cruel. No matter how the world changes, it never turns back and takes the world forward.

The galactic society in the years of war was filled with endless unrest, changing the lives of quadrillions. Some threw themselves into the tides of the era, some were forcefully dragged into the vortices, and some were firm on living a meaningless life till death.

Protests, revelations, coups, political strife… countless chain reactions spread in the various Star Fields.

The root of this storm in the universe was the Flickering War between the three Universal Civilizations and the Super Star Cluster Alliance. After the Immortals disappeared, the war became more and more intense, gradually turning from using representatives to sending in official armies.

Even though both sides kept the battles as undestructive as possible, the large-scale battles between advanced civilizations were not things ordinary organizations could take part in.

The various frontlines in the fourth exploration phase exploration area became almost forbidden grounds. Once the war machines of advanced civilizations started moving, they were different from the battles between individuals with great power. It was as if they had taken over the sky.

In the face of the attacks of the three Universal Civilizations' official armies, due to the problem of having a limited supply lines, the Super Star Cluster Alliance started to show signs of defeat. Their territories were snatched away time after time, and their battlefronts kept shrinking.

In the midst of all this madness, the Beyond Grade As, however, were unshaken. Their days were spent in comfort, keeping a low profile while slowly completing the association's profit network, linking the Beyond Grade A organizations from various industries.

While heated wars were going on outside, Han Xiao ignored all of it and announced his isolation. Other than the Beyond Grade A meetings, he did not step out of the gates of his workshop at all, spending all his time studying the technology treasure trove from Jayz.

The operation of the Black Star Army no longer required his attention. With the army's resources and partnerships with multiple organizations, it slowly expanded the subdivisions in the various Star Fields. The immense profits earned were used by the Great Mechanic Han to study the technology. The army was making so much money that he could not spend it all. His cash power became ever stronger.

With his current position, no one dared mess with him without good reason. As for those who were overconfident and did not know where they stood, the army could easily deal with them. There was no need for Han Xiao to settle those issues personally.

The various Primordial Ones of the Holy Accord organization were training secretly and peacefully. Manison, Sorokin, and the others who had beef with him were also busy with their own things. No one came to disturb him.

In this peaceful environment, the Great Mechanic Han finally had the time to study technology for several years.

During which, he even obtained the Stuarts Peace Prize once and got himself a Legendary Point, as well as some fame for some time.

High-level beings' sense of time varied. They could make one second feel many times longer to themselves, and they could let pass months in the blink of an eye. Therefore, Han Xiao never felt bored being submerged in the sea of knowledge. He even grew more patient.

Days passed in the flames of war. The time now was Galaxy Calendar Year 738.

At a certain secret Crimson Dynasty military training base, all of the lessons had stopped. All the students and drill sergeants gathered in the biggest square and looked up at the enormous virtual screen in the sky.

The screen was split into dozens of smaller windows displaying different images. Most of the screens were showing different angles of a silhouette that was shining brightly from all over his body.

One of the windows that was showing the widest angle was displaying a spherical mechanical satellite that was filled with energy circuits. Condensed chimney-looking devices extended from all over the satellite. Some were absorbing the dark energy that existed everywhere in the cosmic space, and some were shooting out white plasma. The energy circuits on the satellite's surface flickered like it was breathing. This seemed to be a certain kind of energy cycling and converting device.

If the people on the square looked at the other side of the sky, they would see that many more similar satellites were hovering above the base. One of them was operating, and it was the one shown on the screen.

This was one of the facilities in this training base. Its official name was 'High Energy Life Form Enhancing Device', commonly known by the students as the Energy Tower. It only had one function. Through a special method of converting and accumulating energy, it could create a special environment to help Calamity Grades take that crucial step, slightly increasing their chances of becoming Beyond Grade As.

Usually, this device would not be used even once in many years. Now, someone who could use it finally appeared. It was indeed Gaud, who was very famous in the base.

After training for many years in the base, he had finally reached the point where he had to take this step.

All students and drill sergeants came to witness it, holding their breath and waited for the birth of a new Beyond Grade A.

In the images, the shining silhouette was in the middle of the energy vortex created by the device, ravaging the energy around him, creating colorful energy streams that looked like silk as well as fog. It was dreamy.

After some time, the silhouette seemed to have reached saturation and gradually stopped absorbing energy. The brightness of it slowly reduced.

The next moment, Gaud opened his eyes. A beam of light shot out and retracted back one second later.

As he moved his body, he turned into a meteor and flew out from the tunnel within the device. He descended from the sky in front of everyone and hovered above the crowd.

"He did it!"

Deafening sounds of cheers shot up the sky from the square. Everyone present had witnessed the birth of a Beyond Grade A. They were thrilled.

Gaud controlled his body and landed on the ground. The base manager and the chief instructor approached, their faces filled with bright smiles.

"Congratulations on stepping into the territory of the Beyond Grade A. You really did not disappoint the dynasty!"

Back then, the two of them had felt that Grade A had the chance of becoming a Beyond Grade A within eight years, but Gaud had done it in just less than five years. It was better than they expected, and they were happier than anyone because of it.

Gaud moved his fingers around, seemingly familiarizing himself with the new power he had gained. "The dynasty upper echelons should want to see me, when?"

"Yes, the Ruler is already waiting for you."

"Lead the way then."

Gaud tone was normal.

The students were chased away by the drill sergeant. Gaud changed his clothes and went with the manager of the base to a remote communication room.

Then, the base manager left leaving Gaud alone in the room.

Gaud operated the communication device, activated the remote projection, and entered the preset channel. The next moment, the environment in his sights changed. He came to the Ruler's office. Urranrell was sitting in her chair, and Clotti was standing right away.

"Congratulations on becoming a Beyond Grade A. The dynasty is proud of you." Urranrell's tone was friendly.

"Greetings, Your Excellency Urranrell." Gaud nodded.

"You've done a great job. Your growth exceeded our expectations…"

Urranrell gave him some words of praise and encouragement. This was the patriotic education every direct Beyond Grade A had to go through. It was to encourage them to contribute to the dynasty.

After saying that, Urranrell quickly got to business and said, "The dynasty will adjust your authority, privileges, and position as soon as possible. Do you have any thoughts about the position you'd like to take?"

"My power isn't solid yet. I don't wish to take on any positions for the time being. As for the future… I think my ability is very suitable for the research and developments area. I hope to take on a position in the dynasty's Science Institute."

Gaud smiled faintly.

"Hmm, the dynasty will consider your suggestion." Urranrell nodded.

This time, Gaud narrowed his eyes and said, "Speaking of which, I'm already a Beyond Grade A now. Is the plan regarding the Evolution Cube going to be carried out?"

Hearing this, Urranrell's movements paused for a second.

Many years ago, the dynasty's upper echelons had secretly made a plan to use Gaud's Esper Ability to analyze the energy composition of the Evolution Cube after Gaud became a Beyond Grade A. This way, they would have a chance to secretly crack part of the mechanisms of the Evolution Cube, so the dynasty would acquire this technology as a form of insurance.

However, the Black Star Army had been growing stronger too quickly over the past years. The risk of this plan had increased rapidly. After Black Star became the Special Safety Consultant of the three Universal Civilizations, this plan was indefinitely postponed.

Urranrell went silent for a few seconds, shook her head, and said, "This plan won't be carried out yet. We don't wish to damage our relationship with Black Star for now, even if the chance of that is very low."

Gaud narrowed his eyes and asked, "Alright, will I still have the privilege of using the Evolution Cube?"

"Yes. If you want it, submit a request. We'll arrange to put you in the next fleet headed for the Flickering World to use the Evolution Cube."

Then, Urranrell paused and added, "When you arrive at the Flickering World, go to Planet Finn while you're there and join the Beyond Grade A Association. The dynasty needs more direct members in the association to keep an eye on their movements."

"Sure, I'll go."

The two of them talked for a while more before cutting off the communication. From the start to the end, Clotti did not say a word.

After the remote projection was deactivated, Gaud returned to his room. His eyes were flickering.

He pondered for a while, then as he was about to exit the room, his private communicator suddenly rang. He received an encrypted communication request. It was surprisingly from Bekorodi.

Gaud made contact with the hawk faction very long ago. Bekorodi was one of the upper echelons of the military hawk faction. After the plan was postponed, the two of them had not spoken in a very long time. He was curious as to why Bekorodi called him.

The communication was picked up very soon.

"Gaud?"

"It's me. What is it?"

"Congrats on becoming a Beyond Grade A. Remember the plan back then? Stick to it. When you're going through the evolution process from the Evolution Cube, use your ability to analyze the Evolution Energy." In the encrypted channel, Bekorodi's voice was very blurry.

"Oh? That's not what the ruler said." Gaud found it interesting.

Bekorodi seemed to have expected this. He lowered his voice and said, "The Flickering War won't last for long."

This reply did not seem to answer Gaud's question at all, but he understood what Bekorodi meant.

The entire dynasty knew that Urranrell's term was about to end, and that would certainly happen after the war ended. Then, the already chosen new ruler would take her place.

Toward the end of her term, Urranrell's control over the upper echelons weakened unavoidably. The identity of the new ruler was a secret to the outside world but not to someone like Bekorodi.

Although Gaud did not know who the new ruler was, he was almost certain Bekorodi telling him to continue the plan of analyzing the Evolution Cube was already secretly approved by the new ruler.

Through this, Gaud could see that the next ruler seemed to be more controlling. It was no wonder the next ruler was close to the hawk faction.

From another perspective, this might also be because the new ruler did not wish to execute such a risky plan during their term, so they wanted to carry out this plan at the end of Urranrell's term.

Gaud thought for a while before slowly saying, "Understood, I'll find a way."

"Good, I'm counting on you."

Bekorodi gave a short response before hanging up.

Gaud did not take this matter to heart at all. He looked like he was thinking of something in the past.

"Black Star, we're finally going to meet again…"

A few days later, in the Black Star Army commander's private workshop, Han Xiao was debugging the machines when he suddenly received a report from Phillip.

"Master, I've received the name list for the next batch of candidates from the dynasty who are going to accept the evolution process from the Evolution Cube hum."

Han Xiao continued to do his things and said casually, "Anyone worth paying attention to?"

"Yes, yes. A new direct Beyond Grade A of the dynasty is on this list. His name is Gaud, hum!"

Han Xiao's movement suddenly stopped.

"Gaud?"

He put down the work in his hands, brought the list up, and looked at the basic information of Gaud. His eyes instantly narrowed as he searched through his memories.

"I think I met him a few times decades ago when fighting the Kunde Race. He seemed to only be an aide-de-camp back then…"

That's weird. I didn't expect this guy to become a Beyond Grade A. This guy did not exist in my previous life. Is this because of the butterfly effects I've caused again?

Han Xiao grinned slightly.

"Interesting. When this guy gets here, I'm going to find out what's going on."

Anyway, no matter who Gaud was, since such a person did not appear in his previous life, there were definitely some secrets within him. He might even come across a hidden mission or sorts, so there was no reason for him to let it past.

Chapter 1219: [Esper Ability—Rebirth]

Phillip's report interrupted his work. Han Xiao thought about it and decided to rest a while. He left the workshop, entered his personal lounge, and sat on the couch. He waved his hand to have the mechanical assistant bring some snacks and drinks, then browsed the recent news on the quantum network.

During the version upgrade, the forums were frozen, so Han Xiao lost a major form of entertainment. In his free time, other than teleporting to Floating Dragon Island to accompany Ames, all he did was look at the news online.

Looking at the situation of the Flickering War, Han Xiao thought, Yo, it's already at this stage. The Super Star Cluster Alliance is almost going to lose grip. Looks like they couldn't change their fate. The ending of the war is near.

Due to the butterfly effect he caused, Han Xiao could not accurately predict which exact day the Flickering War would end. However, judging from the current situation, the dust would probably settle within three years. The Super Star Cluster Alliance would not be able to last much longer.

The Flickering War broke out in Galaxy Calendar Year 732. Six years had already passed. This was close to what he predicted. He felt that the war would last at least three to five years, and at most ten to twenty years.

Although the Intelligent Plague broke out in advance, causing the Super Star Cluster Alliance to have more time to prepare, there were still way too many factors that caused them to have disadvantages. The Super Star Cluster Alliance were fighting a defensive war. The battlefield was far from their territory, they were surrounded by enemies like an island. In the past years, the three Universal Civilizations cut off tons of secret supply routes of the enemy, causing the Super Star Cluster Alliance to have less and less external support. Their situation was becoming worse every day.

The only way for the Super Star Cluster Alliance to get out of this situation was through external means, dispatching soldiers from their home territory and making new battle zones in other Star Fields. However, if they did that, the nature of the war would become completely different. The laws between advanced civilizations would break, and the scale of the war would jump multiple levels. The war would become much more intense.

They were just putting down a small bet. No one could take the consequences of flipping the table completely.

Han Xiao rubbed his chin and said, "When the war is over, the Crimson Dynasty and the Federation of Light are both going to have different leaders. Urranrell's term will end, and she'll retire. The new ruler… tsk, a troublesome person."

He was not sure if the butterfly effect he caused would change who the next ruler was, but the chance of that was not high. Hence, of course, he knew who the new ruler was.

Although he occasionally had trouble with Urranrell, the partnership was quite pleasant. However, the next ruler was someone in the hawk faction who had different ways of doing things.

In his previous life, the Calamity of the Supers and the Silver Revolutionary Army both happened during the term of the new ruler. The next ruler was also the ruler the players were most familiar with in his previous life.

The ruler was not as lenient toward the Supers, which was also one of the reasons the Calamity of the Supers broke out. The next president of the Federation of Light was also not the nicest person.

"When the new ruler takes office, he'll definitely make contact with all the Beyond Grade A allies. I hope things can stay the same."

Han Xiao shook his head. Throughout history, every time the new took over the old, a lot of problems would come up.

He put this thought behind him and looked at the interface. Currently, his [God's Trait Transformation—Machinery] was already at the twelfth stage. He settled all the prerequisite missions with Mission Completion Cards, so he only spent a total of seven God's Trait Transformation Points.

The cost of leveling up to the thirteenth stage was eight points with three prerequisite missions. This meant that it would at least require five God's Trait Transformation Points.

The technology treasure trove from Jayz consisted of Gold blueprints. This was a gold mountain that needed to be digested slowly. Han Xiao only studied part of it in the past years, and he already felt that his inventory had become richer.

If he was to accumulate Contribution Points and exchange Gold blueprints from the three Universal Civilizations, God knew when he would be able to obtain this much knowledge.

Han Xiao considered the technology as his final trump card and had yet to display any of it.

He believed that once he used it in front of others, the various civilizations and the other Beyond Grade As would probably be in an uproar, and he would face tons of trouble. Hence, it was better to slowly study them for now.

…

More than two months later, a dynasty fleet arrived at Black Star Palace, carrying the new batch of dynasty elites there to receive the evolution process from the Evolution Cube.

Spaceships rode into the dock at the exterior base of Black Star Palace one after another. The hatches opened, and the elites from the various departments of the dynasty swarmed out, gathering on the platform.

As the only Beyond Grade A, Gaud naturally became the leader. As soon as he stepped onto the dock, a few army receptionists approached him directly.

"Elites of the dynasty, welcome to the Black Star Army. The army commander has been waiting. Please follow me."

Then, the receptionist led the way ahead, and the crowd followed behind.

They quickly came to an intersection.

This time, the receptionist stopped, turned to Gaud, and said, "Your Excellency Gaud, the army commander would like to chat with you. Please follow me to see the army commander. As for the rest of you, my colleague will bring you to the hall to wait for the evolution process."

This was the army's territory. The two sides had been partners for many years, so the dynasty elites had no objections. Black Star's love for networking spread across the entire universe; no one found this strange.

"Lead the way then."

Gaud nodded with a calm expression.

The crowd split into two and went different directions. Gaud followed the receptionist. The footsteps of the others soon faded.

The two of them came to a private guest room, opened the door, and walked in. Gaud immediately saw Han Xiao, who was standing in front of the window, facing away from him.

The stars were shining brightly outside the window. The person in front of the window was tall, muscular, and had wide shoulders, giving off a manly vibe all over his body. He looked like a Pugilist.

Hearing the sound of the door opening, Han Xiao turned around, gave a friendly smile, and pointed at the seat with a hand gesture.

"You must be Gaud. The dynasty got another direct Beyond Grade A member, congratulations. Quick, please sit."

"We meet again. Do you still remember me?" Gaud sat down, his tone casual.

"Of course, we met once during the Kunde Race war."

Han Xiao sat opposite Gaud, secretly sizing him up. He was now completely certain this person never existed in his previous life. He wondered where he came from.

Gaud nodded, smiled faintly, and said, "Yes, then you definitely remember what I said back then. I said we'll surely become colleagues one day, and now it has come true."

"I like your confidence. I love to make friends with people who have a lot of potential."

Han Xiao nodded but was secretly pondering in his mind.

From how it looked, this guy was someone who had extreme confidence. Even when speaking with him, he was casual and did not put himself in a lower position… This was very common among the new Beyond Grade As. It only felt arrogant but nothing strange other than that.

In the database of the dynasty, the information of the direct Beyond Grade As was all kept secret. Even with Han Xiao's authorization as an ally, he could only find some of the basic information, and Gaud's past was very clean. He looked like a regular military man of the dynasty.

Han Xiao was only curious because this person did not exist in his previous life. He did not have any other suspicions for now.

Gaud was a direct member of the dynasty, so Han Xiao was in no position to question him. Of course, he was not going to cause trouble with a colleague just to satisfy his curiosity.

Afterward, they had a casual and pleasant chat.

After a while, Han Xiao felt it was time and said with a smile, "I'm a little curious as to what your ability is. Is it ok to tell me?"

"The world will know my ability sooner or later. But before that, let me keep it a secret for some time. This is what the dynasty requested too." Gaud grinned and refused.

Seeing this, Han Xiao did not continue to push him but neither did he give up—he decided to sting him later.

They chatted for a while longer. Gaud actively stopped their chat and said with a smile, "Black Star, let's stop chatting for now. The others are still waiting. I want to go through the evolution process as soon as possible. I still have to visit Planet Finn and request to join the Beyond Grade A Association."

"Oh, that's easy. I'm the vice president. I'll handle the procedures needed." Han Xiao stood up. "Since you're in a hurry, I won't keep you. Let's keep in contact in the future."

Then, the two of them walked out of the room side by side and came to the hall where the dynasty elites gathered. They were all waiting there.

Han Xiao said a few words of encouragement and raised his hand. The Evolution Cube hovered and spun in front of him.

He entered the secret code to activate it. Black Evolution Energy gushed out and swept past everyone like a tide.

Then energy solidified and black cocoons appeared in the hall. Gaud was in one of them.

The place became silent instantly. Only Han Xiao was able to walk around.

Hehe, kid, you can't move now, can you?

Han Xiao giggled, stowing the Evolution Cube. Then, he controlled the nanoparticles to form a needle and poked it into the black cocoon Gaud was in.

He knew how it felt to go through the evolution process. They would feel an overwhelming itch all over their body. The senses inside their body would be enhanced, and their senses of the outside world would become dull.

Even if Gaud discovered he did this, he was not worried. After all, he could easily find an excuse for it.

The combat information popped up on the interface, and Han Xiao browsed through it carefully.

"Gaud, level… oh, 240? He's got a lot of potential, his level is the same as mine when I became a Beyond Grade A… Woah, this guy's ability is Energy Control‽ This is the top tier ability among the Super High Risk Esper Abilities. It actually really exists. No wonder he's so secretive about it. This ability almost counters all classes…"

Han Xiao was secretly shocked.

There were stronger and weaker Super High Risk Esper Abilities too, and Energy Control was undoubtedly top tier. It only existed in theory before, but now it really appeared. Gaud was probably the first ever person to possess this ability.

His ability was outrageously powerful, and his potential was also very high. If he continued training, becoming a peak Beyond Grade A would only be a matter of time. It was no wonder the dynasty poured so many resources into training him and kept him a highly confidential secret. This kid got a golden future!

In the battle of Beyond Grade As, one's Esper Ability was a decisive factor too. If Gaud reached the same level as Clotti, Gaud would have a more than ninety-percent chance of beating Clotti. This was the advantage his Esper Ability had.

Energy Control countered almost all Supers. Be it psychic, magic, psionic, or dark energy, they were all included in the energy this ability could control. The only restriction was the user's strength, which decided the limits of his control.

It would not be an exaggeration to say when Gaud reached his peak, he would be absolutely qualified to compete for the spot of the strongest individual in the entire explored universe.

No wonder he was so confident, anyone who had an Esper Ability with infinite potential like this one would be very confident about their future.

How did the dynasty get this lucky? Where did they find this guy? Han Xiao exclaimed in his mind, but then he wondered. Wait a minute, if he has such an extremely powerful Esper Ability, he shouldn't have been completely unknown in my previous life.

Did he die in my previous life and the butterfly effect I caused saved him?

Han Xiao continued browsing the interface with these doubts in his mind. He was then appalled to discover that Gaud's attributes were quite irregular. The other attributes suited his level, but his Intellect and Mystic were way too high. One was more than 9,000, and the other was 13,000.

That doesn't check out. When I became a Beyond Grade A at level 240, my highest attribute, Intellect, was only just over six thousand, and my second highest attribute, Endurance, was little more than four thousand. How are his attributes so high? This is almost the normal standard for Beyond Grade As who are about level 320!

Han Xiao initially only wanted to look at his Esper Ability, but he discovered more and more dubious things on the way, and he got more and more suspicious.

He looked through his information for some time. Suddenly, his eyes were drawn to one of Gaud's talents as he discovered another anomaly.

[Esper Ability—Rebirth]: Your body has been reborn. Your soul is still strong. You have inherited a fraction of the INT and MYS attributes from before.

This is…

Han Xiao's eyes immediately widened.

He could think of many things just from the name of this talent.

There's indeed something unusual!

This kid is probably just some new Beyond Grade A. His secrets seem to be more shocking than I thought!

Chapter 1220: Speculation

Body is reborn. Soul is still strong…

Looking at Gaud's cocoon, Han Xiao started pondering.

According to the introduction of [Esper Ability—Rebirth], it was similar to how Psychics could possess others' minds, as well as Sorokin's ability to keep changing identities. Judging from the several anomalies on Gaud's attributes in the interface, he was most likely someone who 'started a new account'.

The detailed mechanisms of this ability were still unknown. It should be in the form of changing a body but keeping the same soul. If that was the case, judging from Gaud's Intellect and Mystic attributes, he should have been a Beyond Grade A before he was reborn.

This was where the problem lay—the ability [Esper Ability—Rebirth] almost had no combat capability and extremely limited uses, as well as a very low growth potential. It should not allow the user to become a Beyond Grade A.

Either Gaud did not have [Esper Ability—Rebirth] and received help from another Super who had it to complete the rebirth, or a Grade A became a Beyond Grade A with both Energy Control and [Esper Ability—Rebirth].

There was not much speculation to be done if it was the former, but if it was the latter, Han Xiao only knew one person who had this ability…

EsGod!

Could it be that b*stard? His body is locked in the Spacetime Amber but his soul escaped?

Han Xiao's eyes flickered. He was used to making daring speculations.

The chance of EsGod breaking out of the Spacetime Amber was very low, which meant he would have done it before he was captured.

The possibility of this was not low. EsGod had enemies everywhere, so he would have most likely prepared for it. Plus, he absorbed so many strange Esper Abilities. There was a high chance he had this type of ability. Maybe this was why he dared to make enemies everywhere, since he could 'start a new account' once his main account was done for.

However, [Esper Ability—Rebirth] was somewhat different from other ways of changing bodies. For example, no matter how many times Sorokin changed bodies, his abilities would remain the same. His soul was his foundation. However, the foundation of being able to absorb Esper Abilities was in the genetics of EsGod's body, and his body was trapped in the Spacetime Amber. If Gaud was really EsGod, by changing into another body, his abilities should have changed too. He would have lost the ability to absorb Esper Abilities and only have one Esper Ability, [Energy Control].

Could it be that Gaud is a secret container EsGod prepared for himself? Hmm, EsGod was always driven to create Super High Risk Esper Abilities. Energy Control might be the results of many years' work. That b*stard might have really succeeded in fusing a ton of Esper Abilities into one overpowered ability and somehow planted it into Gaud's body…

Han Xiao pondered.

Gaud did not appear out of nowhere; he had a complete life. Since the dynasty was confident enough to pour resources onto him, the dynasty was definitely certain that Gaud's background was clean.

If this was EsGod's doing, he definitely started to prepare for it a very long time ago. Somehow, he was able to create an identity with a clean background.

If this speculation was true, EsGod joining the three Universal Civilizations after being reborn would not just be to simply 'join them if you can't defeat them' but part of a very ambitious and huge plan.

This might be how it happened…

To achieve his goal, EsGod committed countless crimes, became an enemy of the world, and finally created a Super High Risk Esper Ability with infinite potential. However, the identity 'EsGod' was too notorious, so he would never have peace even though he obtained this ability. Furthermore, his genetic chain became overloaded as a side effect of absorbing countless Esper Abilities. He might have planned to give up this identity long ago!

Therefore, EsGod planted the Super High Risk Esper Ability he created into a 'container', waiting for the day to use Rebirth and shift his soul into it. Thus, he got a new life, a new identity, and joined the three Universal Civilizations with the Super High Risk Esper Ability he had obtained. He was raised by the three Universal Civilizations and wiped his history completely clean!

Han Xiao pondered.

EsGod is definitely someone who could do something like this. He does not care about whether he's a wanted criminal or a member of a civilization. All that matters is how much he will benefit from the faction he's in. He only ever had one goal, to step into that higher territory…

The more he thought about it, the more likely it seemed. This should be one of EsGod's many plans.

However, all of this relied on the assumption of 'Gaud is EsGod' being true. Actually, just having [Esper Ability—Rebirth] could not prove this to be completely true.

Although he felt there was a high chance Gaud was EsGod, the evidence was not enough for him to fully believe it.

Make daring speculations and cautiously search for evidence… it's a pity Bold Explorer can't be used on people.

Han Xiao shook his head.

No matter who Gaud really was, he did a perfect job of rebirthing, not leaving any clues behind. He thought no one would notice it, which was why he was so confident and relaxed when he was with Han Xiao.

Luckily, my level is higher than his, so I saw all of his abilities. I might be the only one who's discovered Gaud's secrets…

Han Xiao did not leave but sat on the side and waited while brainstorming.

After a while, the black cocoons in the room shattered one after another. Dynasty elites completed the evolution process and came out of it one after another, feeling refreshed. Seeing that Han Xiao was still there waiting for them, they could not help but feel flattered.

Gaud took the longest and came out of the cocoon last.

"How are you feeling?" Han Xiao acted completely normal and spoke with a friendly tone.

"Quite good." Gaud glanced at Han Xiao. "When I was inside, I felt someone poke me with a needle. Was that you?"

"Haha, don't mind it. That's a needle used to check if the evolution process is going smoothly. You're a direct member of the dynasty, so I have to pay more attention. After all, the evolution process is not completely safe. There are still risks, and I don't want anything to happen to you." Han Xiao smiled and easily found an excuse to cover it up.

Gaud nodded and calmly said, "Thanks for your concern. I have to go to Planet Finn, so I won't disturb you any longer."

Seeing that Gaud intended to leave, Han Xiao did not stop him. "Alright, I won't keep you then. See you in the association."

Then, Han Xiao turned around and left the hall, quickly disappearing from everyone's sights.

Gaud's eyes gleamed, followed the receptionist and returned to the dock, led the dynasty elites back to the fleet.

The dynasty fleet quickly left the dock, shot into the galaxy, and split up into two groups. One headed back with the dynasty elites, and the other carried Gaud to head to Planet Finn deep in the Flickering World.

In the spaceship, Gaud looked at Black Star Palace getting further in the porthole. A slight grin appeared on his face.

"Black Star, oh, Black Star, I said we will meet again sooner or later, but never would you have expected not to recognize me when I stand in front of you again, even enthusiastically trying to befriend me…"

Seeing how Black Star had absolutely no idea, Gaud could not help but laugh in his mind.

Tricking Black Star right under his nose felt strangely thrilling.

During the evolution process earlier, he used his ability to try to analyze the Evolution Energy. With the edge his ability had, he already had some clues.

"No wonder this is an ability only thought to exist in theory. With enough time, I'll have a sixty-percent chance of figuring out the Evolution Energy. My position will then skyrocket in the dynasty, and the upper echelons will also be more likely to agree with my request of being stationed at the Science Institute when they see the results. This way, I'll be closer to the dynasty's research results of that set of data from back then…"

A snicker appeared on Gaud's face as he went through the plan in his mind.

Han Xiao watched the departing dynasty fleet from his office.

"I did not act differently. Gaud should not know that I've already seen through his secrets. The most important thing now is to find out who this guy really is. He's a big uncertainty…"

Han Xiao frowned slightly.

The situation was not in his favor currently. Gaud was a direct member of the dynasty. This identity protected him. There were many things Han Xiao could not do because of it.

The imminent issue was to acquire evidence to prove there was something abnormal with Gaud. Only then would he have sufficient reasons to do something.

Otherwise, if he beat up a new direct Beyond Grade A whom the dynasty expected a lot of for no reason, he could easily imagine just how strongly the dynasty would respond.

The dynasty had to take responsibility for all of its direct members, so they would certainly never compromise or take a step back. In the worst case, the dynasty would instantly become his enemy, which would destroy almost all the preparation he had done up till now. Even though he was very useful to the dynasty, when it came to this kind of thing, there was zero room for negotiation. The dynasty would not hesitate to lose him as an ally.

As long as there was no evidence, any explanation for such actions would be meaningless.

If he really had to act without enough evidence, he had to do it secretly and wipe out all the clues. There could not be witnesses, clues, or anything else, and he must not fail…

"The risk is too high. There'll be tons of problems if I'm even slightly careless."

Han Xiao shook his head.

Clearly, giving up the profit network and connections he had built up over all the years just for Gaud was certainly not worth it. Unless he had no other choice, he would never do it.

There was a less risky path now, so Han Xiao did not want to take this risk.

If Gaud really is EsGod, something has definitely happened with the body he left in the Spacetime Amber… Looks like I'll have to request from the dynasty to visit EsGod.

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes.

Gaud still had to stay in the Flickering World for some time. It would be best to figure things out before he returned. Otherwise, things would be much more difficult once Gaud returned to the dynasty's territory no matter what he wanted to do.

Ding!

While he was pondering, a notification popped up on the interface.

You have triggered the hidden mission [Gaud's Secret]!

Mission Introduction: Gaud is a new direct Beyond Grade A of the Crimson Dynasty. During your contact with him, you noticed something abnormal about him. This might be a shocking secret.

Mission Requirements: Figure out Gaud's secret.

Reward: 1 Character Summon Card, draw one ability/talent from the target.

Tip: This mission might affect your relationship with the Crimson Dynasty faction. Please decide how to act cautiously.

Han Xiao looked at the interface.

A hidden mission… Was it triggered because I saw his abilities? That's not an easy trigger condition… I can only see all of Gaud's abilities because my level is higher than his. I'm probably the only person who can trigger this mission.

Chapter 1221: Release

Han Xiao turned off the interface, prepared a request to visit EsGod, and sent it to the dynasty.

After a short while, he received the response.

"Hmm? My file got sent back?"

Han Xiao looked at the virtual screen in front of him that was showing the request file he sent to the dynasty.

A red stamp was added to the bottom right corner of the file that wrote 'Unapproved' in the dynasty's language. This meant that his request was rejected.

"The dynasty isn't letting me visit EsGod. What does that mean?"

Han Xiao frowned. He took out his communicator, thought for a while, and did not call Urranrell's private number but her office.

The communicator rang for a while and was picked up very soon. Seeing that it was Black Star calling, the liaison officer directed the call to the head secretary of the office.

"Your Excellency Black Star, what can I do for you?" The head secretary had a good relationship with Han Xiao.

"I have just sent a request to visit EsGod, but it was not approved. Is this Urranrell's decision?"

"Ah, Her Excellency has been attending a meeting, so it shouldn't be her. I didn't know about this. Your request was not reported to us."

"Can you check which department processed the request for me?"

"Sure, please wait for a moment…"

The head secretary searched through the internal system for a while and brought up the files before sighing.

"This is the collective decision of the dynasty's main artificial intelligence, Heroic Soul, and the prison department. I looked at their internal remarks. The location of EsGod is top secret, and no one is allowed to visit under normal circumstances. Your Excellency Black Star, you are a special case. You're surprisingly on their visiting blacklist…"

"Why am I on the blacklist? What did I do?" Han Xiao was confused.

The head secretary sighed and said, "You didn't do anything, but you're currently the only person in the world who can release EsGod. Therefore, before the five-hundred-year sentence ends, you're not allowed to visit…"

Han Xiao was speechless.

I caught EsGod for the dynasty, and now I can't even visit him?

Alright, from the dynasty's perspective, this is logical. I'm the only person in the universe who can open the Spacetime Amber seal, so I'm the only one who has the ability to release him. This way, the reason for the dynasty rejecting my visit seems normal. It's simply to avoid risk.

Although it was not wrong for the dynasty to do this, Han Xiao was still disheartened emotionally.

He thought the request would be smoothly approved. He did not expect it to get rejected.

"Can't something be done?" Han Xiao frowned.

"The authorization level for EsGod's prison is very high. If you must visit him, you'll have to ask the Ruler to help. She can approve your request, but it'll need a sensible reason, otherwise…"

Hearing that, Han Xiao nodded.

He had quite a good relationship with Urranrell, but there was no way she could just approve it without a valid reason.

Han Xiao hung up the communication. Urranrell was in a quite important meeting, so he had to wait a while before he could contact her. Since there was time, he used it to think about what to say.

"I was going to see EsGod by visiting him, but sadly, that won't work. Without a valid reason, the dynasty won't allow me to get close to EsGod's cell in any form. Even the coordinates of the prison are a secret, and I don't have the authority to check it…"

Han Xiao tutted with dissatisfaction.

Simply saying he wanted to check on EsGod would not be able to convince the dynasty. Plus, he had to open the amber seal if he wanted to check on EsGod. The best method was still to come up with a special reason so that the dynasty would allow him to open the amber. The risk of this method was the lowest.

If he could not convince the dynasty, he would probably have to imitate Old Manison and try to hack into the dynasty's database to search for related information. Although he would offend the dynasty by doing so, stealing information was not too serious an offence… but this could only be the backup plan.

After a while, the secretary sent a message to him saying that the Ruler's meeting ended. Han Xiao then called Urranrell's private number, and it was picked up very quickly.

Urranrell appeared on the screen with a calm face and cut to the chase.

"Black Star, I heard you just tried to contact me and want to visit EsGod, why?"

Although she hid it very well, Han Xiao was very observant and saw that Urranrell was a little mentally tired. He thought about it and said, "EsGod has already been locked up for decades. I want to open the seal and check on the status of his soul. "

"Is that necessary?" Urranrell frowned. "You were the one who suggested the five-hundred-year sentence, and it's only been a few decades. With EsGod's strength, his soul won't have dissipated this quickly. Opening the seal now will only cause trouble."

"Ahem, I was not strong enough back then and had a limited understanding of the level of strength EsGod has. That's why I suggested that the sentence should be as long as possible. Five hundred years was just a rough estimate. Now that I've reached this level and have a deeper understanding of the Spacetime Amber, I've discovered that wiping out the soul of a Beyond Grade A probably won't take that long."

Han Xiao said the reason he had prepared. He did not have proof to explain his suspicion of Gaud, so saying that would only make the dynasty suspicious. Thus, he did not mention Gaud.

Urranrell did not doubt him but still shook her head and said, "I don't think that's needed. EsGod is too dangerous. I still think imprisoning him is the safest. The dynasty can afford to wait that long."

Han Xiao expected Urranrell to say this; he was not surprised. "Experimenting on him is just one of the goals. I actually have other worries. I've only come to understand how strong someone at this level is, and thinking back now, I realized that capturing EsGod was too easy. Something's not right. From what I know about EsGod, he very likely escaped using some kind of soul-related ability. I'm worried that we've been tricked, so I want to open the seal and check."

Urranrell's eyes flickered, but she was still not very convinced.

"Evidence?"

Han Xiao deliberately spoke in a solemn tone. "This is just speculation, which is why I want to verify it. But if you need evidence, you can ask Lotus Swordsman. Back when we caught EsGod, she sensed a strange soul ripple from EsGod. I suspect that was where the problem lay."

Gaud was a star the dynasty had high hopes for, so mentioning him was not a wise choice. Han Xiao's words were mainly targeted at EsGod.

Hearing this, Urranrell finally became serious about the issue and immediately told the head secretary to contact Lotus Swordsman.

Lotus Swordsman came online very quickly and agreed that it did happen. Only about thirty years had passed since it happened, so she remembered it vividly.

Seeing this, Han Xiao heaved a sigh of relief in his mind. This evidence actually could not prove anything. Everyone thought that it was just EsGod's final meaningless struggle. However, now that he made use of it to make his excuse sound more convincing… If this did not happen, convincing Urranrell would probably have been much more difficult.

Having received a response, Urranrell went silent, seemingly analyzing the pros and cons. After a while, she looked up right at Han Xiao's eyes and said seriously, "Black Star, if EsGod gets free, can you guarantee you can capture him again?"

Han Xiao smiled. "I could do it then; I can do it now."

He no longer had the Esper Silence Character Summon Card, but after decades, he was much stronger than before. Even if his guess was wrong, he would just have to seal EsGod up once more.

Furthermore, the others did not know that the Character Summon Card was a one-time ability. They would only think that he could still use the ability.

Urranrell pondered for quite a while and nodded in the end.

"Okay, I'll approve it! Since your suspicion makes sense, open the seal and check EsGod's status. Make sure that we did not capture an empty shell!"

…

Over ten days later…

A huge cube shaped mechanical building hovered in space. It was a galactic fortress covered with armor and shields that were more than enough to endure bombardments from hostile fleets. This was the space prison EsGod was locked up in.

At this point of time, dense dynasty fleets surrounded the prison. Cannons extended from every battleship, all ready to fire.

A black silhouette hovered near the prison. It was Han Xiao. He had opened the secondary dimensional army box and was summoning his army, forming a second encirclement.

Gaud was still on his way in the Flickering World. Han Xiao wasted no time and directly used the King to teleport into the dynasty's subdivision in their territory, boarded the dynasty fleet that was there to pick him up, spent about ten days traveling, and finally arrived at this restricted area.

After summoning countless mechanical soldiers, Han Xiao finally closed the secondary dimensional army box gate and said in the communication channel, "I'm ready. Activate all spacetime stabilization devices and open the prison core."

"Roger." The fleet commander's serious voice sounded in the channel.

The next moment, an invisible ripple extended from the fleet's center. The spacetime of this area instantly 'tightened'. The spacetime coefficients of this area became extremely stable. Almost all abilities related to spacetime became useless.

Then, the space prison opened layers by layers like a blossoming flower showing its stamen. The core of the prison was an egg-shaped cabin that stored the Spacetime Amber of EsGod, tightly locked in place by the mechanical structure of the prison.

As the prison opened, the egg-shaped cabin was unlocked as well. Its independent power system started operating. The thrusters shot out flames and slowly pushed the cabin out.

As Han Xiao extended his arm, his Mechanical Force pulled the ten-meter-long egg-shaped cabin toward him. He then opened the cabin door.

A familiar face entered his sights. It was EsGod, who had been trapped in the Spacetime Amber for decades. He still had the same expression and posture as his last moment of freedom before he was locked up.

"All units ready! Prepare to fire!"

The fleet commander's grave toned voice sounded in the communication channel.

Even after decades, the fear EsGod had left in people's hearts had yet to fade away.

"Now, it's time to verify my speculation…"

Han Xiao looked into EsGod's eyes, took a deep breath, took out the core of the Spacetime Amber, and poked at the Spacetime Amber seal.

Pop!

It was as if the crisp sound of the Spacetime Amber shattering could be heard.

The prison that locked EsGod up was opened, but his body did not move. It only floated in the vacuum right before Han Xiao's eyes.

"Is it already an empty shell…"

Han Xiao took out a suction plate shaped device and placed it on EsGod. This was a device used to detect the state of one's soul.

Although Mechanics were not experts in the soul territory, at his level, building a device to only detect if the target had a soul was not a problem.

As the suction plate was just about to touch EsGod's body, the next moment, Han Xiao suddenly felt a resistance force at his wrist as if someone suddenly grabbed his wrist tightly. His hand stopped moving abruptly.

Han Xiao immediately looked up at EsGod's eyes that had color once again.

At the same time, a deep mind message entered Han Xiao's mind.

"Like I said, we'd meet again sooner or later…"

Chapter 1222: Deception Is the Way of Wars

"Like I said, we'd meet again sooner or later… Only, I didn't expect it to come this soon."

EsGod's tone was filled with mockery.

Han Xiao's pupils constricted.

This body isn't an empty shell‽

His first thought was that he got Gaud's identity wrong and set EsGod free for nothing.

However, when he heard what EsGod said, his eyes gleamed, and he asked, "Why were you so sure I'd definitely let you out?"

"Oh? You're not letting me out to seek help from me?" EsGod's brows raised. "You didn't station so many soldiers here just to open the amber and see if I'm dead yet, did you?"

Seek help? Right, this b*stard knows about the World Tree Civilization and left the wormhole data behind. He might think that when the advanced civilizations discover the World Tree Civilization, they'll most likely let him out to ask him for information. Is that why he said that we'd meet again sooner or later?

The Spacetime Amber froze everything except the soul that was also trapped inside the body. EsGod knew absolutely nothing about the outside world in the past decades. His impression of the universe was still the same as when he got captured.

The mind conversation happened in the split of a second. The movements of the two of them did not stop during it.

Hu!

EsGod backed away instantly and was about to teleport right away, only to realize that the spacetime of the area around him was stabilized and he could not teleport. He quickly analyzed the strength of the encirclement he was in and came to the conclusion that he would not be able to break through it using ordinary methods. Hence, he quickly thought of other ways to escape and started to use his Dimension Crack ability to fill this area. As long as he could create just a tiny crack, he would be able to escape with teleportation.

Although he did not know why the dynasty let him out, to him, escaping was his top priority.

Han Xiao acted immediately. He led the dozens of Apostle Weapons and many mechanical soldiers forward to surround EsGod. It did not matter what was going on with EsGod. As long as this body was not an empty shell, he had to seal it up once again.

The dynasty fleet around started attacking. All kinds of control-type weapons were also launched continuously. Dark-red energy filled the space.

The battle erupted in an instant!

EsGod was submerged in countless attacks in the blink of an eye.

"Back then, it took eleven Beyond Grade As to finally catch me. Black Star, you're alone now. How are you going to capture me?"

EsGod's mocking voice appeared in Han Xiao's head. Despite being heavily surrounded, he did not panic at all.

After he evolved, the load on his genetic chain had drastically decreased. His strength was undoubtedly at the top tier in the universe. Although he had just come out of the Spacetime Amber, his soul was in a weakened state and had no time to prepare dozens of Beyond Grade A level doppelgangers, he still had the health-energy conversion ability.

Using [Esper Ability—Black Hole], EsGod could convert the attacks he received into his own energy, then use his regeneration Esper Ability to heal at a rapid rate. The enhanced ability to convert energy into health that Han Xiao had was obtained from EsGod too.

If EsGod had time to prepare dozens of doppelgangers in advance, he would probably have been able to single-handedly deal with the Stars Alliance world that Han Xiao had once experienced. Currently, most peak Beyond Grade As were no match for EsGod. Plus, with the many slippery space related Esper Abilities he had, he was basically undefeatable.

If not because Han Xiao landed the Esper Silence ability on him back then, causing all his Esper Abilities to stop functioning and all his doppelgangers to perish, even eleven Beyond Grade As would not have been able to capture him.

Luckily, this time, Han Xiao and the dynasty had set up in advance. EsGod's escaping abilities were rendered useless. With his most troublesome ability gone, his threat level reduced dramatically. Otherwise, he would have been able to escape anytime he wanted.

However, this did not mean that EsGod would certainly never be able to escape. Although the dynasty had used all kinds of advanced spacetime stabilization devices, if they took too long to trap EsGod again, he might still find the chance to 'dig a hole' and escape.

"You'll find out how. I'm no longer the same as before. I don't need help to deal with you."

Han Xiao chose some of the mechanical soldiers and assembled them. As electronic light flickered, the Mechanical Deity appeared and instantly chased after EsGod, slashing and smashing down at him, dragging a trail of electric sparks behind.

Although EsGod had many abilities, he could not use too many of them simultaneously. He solved this problem by using doppelgangers, giving them some of his Esper Abilities. The more doppelgangers that existed at the same time, the more abilities he could use.

As creating doppelgangers required large amounts of energy and he could absorb energy in battle, as the battle went on, the number of doppelgangers would increase. EsGod was also someone who would become stronger the longer the battle went on.

However, EsGod did not prepare any doppelgangers in advance this time. Although he could create them slowly during the battle, Han Xiao's Apostle Weapons were not for decoration. As soon as he created one doppelganger, it would be murdered by the many Apostle Weapons. The number of doppelgangers he had could not increase at all.

Therefore, the current situation was very clear. All factors present had placed EsGod at an extreme disadvantage. All he could do was get beat up.

Despite being able to convert between energy and health, the rate was much slower than Han Xiao. [Esper Ability—Black Hole] had a limit and could not block all damage, and the speed of his regeneration also had a limit. The damage Han Xiao was now able to dish out was on a completely different level to before. Plus, the dynasty fleet also provided support on the side. EsGod's health was decreasing faster than he was regenerating.

After several decades, the level difference between Han Xiao and EsGod became much smaller. He opened the interface, looked at the combat information, and saw more of EsGod's information than before.

He quickly scanned through but did not see [Esper Ability—Rebirth] in EsGod's ability list. He wondered if it was one of the few question marks he still could not see.

However, in EsGod's status bar, Han Xiao discovered something abnormal.

You are in the [Intermediate Weakened Soul] state. Your Psychological Resistance is decreased by 30%. Your INT and MYS attributes are decreased by 15%. Duration: Unknown.

You are in the [Torn Soul] state. You have lost a large portion of INT and MYS attributes. Your Psychological Resistance is decreased by 60%. Duration: Permanent.

"This is…" Han Xiao narrowed his eyes.

Weakened Soul should be the side effect of being imprisoned by the Spacetime Amber, which EsGod could recover from. However, the [Torn Soul] state clearly had nothing to do with the Spacetime Amber, and it just happened to match Gaud's abnormally high attributes.

So, I didn't guess wrong. EsGod is indeed related to Gaud.

The possibility of Gaud being a doppelganger that EsGod had created could be limited, as all his Esper Abilities were useless once he got affected by Esper Silence. Gaud had to have nothing to do with EsGod's abilities to still exist. At the moment of EsGod's capture, he did not have a chance to create doppelgangers. All he could do was soul-related things in that short period of time.

Therefore, EsGod did not just simply shift his soul but unflinchingly used some kind of Esper Ability to tear his own soul apart and fuse it into Gaud's body, leaving the remaining soul in his original body.

The Spacetime Amber froze everything, so there was no way EsGod could control Gaud from inside. Being in the outside world for so many years, it should be EsGod's main consciousness inside Gaud.

At this point of time, the various detection devices of the dynasty fleet did not discover any odd soul ripples, meaning that this 'EsGod' was also not remotely controlled.

Therefore, the two souls were now completely separated into two independent individuals.

This meant that this 'EsGod' before him might not be the EsGod he knew but instead a new personality, a new consciousness that birthed from the remaining soul and memories of EsGod, like a clone. As for the main consciousness of EsGod, it was actually in Gaud… or was it the other way around?

If this was the case, EsGod was still EsGod, and Gaud would still be Gaud. Even though their personalities and memories were hardly different, they were two different people… Could this be what the word 'rebirth' in [Esper Ability—Rebirth] meant‽

His original body is a Beyond Grade A, and Gaud also became a Beyond Grade A. This b*stard split into two different Beyond Grade A individuals… If his main consciousness is in Gaud, then he's really completely merciless toward himself.

All kinds of thoughts flashed past Han Xiao's mind.

If the two souls were still linked and shared memories, it would be a conspicuous flaw. Judging from EsGod's personality, if he made up his mind to wipe his ledger clean, he would not have made such a mistake. Therefore, he most likely completely cut off the connection of the two souls.

Not only did he abandon his old body, but he even did not mind creating another 'him' in the universe, giving all the strength he had accumulated in the past to 'someone else'.

If this was really the case, any memories related to Gaud that this 'EsGod' had were probably all deleted by EsGod's main consciousness when his soul split. That way, if the dynasty dissected this 'EsGod' in the future, they would not find anything in the memories.

This was why he was given the name 'God of Espers'. No one but him could ever do something this crazy.

While making all kinds of speculation in his mind, Han Xiao's attacks did not stop. The battle carried on fiercely.

The situation was completely one-sided. EsGod was bathing in psionic energy. His flesh was melting and regenerating countless times every second. Under the nonstop attacks, he could hardly move at all and was in a completely defensive stance. He did not dare stop regenerating health for even a second.

The way he regenerated was through accelerating the division of his cells. Every time his body regenerated, the vitality of his cells would increase, and his life span would decrease. If not because the Evolution Cube had given him a boost in the past, he would not have been able to endure such a highly intense battle.

Feeling Han Xiao's powerful attacks, EsGod was shocked too.

He remembered that when he was locked up, Black Star was not even a peak Beyond Grade A yet. However, with the strength Han Xiao was now displaying, even EsGod could not confidently say he would be able to defeat him. Even if he was at his peak strength, if they fought in a fair duel, he felt it would most likely end up in a tie.

Only how many years have passed, and Black Star is already catching up to my level, even looking like he's about to surpass me‽

"Your growth is really unbelievable! I've never seen anyone as talented as you!" EsGod honestly marveled from the bottom of his heart.

"Don't think I'll attack you one less time because you complimented me."

Han Xiao continued attacking with an expressionless face. Among all the classes, he now had the easiest time fighting Espers. He gained bonus attributes and increased damage when fighting Espers.

Also, the [Elderly Killer] ability was great against an elderly like EsGod…

Though the evolved EsGod was strong, Han Xiao was not any bit weaker!

Rounds of attacks landed on EsGod continuously. Explosions appeared everywhere EsGod passed by like a snake made of flames.

After continuing to attack for some time, as Han Xiao estimated that the bonuses of his various talents had reached the maximum, Mechanical Force erupted from his body.

Ka la ka la…

The armor at the Mechanical Deity's forehead suddenly opened up. A pile of mechanical parts extended out, turning into an exquisite mechanical crown that landed on the Mechanical Deity's head.

The next moment, an invisible shockwave erupted from the crown, concentrated into a beam, and hit EsGod.

EsGod's entire body trembled. It was like a huge hammer heavily bashed his consciousness.

This was the Universal Treasure Grade equipment Han Xiao learned from Jayz's technology treasure, a Mechanical Deity exclusive weapon—[Soul Breaking Crown]!

Its name sounded like a magic item, but it was actually a piece of machinery. It worked by obtaining soul energy from breaking down psionic energy. The Soul Breaking Crown could provide an extremely high amount of Psychological Resistance for the user of the Mechanical Deity while at the same time being able to launch mental attacks.

Usually, Mechanics' weaknesses were their original body and their mind, they also tremendously lacked mind attack means. The effect of this Gold equipment could make up for that weakness to a certain extent… Although Han Xiao was no ordinary Mechanic, the Soul Breaking Crown was still useful to him.

The debuffs on EsGod made his mind his biggest weakness. Han Xiao was used to targeting the enemy's weak points, so of course, he was not going to let this kind of opportunity slip.

Before EsGod could recover, Han Xiao instantly activated Virtual Soul, easily dragged EsGod's soul into the virtual world, and gave him a beating.

Having his vital spot being attacked continuously, EsGod received tons of damage.

While EsGod was still stunned, Han Xiao's original body left the Mechanical Deity, grabbed EsGod's neck, activated the Spacetime Amber and started to create a seal instantly.

EsGod regained focus very quickly and was about to resist. Seeing this, Han Xiao pressed him into his wide chest and said, "Don't move. Do you remember how I caught you the last time? If you do it again, you won't just be spending the rest of your life in prison; you'll die!"

Hearing this, EsGod's movement paused for a moment as he instantly recalled the trauma of getting hit by Esper Silence back then.

He knew nothing about Character Summon Cards, nor did he know why Black Star could use this ability, so he could not help but think Black Star still had this ability.

"Compared to an endless sentence, why shouldn't I fight till my last moment?" EsGod's eyes narrowed.

He was in a situation that was more than enough to threaten his life. Through the fight earlier, EsGod knew very well that there was absolutely no chance he could escape. If Black Star used Esper Silence, he might really die.

"Are you sure you want to die?" Han Xiao whispered. "Don't you want to see the day the World Tree advents?"

EsGod's body suddenly froze, and shock finally appeared on his face.

He had always thought that he was the only person in the entire universe that knew about this. Never did he expect to hear it from Han Xiao.

When did Black Star find out‽

"That data… have you guys already completed studying it‽"

EsGod's eyes gleamed.

Han Xiao, however, did not reply. He deliberately said in a meaningful tone, "Stop resisting, and you'll still have a chance to be set free to witness it all. If you die here, there'll be no more hope."

"…" EsGod's expression changed rapidly. He was caught in a dilemma.

However, it only took a few seconds for him to understand the situation he was in. His body became relaxed, and he had stopped resisting.

He looked up right into Han Xiao's eyes and said slowly, "I don't trust that you'll let me out… but I'm willing to make the bet. After all, I don't have anything more to lose.

"This is the second time I've lost to you. Maybe you really can step into that level and witness the scenery there for me…"

At this time, Han Xiao took a step back without saying anything. The prison was complete.

EsGod's body was fixed. He was locked in the Spacetime Amber once again.

The only difference was that he was in a different position.

Seeing this, Han Xiao finally let out a long breath. He shook his head.

"If you continued to resist, I really might not have been able to capture you… Sorry, deception is the way of wars."

Chapter 1223: Choice

Han Xiao speculated what EsGod would think. EsGod's first reaction would not be to think that he knew about this long ago but that the dynasty's research on that wormhole data had come to a result. Hence, he would suddenly have a little bit of hope. In such a desperate situation, there was a very high chance he would give up resisting. From the results, Han Xiao won the bet.

Deception was a way of the war; conquering the enemy's mind was the smarter strategy. If not because he used this to successfully intimidate EsGod, he would have spent much more time capturing him, and there would have been a lot of uncertainties.

"Speaking of which, this is this b*stard's second time going in…"

Han Xiao looked at EsGod, who was in the amber, and sighed.

Ignoring all other factors, EsGod was really a very pure person. In order to reach his goal, he was willing to do anything in the world. As long as one did not get in his way, he would not do anything, and vice versa.

While he was looking at EsGod, the dynasty fleet around instantly stopped attacking upon seeing that the mission was complete and retracted their weapons.

Tons of parts of mechanical soldiers floated in the battlefield. Some were even destroyed by the attacks of the dynasty fleet. In order to dish out as much damage as possible to EsGod, they could not be concerned with causing damage to their ally. Even Han Xiao was confused as to whether these teammates of his were attacking EsGod or him.

He deactivated the Mechanical Deity. Mechanical Force shot out from his hands and turned into electrical chains, linked onto the shattered parts, and assembling them back into mechanical soldiers using Advanced Machinery Construction.

This time, the fleet commander heaved a sigh of relief in the communication channel and said, "Luckily, we set up enough traps in advance and had the edge. If not, we wouldn't have been able to capture him again while paying such a small price… Alright, please give EsGod to us. We'll find a place to lock him up."

His tone was formal.

As Black Star was the one who requested to release EsGod to check on him, capturing him again was not considered a contribution, but letting him get free would have been a huge demerit. Therefore, this was a mission that required a lot of effort but gave no merits, so the fleet commander did not feel appreciative toward Han Xiao.

Capturing EsGod this time looked easy, but that was because they had too big an edge. EsGod was immobile before, which was why they could set up an encirclement any way they wanted, letting EsGod, who was in a weakened state, out after being fully prepared. If EsGod was free in the beginning, there was no way he would have been surrounded by this many traps.

A few dynasty spaceships came to take the prisoner away. Han Xiao stood in place for a while as he watched them bring EsGod away. Only then did the dynasty fleet turn off all the spacetime stabilization devices.

He curled his lips, opened the dimension factory, and stuffed his mechanical army into it for repairs. After rejecting the invitation of boarding the ships, he took out a King mechanical army and disappeared.

The next moment, he appeared in a machinery factory that was no longer in the Constellation Corridor. He crossed multiple Star Fields directly and arrived in Black Star Palace that was in the Flickering World instantly, using the 'Throne' in his private workshop.

Beep beep beep!

At this time, the communicator rang timely. Han Xiao took it out, and as he expected, it was a call from Urranrell.

As she used her ruler rights to approve Han Xiao's request to open EsGod's seal to check his status, she had been paying attention to the live broadcast the whole time, so she called right after it ended.

"Black Star, I've seen the process. Looks like your worries did not come true."

Urranrell nodded.

"…Maybe." Han Xiao shook his head.

EsGod's body was still very much alive and not an empty shell, so in the dynasty's eyes, this was undoubtedly his original body, and their doubts were cleared.

Although he had confirmed EsGod and Gaud's relationship through this, he could not use the information from the interface to convince the dynasty.

Although EsGod showed signs of his soul being torn, the difficulty of verifying that was way too high.

First of all, EsGod would certainly resist and not possibly obediently accept the check. Plus, they could not check on EsGod when he was locked inside the Spacetime Amber.

Secondly, EsGod's level was too high. Only an extremely few peak Beyond Grade As in the universe who were experts in the soul territory could investigate his soul fully, which would also require EsGod to not put up a fight. This was like the difference between using one's ability to attack and using it to cure a sickness; the latter required much more precision.

Thirdly, on the surface, the effects of having a weakened soul and torn soul coincided. It would be extremely difficult to differentiate them. Both could be seen as the side effects of being locked up by the Spacetime Amber.

Even if all of those difficulties were overcome and EsGod's soul was proven to be in a torn state, there was no way he could prove the connection between EsGod and Gaud to the dynasty. The evidence was too weak.

Considering all the factors, Han Xiao felt that there was close to no way he could find any solid proof on this matter.

Urranrell did not have many doubts and said, "Being worried is a good thing. At least what you did got rid of a possible problem for the dynasty, and now we can safely lock EsGod up without having to worry. Plus, you captured EsGod again without paying much of a price. You didn't disappoint me."

She did not feel what Han Xiao did was completely unnecessary. She was the one who gave the order, and Black Star executed it only after she approved it. Now that the matter was settled, it was not a bad thing but a good thing. From her perspective, this operation was a form of reassurance.

"I guess…"

Han Xiao was not in the mood to say much. He casually chatted for a while and went offline afterward. He looked somewhat upset.

Urranrell had already done a lot for him. There was absolutely no merit in this operation. Instead, she had to bear the risk of letting EsGod escape and the responsibility of approving the operation that caused it. At the end of her term, she definitely had to focus on keeping a low profile and making sure everything was going on smoothly. Willingly approving his proposal was already a sign of her strong trust in him; he could not ask her to do more.

If EsGod… no, Gaud wanted to completely wipe his history clean, he most certainly did everything the dynasty asked him to do and nothing else while he was weak, not showing any signs of his ulterior motives. Han Xiao was not able to find any solid evidence this time, so he could not accuse Gaud of anything.

Without solid evidence, the dynasty had no reason to believe in his accusations and test the loyalty of a direct Beyond Grade A member out of nowhere. Therefore, this method was definitely not going to work.

If Gaud really decided to take the lawful path, even if he found evidence, as long as it was not completely definitive, the dynasty might not even want to recognize it so that they could avoid losing a direct Beyond Grade A member with infinite potential. This was not completely impossible.

I'll have to make other plans. Since there's no way to convince the dynasty to investigate Gaud thoroughly, I can only do it myself…

Han Xiao frowned and pondered.

If he was to attack Gaud secretly and it was discovered, he would undoubtedly be in astronomical trouble.

Even if he did it secretly enough, the dynasty would also put in a tremendous amount of effort to search for the culprit. Due to the organizational nature of the Beyond Grade A Association, it would certainly become a key target for the dynasty's investigation, which would also cause an enormous storm. It might even become the fuse of a new Tragedy of the Pinnacles.

Han Xiao had to admit that the method Gaud used to wipe his history clean was impeccable. He became a direct member of one of the three Universal Civilizations, acquiring super powerful protection. If something happened to him, more Beyond Grade As might be dragged down with him.

However, if he was left alone, the entire explored universe would be in danger. He was a colossal hidden threat. This was especially true because this b*stard already got into the insides of the dynasty. God only knew what storm he would stir up. He might even end up being the usher for the World Tree Civilization.

Furthermore, Gaud's Esper Ability had way too much potential. He was still considered easy to deal with now that he had only just entered the Beyond Grade A territory, but as he grew stronger, he would rapidly become tougher to deal with.

"What a dilemma…" Han Xiao rubbed his nose and was a little troubled.

Sometimes, there was no perfect solution, and a decision had to be made between two bad choices.

His thoughts fought internally for a while, and he finally made up his mind.

I must get rid of this time bomb as early as possible before he grows too strong. If I wait for him to show any flaws, it'll be too late!

Han Xiao clenched his teeth.

He started to brainstorm quickly, analyzing the possible consequences while coming up with all kinds of wicked plans.

The best method is to not let Gaud disappear out of nowhere but give a target the dynasty can vent its anger toward. With a direct target, no one else will be dragged down. Hence, not only do I have to avoid being suspected, but I must think of a way to frame it on someone else. I'll also have to consider what different impacts framing different people will cause…

Han Xiao's thoughts quickly spun, and he very soon had a rough plan.

Putting aside the differences between the detailed plans, there were only two choices in terms of execution. One was to do it himself secretly and find a way to frame it on someone else afterward. Another was to find a way to create a situation to lure others to attack Gaud so that he would not be suspected.

Not mentioning the former, the key factor of the latter was 'lure'. It was best for him not to be involved in any way, so calling his friends to murder Gaud was not doable.

For example, the Holy Accord organization had more than enough strength to kill Gaud, but Han Xiao could not possibly ask them to do it. This was the equivalent of handing his vulnerability right into their hands. The revived Primordial Ones all had their own philosophy and were not united, nor were they his subordinates. He could not ensure they would not leak this secret in the future… Plus, whether they would be willing to help or not was another matter.

The more people who knew about it, the higher the risk, no matter who he asked to help do it.

"No matter which path I take, I'll have to muddy the waters first…"

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

The Beyond Grade A Association headquarters on Planet Finn were visited by a dynasty fleet.

Gaud walked out of the hatch. The dynasty's senior officer uniform reflected the light of the artificial sun like it was shining.

"Welcome to Planet Finn, Your Excellency Gaud."

A receptionist who was wearing the association's uniform instantly approached with an enthusiastic smile.

The news of the dynasty acquiring a new direct Beyond Grade A member had already spread out among the high-class circle, but it was only limited to the name Gaud and nothing else. The dynasty did not publicize too much information; they even controlled the flow of any information regarding Gaud. Therefore, many organizations were guessing Gaud's way of doing things and his specific abilities… This was the normal treatment for a new Beyond Grade A.

Gaud handed over the request to join the association with all the documents needed. The Beyond Grade A Association hosted a meeting just to welcome this new member. The staff was arranged long ago to wait for Gaud there.

"Lead the way." Gaud's tone was casual.

The two of them left the dock, boarded an anti-gravity carrier, and headed toward the spherical conference room at the top of the headquarters building in the middle of the city.

Looking down from the sky, the ground was filled with closely packed buildings. It was a highly advanced galactic city. The receptionist pointed out some of Planet Finn's hotspots on the way like a tour guide. Gaud did not stop him. He looked down and silently observed the streets that passed by.

The various Beyond Grade A organizations had all set up their agencies there. In the last decade, Planet Finn had already become a prosperous galactic city. Flying carriers dashing across the sky formed the transport network.

Base level personnel in uniforms of different organizations could be seen everywhere on the streets. Gaud even saw quite a number of base-level office workers of the Black Star Army.

However, these organizations were just stationed there. The association's staff were the ones who were responsible for managing this planet.

The carrier arrived at the platform outside the conference room very soon. Gaud followed the receptionist into his personal lounge. As he was the focus of today's meeting and he had come with his original body, he had to wait for someone to notify him to enter the venue from another door.

After watching the receptionist leave and shut the door, Gaud casually picked up the snacks on the table and started chewing. He sized up the marvelous lounge, and his eyes were filled with enjoyment.

"The Beyond Grade As have been split up for so many years, only finally showing signs of unity in recent years. Black Star, Manison, and Kasuyi have done a really good job. Sadly, I did not wait for such a good time to arrive in the past… However, they probably wouldn't dare take in the most vicious criminal in the universe anyway. If I didn't change my identity, all of this would have nothing to do with me."

Gaud could not help but sneer.

After gangs earned enough money, they would all consider wiping their history clean and turn to legal businesses. It was the same for him. Committing crimes was not his goal, just a path he took to accumulate enough strength.

After getting rid of his past identity, he could now start a new life.

A while later, someone finally came to notify him to enter the venue.

Gaud stood up, patted his clothes, walked down the corridor all the way to the end, and pushed open the tall, exquisite gate. Light shone from within and entered his eyes.

A huge, round table conference room entered his sights. The remote projections of all the Beyond Grade A members were sitting in their own seats. They turned to face him simultaneously. Their eyes all focused on Gaud with all kinds of different emotions.

Gaud became the focal point of the entire venue. He looked around at the familiar faces and uncontrollably dazed off for a moment.

This was the first time he had appeared in front of most of the Beyond Grade As in the universe with his new identity. Looks of hatred, hostility, and fear were no longer anywhere to be found. The hate and conflict of the past was all gone; his relationship with every one of them was completely new.

Being reborn had never felt so refreshing.

At this time, Manison, who sat in the main seat, nodded and said, "This friend here is Gaud. On behalf of all the members of the Beyond Grade A Development Union, I welcome you to the association."

"It's my honor to join the association." Gaud regained focus. A smile with unknown meaning appeared on his face as he placed his hand on his chest and did a universal greeting gesture.

Clotti, who had always been quiet, pointed at the empty seat beside and said, "You're a direct member of the dynasty. I've saved a seat for you. Come here and sit."

Seeing this, Gaud smiled, walked over, and sat beside Clotti. The entire row beside him was the seats for the direct members of the dynasty. It was like he had found his clique.

However, as soon as he sat down, a voice filled with a strong sense of curiosity sounded.

The content of what that person said made Gaud's calm heart skip a beat.

"Gaud, right? I heard your ability is the Super High Risk Esper Ability that only exists in theory, Energy Control! Is that true?"

Chapter 1224: Muddy the Waters

As soon as this was said, the atmosphere in the conference room changed immediately. Everyone looked toward the source of the voice and saw that the person who asked the question was a neutral Beyond Grade A called Lucie, nicknamed 'Ancient Snake'. He was a shapeshift-type Esper who occasionally worked as a mercenary for advanced civilizations. He also frequented the black market.

Gaud stared at him feeling shocked inside.

He had only ever used his ability a few times. He had only fought a little bit decades ago during the Kunde Race war and never sparred with anyone after becoming a Beyond Grade A. Only a few people in the dynasty should have known about his exact abilities. This information was tightly controlled and had yet to spread. He did not expect someone to find out his ability on his first day after joining the association…

Where did the information get leaked?

Gaud did not respond, so someone asked curiously, "Lucie, where did you get that information?"

"The black market, of course. I heard it coincidentally," Lucie casually said.

"Is it reliable?" someone else asked.

"How would I know? I'm trying to find out now, aren't I? Did none of you hear anything similar at all?" Lucie questioned.

Secret Master frowned and slowly said, "My subordinates acquired similar information too, but there's no solid proof. There are hundreds of speculations like this on the black market. God knows who they came from. Most of them are random guesses anyway."

Seeing this, a few more frequents of the black market also expressed their agreement, saying that they had all heard similar things, but none took it seriously.

Han Xiao watched from the side and heaved a sigh of relief in his mind.

He was indeed the one who anonymously placed the information about Gaud's ability into the black market. With his Virtual Technology skills, he left no traces behind at all. From others' perspective, this rumor looked like it appeared out of thin air and spread so quickly that no one could find the root of it. This kind of thing happened every day on the network.

The black-market network was a magical place. Countless information trades were carried on here every day. There was a lot of false information, but secrets would also appear occasionally. Sometimes, even the advanced civilizations had no idea how their secrets were leaked.

For example, a Super High Risk Esper Ability that only existed in theory attracted enough attention and spread very rapidly. Currently, all the organizations were using their own intelligence channels to search for information related to Gaud. Therefore, for someone like Secret Master, who frequented the black market, there was a high chance he would discover it.

However, there were way too many speculations and no solid proof. These guys would not ask Gaud directly just because of these rumors. Therefore, Han Xiao selected a few targets to specifically leak this information to, luring these guys to bring up this topic when everyone was present. Lucie was one of them.

He did not select these targets randomly. Others thought Lucie was a neutral Beyond Grade A, but the truth was that his identity was exposed in the later versions in his previous life as a secret member of a Super Star Cluster civilization just like Traveler. Han Xiao knew all about who he was.

Due to the sensitive competitive relationship between the three Universal Civilizations, Han Xiao had some confidence that he could lure the secret members of the Super Star Cluster civilizations in the association to deliberately stir things up. Even if that failed, he had backup plans.

The crowd discussed the rumours for a while before turning to look at Gaud with strong curiosity in their eyes.

"What's your real ability?"

Looking at everyone's curious expression, Gaud exhaled and slowly said, "Do any of you have a habit of announcing your secrets? Well, I don't. You don't have to be so curious. You'll find out in the future."

Lucie curled his lips and continued to question him. "We're all association members. What's so secretive about it? You've joined the association, but you won't share any information with us. That's not sincere at all. It's unfair to us. Or is your ability really Energy Control?"

Hearing this, many people nodded in agreement.

In the Beyond Grade A circle, rookies were all treated this way. Everyone wanted to know about the rookie's secrets and abilities so that if they had to fight the rookie, they would not be surprised by unknown abilities. Most Beyond Grade As had already walked down the same path.

Gaud's eyelids twitched.

He totally understood that Lucie was basically a sh*t stirrer who wanted to force him to share his secrets.

"Don't bother asking anymore. I won't answer you."

Gaud shook his head and did not deny it but avoided the question.

Keeping his ability a secret was only temporary, not permanent. Once he grew to a certain stage, the dynasty would no longer keep it a secret and would instead promote the fact that he was the first person ever in history to possess this Esper Ability to intimidate the Beyond Grade As of other civilizations.

Therefore, dynasty's current demand of him was only not to directly answer any question about his ability but not lie about it, or the promotion they did in the future would not be as effective.

Furthermore, denying his own ability was not something someone as strong as him should do. It was bad for his reputation. If he damaged his image among the Beyond Grade As, making up for it would be much more troublesome than simply not answering and avoiding the questions.

"So, you're not going to give us face?" Lucie narrowed his eyes. "Our real bodies aren't here, otherwise all we'd have to do is spar with you, and your ability would no longer be a secret. Why are you being so secretive about it? Looks like the rumors are not complete nonsense. Your ability is probably really Energy Control. Even if it isn't, it's definitely very special. That's why you're keeping it a secret."

"Think whatever you want." Gaud did not want to argue with him anymore and looked away.

Seeing this, many people's eyes flickered with some suspicion.

From the way they saw it, by not giving a direct answer, Gaud having the Energy Control Esper Ability seemed more trustworthy. If this was not his ability, he could have just denied it.

If Gaud really did have this overpowered Super High Risk Esper Ability…

Having thought of this, many people had all kinds of ideas.

This time, Han Xiao who had been watching smiled and said, "Alright, alright, if Gaud doesn't want to say it, don't force him. Today, we're welcoming him as a new member after all. Don't make the atmosphere so uptight."

The best result would have been for Gaud to admit what his ability was, but there was nothing Han Xiao could do if Gaud was not willing to answer no matter what. However, this was within Han Xiao's expectations too. As long as he spread the information of Gaud possibly having the 'Energy Control' ability to all the Beyond Grade As present, he would have achieved more than half of his goal regardless of whether Gaud admitted it or not.

Hearing that the vice president had spoken, the others moved on from this topic, and the atmosphere became tranquil again.

Gaud glanced at Han Xiao and saw that Han Xiao nodded at him. He responded with a smile and sighed in his mind.

He had never enjoyed the feeling of being helped; he was always the shared enemy of everyone. At this point, he had to admit that having someone speak for him really felt quite good.

The meeting was casual and relaxed. The main goal of it was to welcome the rookie while helping him to understand the purpose, principle, and the rules of the association, or help him to solve some problems. For example, they could provide support in helping him to grow his forces, lend him resources, assist in battles, and so on. However, since Gaud was a direct member of the dynasty, he did not need help in terms of resources.

The people chatted casually, pulled Gaud around, and asked him questions. The people on the dynasty's side were the more active ones; the other people only occasionally said a few words.

As they were having a good time chatting, Han Xiao glanced at Manison, chuckled, and said casually, "Gaud, you've just joined the association and don't know about many things, so I must remind you. You have to be careful of our dear Mechanic Emperor. He's very interested in new and young members."

"Oh? Why?"

Gaud turned and saw that Manison's expression was calm, as if he was used to it.

Sun Hunter, who was on the side, laughed out loud and said, "Haha, Black Star is right. Manison has been insisting on not giving up the Felon technology. If you really have a Super High Risk Esper Ability, you must be careful. He might be interested in your fragile body and turn you into his puppet."

"Humph, ridiculous."

Manison closed his eyes and ignored them.

Seeing this, everyone burst into laughter. The room was filled with joy.

Black Star messing with the Mechanic Emperor was already a routine part of the meetings. Hearing Han Xiao say that, everyone only felt it was usual. They were used to it and did not suspect anything.

As time was scarce for everyone present, the welcome meeting ended very quickly. The people went offline one after another. Gaud stood up and returned to the dynasty fleet as well.

As soon as he returned to the room, Gaud received a communication request from the dynasty upper echelons that began with a question right away.

"We've heard about what happened during the Beyond Grade A Association meeting. You didn't tell anyone your ability, did you?"

"Nope." Gaud shook his head.

He was not surprised about how quickly the dynasty got the news. After all, there were many direct members of the dynasty in the association, so they were all sources of information for the dynasty.

"Good. We'll investigate where the information got leaked. To think that your ability was so accurately exposed, there's definitely something going on… The contents of today's meeting will certainly pass on to the federation, the church, and some Super Star Cluster civilizations. They might be suspicious about your ability because of it. Come back as soon as possible. The Flickering World is too dangerous."

"You're saying that someone might try to kill me?" Gaud raised his brows.

"I don't know about that. Times are different now than before. Because of the Beyond Grade A Association, as long as the rules are not broken, this kind of thing will most likely not happen… but it's still better to be cautious."

"Alright then," Gaud casually replied and hung up the communication.

He did not feel any organization would attack him. The Flickering World was still in war now. The federation and the church would not attack their allies, and the Super Star Cluster civilization would not dare dispatch Beyond Grade As too due to fear of the three Universal Civilizations also sending their direct members into the war. Plus, the Beyond Grade A Association was another layer of insurance for him. He felt he was in a very safe situation.

Unlike the past, the association Black Star and the others founded became a privilege for all Beyond Grade As.

In the past, when Black Star did a lot of things, he got targeted and attacked by the federation and the church all the time. Now, however, the association guaranteed the safety of the Beyond Grade As, so this kind of situation would most likely not happen again.

Gaud benefited from it as well. Furthermore, his identity as a direct member of the dynasty was another layer of protection. He did not think anyone would have any motive to want to kill him—the risk of it far exceeded the reward.

"Now is such a good era for the Beyond Grade As…"

Gaud sighed and ordered the fleet to depart.

Dynasty spaceships took off one after another, entered outer space, and headed in the direction to leave the Flickering World.

At the same time, the content of the meeting got passed into different organizations by the various Beyond Grade As.

…

On the Federation of Light's mother planet…

"An Esper who possibly possesses the Energy Control Esper Ability that only exists in theory?"

As the federation's president, Bader, browsed the report sent by the direct Beyond Grade As, his expression changed slightly.

The chief doyen on the side tapped his cane and said with a deep voice, "This is just a guess. It might not be true, and it's too early to take it seriously."

"It's a discovery at least," Bader said. "This new Beyond Grade A of the dynasty is so secretive about everything. It doesn't matter if his Esper Ability is Energy Control or not. He's definitely not ordinary… They say the information got leaked from the black market. Tell the intelligence department to collect related information from the black market network and see if they can verify it.

"If this is true, the dynasty really got lucky. If they acquired such a Super with infinite potential, he will most certainly replace Clotti and become the National Pillar in the future… They already have Black Star, and now they have Gaud too. In terms of individual strength, the dynasty will be able to maintain an edge for hundreds of years. Sigh."

The chief doyen frowned. "You're not going to do anything, are you? It will cost us much more than it'll benefit us."

"Don't worry. One Beyond Grade A isn't important. I won't destroy the great situation we're in now just for such a trivial matter. The church will probably make the same decision too." Bader waved and suddenly said, "But as for others… I don't know."

"Don't think too much." The chief doyen shook his head. "Times are different. Nothing will happen."

Bader thought about it and nodded. "Hmm, you're right. No one will do it, unless they're an idiot."

Chapter 1225: Speculation and Attack

On the other hand, the contents of the Beyond Grade A meeting also got passed on to the various Super Star Cluster civilizations.

On the Star Arc Civilization's mother planet…

"An Energy Control Esper… this kind of rumor would not appear out of nowhere. Investigate the reliability of this information as soon as possible!"

The Star Arc Civilization was severely worried.

In the past few decades, the growth of the Crimson Dynasty had been way too rapid and smooth. It could be considered their golden era. Not a single advanced civilization was not jealous.

The dynasty already had people like Dark Lord and Black Star, and now Gaud, whose potential might be infinite, had appeared, not to mention he was even a direct member of the dynasty. This news was undoubtedly a nightmare for the Super Star Cluster civilizations. With every new talent the three Universal Civilizations acquired, the Super Star Cluster Alliance faced more pressure in the individual strength territory.

Back when Traveler got publicly executed by the dynasty, although their good brother Modo took the blame for it for some reason, it was impossible for the Star Arc Civilization leader not to be furious watching their own loyal member getting his execution broadcast live by the dynasty. He had only held back and did not do anything because the big picture was more important.

If he could eliminate Gaud and erase the dynasty's future National Pillar in advance, it would be like avenging Traveler and making the dynasty pay for what they did…

The Star Arc Civilization leader's expression shifted rapidly. In the end, he sighed and suppressed his impulses.

"Forget it. The state of the Flickering War is not positive at all. Our allies are getting defeated time and again. We're already in a difficult enough situation, forcing them to send Beyond Grade As into the war too isn't a wise choice. There's no room for risk-taking in the current situation…"

Currently, no Beyond Grade A was part of the Flickering War. The three Universal Civilizations promising not to dispatch any direct Beyond Grade As was one of the very few great things for the Super Star Cluster Alliance. Once they broke the rule and made the three Universal Civilizations send in Beyond Grade As, the situation would become much worse for them than it already was.

The Flickering War was the hope for the Super Star Cluster Alliance to turn their situation around. Between a Beyond Grade A and the overall strategy of the entire civilization, of course, he knew which was more important.

The three Universal Civilizations had control over the resources of the explored universe. The strong became stronger, forming a positive cycle. Those who came after had to grow under restrictions, unable to catch up to their growth speed no matter what. The difference would only grow bigger, and killing a single Beyond Grade A would not change that at all.

If they lost the Flickering War completely, taking revenge might be considered as a form of collecting some interest. Now, however, the risk of acting far outweighed the benefits, so of course, he was not willing to do it.

"Be it Gaud or Black Star, let them do whatever." The Star Arc Civilization leader shook his head. "I wonder what the other Super Star Cluster civilizations think. No one should want to take this risk; the big picture is more important. As for the federation and the church, they're not likely to fight internally now… right?"

…

Somewhere in the Primeval Star River, Manison deactivated the remote projection, turned on the virtual screen, and brought up Gaud's information that was circulating on the internet. He tapped the armrest of the chair with his fingers and pondered.

"Gaud… a new name, not a Beyond Grade A seed from any Star Field. He suddenly appeared out of nowhere, which means he's been secretly trained by the dynasty all this time. The last person who appeared in a similar way was Clotti, who has the ability to control dark matter. The dynasty heavily promoted his strength as soon as he appeared…

"Usually, the three Universal Civilizations promote the abilities of their direct Beyond Grade A members. However, the dynasty has asked Gaud to keep it a secret instead. Even Clotti did not receive this treatment, which means this guy's Esper Ability is extremely special. The rumor of him having the Energy Control Esper Ability might not be fake. Interesting."

A tint of curiosity flashed past Manison's eyes.

If Gaud really had such an overpowered ability, he could not say he was not tempted. If this was before, he would have most likely tried to ambush Gaud and capture him to make him into a Felon.

Now, however, he had decided to quit that profession. Unless it was a special situation, he would no longer make new Felons, or he would not possibly be able to have a high reputation in the association. That b*stard Black Star had been bringing his dark history up all the time, and he was really annoyed by it.

"I shall see how things go first. If Gaud wants to build a reputation in the future, he'll definitely have to display his ability. There's no way for him to hide it. In fact, someone might already plan to spar with him before he even leaves the Flickering World."

Manison suddenly narrowed his eyes and murmured, "There are so many Beyond Grade As and armed fleets in the Flickering World. It'll be easy to dispatch forces. That place is the most dangerous Star Field in the universe now. It's the land that nourishes conspiracies and plots… Hmm, I wonder if the federation, the church, and the Super Star Cluster Alliance will do anything…"

…

Meanwhile, in the Limitless Financial Group's Flickering World subdivision…

"Another high potential stock…"

Sorokin crossed his arms and recalled what happened in the meeting earlier.

From the way he looked at it, Gaud had a bright future and would definitely be able to grow smoothly with the dynasty's protection. It was almost certain he would become the National Pillar of the dynasty in the future. The dynasty had very high hopes on him.

"If things go well, I might be able to trigger a second Tragedy of the Pinnacles…"

Sorokin contemplated. He felt this was a great opportunity.

If he used the real strength he had been hiding and secretly assassinated Gaud, making the dynasty furious, he should be able to start an enormous storm that would shatter the situation the association had been working so hard to achieve. Thus, the bloody slaughtering between factions would start again.

Although he had joined the association, he was the last person who wanted to see the Beyond Grade A be united. His goals had never changed—one was to earn money, and another was to reduce the number of Beyond Grade As, creating an environment that was beneficial to him.

Furthermore, Black Star had always been a hidden problem. He instinctively wanted to get rid of anything that might expose his true identity.

"If I target Gaud, maybe I can think of a way to pin it on Black Star and cause him trouble… But he knows my secrets, so he'll definitely suspect me. It'll be risky for me too."

Sorokin frowned slightly.

Although he had this idea, it was tough to actually execute it, as Black Star had no motive to target Gaud.

In his eyes, even if he made the move, Black Star would be the last person the dynasty suspected. The framing had almost no chance of working.

He did not dare take the risk before coming up with a detailed plan.

"I have to carefully think on what to do exactly."

Sorokin's eyes flickered.

…

A few days passed very quickly. Under the influence of some people with motives, the content of the Beyond Grade A meeting got leaked. It did not only circulate in the black market this time but throughout the entire galactic society, attracting widespread attention.

The appeal of Super High Risk Esper Abilities related topics was very high. It piqued the interest of countless galactic residents. The rumors got more and more widely known. Although there was still no solid proof, under the secret influence of some organizations, it was as if the galactic society had already confirmed that Gaud's ability was 'Energy Control'.

Although the various organizations were shocked, due to different reasons, no one acted. They only silently kept an eye on the three Universal Civilizations and the Super Star Cluster Alliance, speculating if they would make a move.

In the eyes of the various organizations, as long as these two sides did not make any moves, nothing would happen.

The changes in the outside world did not affect the schedule of the dynasty fleet. It advanced through space with Gaud on board, heading toward the exit of the Flickering World.

Inside the luxurious training room of the fleet, Gaud hovered in midair, giving off a dim light all over his body. The sound of a moving stream echoed in the air; energy formed tides inside his body.

After a while, he opened his eyes and took a deep breath. The light extinguished, and his body returned to normal.

Gaud reached out his hand and turned his palm up. The next moment, a tiny stream of dark black energy suddenly appeared and spun around his wrist.

He toyed with this stream of energy and grinned.

"It's no wonder Energy Control is a 'high class Esper Ability'. It's been less than a month, and I've already cracked about half of the Evolution Energy's structure and can produce a semi-finished version of it. It's going smoother than I thought. At this pace, I'll control this special energy very soon. Then, I will be able to create it all I want and become a walking Evolution Cube…"

The ability of every Esper would change once they became a Beyond Grade A, and Energy Control was no exception. Once he broke down the structure of a type of energy, it would mean he permanently gained control of that type of energy and would be able to create it anytime.

This did not only include all kinds of common types of energy but even special forms of energy such as the Evolution Energy and Primal Esper Ability Entities. As long as he cracked them, they would become his own ability. With every type of energy he controlled, he would become stronger.

Not only that, Gaud even had a fuzzy feeling that once he became even stronger and mastered more types of energy, it seemed like he could even create new forms of energy out of nothing!

Even with his extremely extensive knowledge, he was still astonished. The potential of this overpowered Esper Ability was horrifying!

"Primal Esper Ability Entities are tough to find, but Black Star seems to have two of them. I'm his colleague now, and he wants to build a good relationship with me. If I bring up the request, he should agree to lend them to me… This is so much easier than robbing."

Gaud was in a great mood. The air felt so refreshing and the future so bright.

In the past when he was a wanted criminal, he could only rob something from others if he wanted it. Now that he had become a member of the Lawful Faction, he finally felt the advantages of having connections.

Gaud sighed as he opened the gate and walked out of the training room. The dynasty soldiers he met on the way all greeted him respectfully. He was already used to it.

When he came to the command room at the bridge, the captain approached and greeted him.

"Your Excellency Gaud, we're approaching the edge of the fourth exploration stage area of the Flickering World. We'll be reaching the entrance of the stargate route in two days. After that, we'll quickly pass through the remaining Star Clusters through the Black Star Army's territory."

"Hmm, good work," Gaud responded monotonously.

"Thank you. It's an honor to serve y…"

The captain's tone was humble.

However, before he finished, the ship suddenly trembled. It exited from hyperdrive mood and stopped.

Bang!

The staff all staggered due to the momentum. Some even fell to the floor.

The captain held onto the table and yelled, "What's going on?"

Very soon, an operational officer responded with a shocked tone. "Captain, the spaceship's artificial intelligence suddenly lost control. It locked down the engine, activated the emergency stop, turned off all devices, and disconnected from the quantum network! We've lost contact with the other spaceships!"

"Is this an attack‽" The captain was furious. "Who dares attack the dynasty's forces! Turn on the backup artificial intelligence immediately and regain control of the spaceship!"

The operational officer quickly returned to his post and worked on the system, but he was covered in sweat very soon.

"It… It can't be done! All functions of the spaceship are frozen!"

The dynasty crew inside the command room were panicking. Gaud glanced at them. He then turned to look outside the porthole and frowned.

"Am I the target?"

Gaud was surprised. He felt this was the only possibility.

He had analyzed his situation long ago. For their own sake, the odds of the various organizations attacking him were extremely low. He originally thought his trip in the Flickering World would be smooth and did not expect someone to really take such a big risk.

"Looks like the doing of a Virtual Mechanic. Is it the Mechanic Emperor? Tsk, is he really planning on capturing me and turning me into a Felon? He's already in such a horrible situation, yet he still dares to enrage the dynasty?"

Gaud was shocked.

Being shocked was one thing, but he was not nervous. His experience of being attacked was way too rich. The emotion 'fear' did not even exist in him.

Furthermore, he was not really a new Beyond Grade A. Although his strength could not compare with his old days, he had still inherited part of it and was stronger than someone at his level should be. This was one source of his confidence.

If the attacker was the Mechanic Emperor, he had to admit he would not be able to defeat him and could only look for a way to escape.

However, if it was some other organization that took him as a new Beyond Grade A and wanted to eliminate him, they would have made a huge mistake.

In his eyes, the only ones who had the motive and the ability to attack him were the federation, the church, the Super Star Cluster Alliance, and the Mechanic Emperor. It basically could not possibly anyone else.

Gaud's Beyond Grade A senses suddenly spread out and covered this entire area.

"Let's see who wants to kill me!"

Chapter 1226: Stop Acting. I Know Who You Are

Gaud's senses spread rapidly in all directions, covering more and more area. Very soon, he discovered a faint energy source that was hovering right in front of the fleet. However, he could not see it with his eyes. It seemed to be invisible.

The moment he discovered the target, it appeared before the fleet. It was shrouded in a black mechanical suit. Gaud could not figure out whom it was.

"Just one person… hmm? This presence…"

Gaud's expression changed slightly. His Esper Ability was very sensitive about one's energy presence. He could basically remember the unique energy presence of everyone he had ever met. He noticed that the presence of this attacker was familiar, so he might have met them before.

As the radar no longer worked, he sensed the environment around too and realized that the spacetime of this area was locked. It was the common effects of a trap. Space-related abilities such as hyperdrive, teleportation, and so on were all disabled.

Furthermore, his senses could not continue extending further when it reached a certain distance. There seemed to be a layer that separated this area from the outside world.

At this time, the captain noticed the attacker and immediately responded. He yelled to the crew, "Try to reconnect to the network and report this to the dynasty. Also, pull out the artificial intelligence chip, switch to manual controls, and retreat immediately!"

As soon as the order was given, the crew hastily moved. The staff in the main control room quickly headed toward the engine room and pulled out the artificial intelligence. They then used the hardware system to cancel all the artificial intelligence's authorization to control the spaceship. This was to prevent the spaceship from being controlled by the enemy. Plus, they would only be able to reboot the paralyzed spaceship if it was in manual mode.

This dynasty fleet was only responsible for transporting Gaud, so it was a small team. Although the performance of the dynasty battleships was higher than most spaceship models, the size of this team was too small. Its combat capability was very limited and could not possibly fight a Beyond Grade A.

Most importantly, their communication channel was cut off, and they could not request reinforcements from the outside world. The most important mission right now was to get the information out, so the captain did not want to fight. All of this was the standard response written in the Dynasty Commander Strategy Guidebook.

However, although his idea was decent, with the communication network cut off, the command system was broken, and his orders could not be passed onto the others. Shifting into a magic oriented emergency command system would also require some time… and this time dictated the difference between life and death.

Before this dynasty fleet made a move, countless golden electric arcs exploded from the attacker's body. Inside the cluster of electric arcs, a black-bean-like particle expanded and turned into an enormous mechanical army, instantly filling up the sights of everyone!

Mechanical Force—Soldier Nest!

Compressed Orb Innovation—Armed Body!

Indeed, it was Han Xiao's original body who came to attack Gaud!

He deliberately spread the message to have the various organizations suspect each other, but all of that was for one thing—to eliminate Gaud without anyone finding out. Otherwise, it would all be a waste of effort. The other organizations were not going to do it, so he had no choice but to do it himself.

As history and experience proved, the more parts a plan had, the more unstable factors it would have. Many conspiracies and plots were anything but complicated; they did not have so many twists and turns. Therefore, he did not have to be flashy to achieve his goal, focusing on the main conflict was the key.

Now, the waters were muddied. There were way too many possible suspects. He had achieved the first step of his plan, so he could move on to the next step and act now.

Based on the dynasty's route, he calculated a location Gaud had to pass by. He had teleported to the frontline stronghold using the King long ago and secretly moved here, found a desolate area, and planted the trap.

Not only did he place spacetime stabilization devices in this area, but he even used a large area detection masking device and 'sealed' this area up. The inside could not detect the outside, nor could the outside detect what was going on inside. No matter how intense the battle was on the inside, the detection devices outside would not be able to sense the energy shockwaves of the battle and see it as nothing was happening. This way, the chances of anyone discovering something were reduced.

Additionally, Han Xiao planted many other devices that blocked all kinds of detection methods, anything he could think of, all to reduce the chance of getting discovered. Only a Mechanic would be able to do something like this.

The universe already had the technology he used, but the ones Han Xiao used were all improved versions of them that incorporated some similar blueprints in Jayz's technology treasure. These devices were very advanced and much more effective than the ordinary versions.

Of course, the battleships of advanced civilizations had respective detection devices for all these traps. If they were travelling normally, the dynasty fleet would have discovered the anomaly from very far away. However, the range of Han Xiao's hacking abilities was extremely far now. He had secretly won the heart of the dynasty fleet's artificial intelligence long ago and taken control of the fleet, which was why they did not notice it at all. Otherwise, the dynasty fleet would never have stepped into his traps.

Though Gaud's Energy Control Esper Ability was powerful, he was powerless in the virtual territory and could not notice anything.

As soon as the mechanical army appeared, it fired right away at the paralyzed dynasty fleet without hesitation.

Countless beams of light flickered through space. The next moment, the storm of attacks penetrated the dynasty fleet's formation!

The shields of the dynasty fleets were frozen. They were defenseless under the rain of attacks. Beams penetrated the ships one after another. The thick exterior armor became twisted and torn. The spaceships exploded in the blink of an eye, turning into colorful fireworks!

Buzz!

At this time, a dark blue psionic barrier appeared abruptly and protected the remaining spaceship. The mechanical army's attacks rapidly shattered one layer of the barrier after another, but its speed was still delayed.

During this extremely short delay, the thrusters of these spaceships suddenly released huge flames. The spaceship accelerated in an instant and barely escaped the attacks.

Inside the main ship, Gaud's eyes were gleaming. A cluster of light filled with thousands of light strings floated above his palm.

In the crucial moment earlier, he had activated his ability and created a psionic shield that blocked some of the attacks. Then, he used his Esper Ability to fire up the energy furnace of the remaining battleships, skipping the multiple layers of authorization and forcibly activating the thrusters.

After a round of fire, a small fleet like this was already heavily damaged. There were only seven ships left.

"That was close…"

Gaud's expression was grave. He was on edge.

In the moment of the attack, he sensed the energy level of the attack and confirmed it had definitely reached the peak Beyond Grade A standard. It was strong by the peak Beyond Grade A standard even in that matter.

There were only so many Mechanics in the entire universe who were at this level. No matter who it was, it was not someone he could defeat… Of course, it was still most likely that old b*stard Manison!

"We can't fight. Let's go!"

Gaud glanced at the shocked and furious captain, activated his ability again, and pushed the surviving spaceships toward the edge of the sealed area.

He knew that the crew was of no help. It was not that he wanted to save them, but his flying speed was slower than the battleships; he needed them to escape.

As soon as he left this locked area and out of the opponent's trap, he would have a way to contact the outside world.

However, at this moment, a sudden sense of danger appeared in his mind. His intuition felt an overwhelming sense of threat. He instantly charged through the cabin wall and escaped the spaceship.

Swoosh!

The next moment, five extremely condensed red beams shot out from Han Xiao's fingers, easily penetrated the layers of psionic barriers, and cut the remaining battleships into pieces like a hot knife cutting through butter.

The next second, the energy cores of the spaceships exploded. The spaceships turned into fireworks and destroyed all the spaceship fragments.

In an instant, the fleet was annihilated, leaving Gaud to hover in the battlefield alone.

"What a powerful energy beam. It seems to have extremely strong penetrating ability against all energy shields. If I was hit by it, I would definitely be hurt…"

Fear lingered in Gaud's heart. He was very close to being hit by the red beams earlier.

He looked at and saw that Han Xiao's black mechanical suit was covered in red energy circuits like blood vessels, all connecting to his fingertips. As the five red beams were launched, these energy circuits dimmed again as if they had entered a cooldown.

Seeing that his attacks had missed, Han Xiao narrowed his eyes.

"These Anti-neutron Beams are completely silent. If it was an ordinary new Beyond Grade A, he would have already been hit. He must have foreseen the threat because of part of the soul he inherited from the past."

In the last few years, Han Xiao had built more Universal Treasures than just 'The King'. This black mechanical suit was originally a Gold blueprint from Jayz's technology treasure. Han Xiao had fused some modern technology into it, improved it, given it a new name, and called it 'Black King—Ranged Gear'.

This was just one of the products in the series. There were also 'Melee Gear', 'Army Gear', and 'Defense Gear', which excelled in different areas. He called them the "Black King Series", and they were all Gold Grade mechanical suits!

Without hesitation, Han Xiao charged toward Gaud. Gaud turned around and fled right away.

However, without a spaceship, his flight speed was no match for the mechanical army. He instantly got surrounded by the mechanical troops and fell into a dreadful spot.

As soon as the fight started, Han Xiao immediately noticed just how much of an edge Gaud's Esper Ability gave him. Not only did he have an outrageously high resistance against energy attacks, but he could even absorb the enemy's energy attacks during battle to recover his own energy at an astonishing speed. Basically, at the Beyond Grade A level, having this Esper Ability meant having infinite energy. It was incredibly overpowered!

The superiority of his Esper Ability was extremely apparent. With the edge his Esper Ability gave him, Gaud shockingly did not show signs of defeat under the attacks of the mechanical army.

"He has only just entered the Beyond Grade A territory, and he's already this strong. Will there ever be anyone who can defeat him in the distant future?"

Seeing this, even Han Xiao was astounded by how talented Gaud was. At the same time, his thoughts of eliminating this hidden threat as early as possible became firmer.

The next moment, he personally stepped into the encirclement and charged toward Gaud, deflecting the energy beam attacks from Gaud one after another, successfully closing the distance. Without saying a word, his leg swung down like an axe.

Gaud's expression changed as he hastily raised his hands to block it.

Boom!

An enormous force came from Han Xiao's leg. Even though he protected his body with energy, his body could not endure it. His bones broke one after another, and intense pain flooded his mind.

"To think I got physically beat up by a Mechanic. If my Grade was a little bit higher, you'd be done for…"

Gaud clenched his teeth and endured the pain. As he attempted to back away, he realized his arms felt like they were stuck to the armor on Han Xiao's leg, and he could not pull it away.

He hastily looked at it and saw black nanoparticles spreading at the area of contact, rapidly covered his arms, and headed toward his entire body.

"Sh*t!"

Gaud hastily controlled his energy attempting to get away. However, at this time, his mind suddenly trembled. His soul was dragged into a world made of data streams, and he lost control of his body.

Before he could react, a gigantic silhouette appeared and slapped his soul into the ground.

This is… Virtual Soul!

Gaud had vivid memories of this ability. He clenched his teeth and shouted, "Manison! Is that you‽'

Han Xiao ignored him and continued attacking.

Inside the Virtual Domain, Gaud's soul was powerless and was thrashed. Luckily, the strength of his soul far exceeded normal new Beyond Grade As. Only because of that was he able to quickly escape.

As Gaud's consciousness returned to his body, before he could catch a breath, he realized his entire body was wrapped by machines as if he wore a mechanical suit.

"You…"

Before he could start resisting, he saw Han Xiao snap his fingers.

Whoosh!

The next moment, Gaud disappeared without a trace. The King mechanical suit took him away through teleportation, ignoring the spacetime lock in the area.

"Execute the second plan."

Han Xiao turned around immediately and told the mechanical army to bombard the area, wiping away all possible traces of the fleet. At the same time, he folded and compressed the mechanical army and placed them back in his main body.

He had prepared multiple plans. If he could quickly eliminate Gaud right here on the spot, it would be the best. However, if Gaud had the ability to hold on for an extended period of time, he would find a way to change the battlefield.

Although he had set up many traps, the fourth exploration stage area of the Flickering World was way too boisterous. There were uncertainties everywhere. The longer he took, the more risk he would have to bear. He did not want to spend too much time there to avoid running into someone.

The last time he traveled with Kasuyi, he had recorded the coordinates of many Deep Layer secondary dimensions on the way. While waiting for Gaud to arrive, he had chosen a stable dimension no one had ever visited and placed a few 'Thrones' there. He had also left some mechanical armies in that dimension to transform it into a larger sealed area.

When they arrived in the Deep Layer secondary dimension, only then would all of Gaud's ways of escaping be eliminated.

Han Xiao quickly finished up cleaning the traces, stored his troops, hastily changed into another King suit, and instantly disappeared.

As the images in his eyes flickered, he arrived at a new area.

There, the earth was white. It was desolate. There were absolutely no signs of life, as if it was a black and white world. Only outsiders carried colors with them.

In midair, the mechanical army that had set up an ambush in this secondary dimension had surrounded Gaud and was attacking him so that he could not escape.

Seeing that Han Xiao had appeared, Gaud instantly turned and looked at him. His eyes were filled with shock.

The teleportation function of the King was already one of Han Xiao's signatures. When he fell for it, he finally knew who the attacker was, and he could not believe it!

While barely holding on against the attacks of the mechanical army, Gaud stared at Han Xiao. His tone was filled with shock and confusion.

"Black Star! It's you! What do you mean by this!"

He had absolutely no idea why the person who attacked him was Black Star.

Aren't we buddies now?

Didn't you want to befriend me?

Why attack me‽

Knowing that Gaud's doom was certain, Han Xiao finally spoke in a calm tone.

"Stop acting. I know who you really are… EsGod. Do you really think you can cut off your past completely and get a new life?"

The moment his words sounded, Gaud's pupils constricted into dots. He completely lost it!

Impossible!

My plan's perfect. How could he possibly know‽

Chapter 1227: I Am Starting to Feel More and More Like a Villain

In the past, in order to create a Super High Risk Esper Ability, he had captured Espers ruthlessly without ever considering the consequences. After fusing countless abilities, he had obtained the genetic chain of [Energy Control]. By then, as his original body's ledger was already filled with blood and his life span was ending, he thought of starting a new life.

Hence, he had hidden this ability all along and never shown it. He had secretly chosen 'Gaud' as the container for rebirth and planted this part of his Esper Ability genetic chain into Gaud, planning to inherit this ability after his rebirth. He then killed all his subordinates who knew about it and made sure that this identity had a clean background.

The core of this plan was [Esper Ability—Rebirth]. This was an ability that could only ever be used once, giving the user a second life. It was not a pure soul-type Esper Ability but was related to the High Dimensional Information Form.

Of course, the effect of it was not as simple as simply splitting up his soul. His consciousness would fuse perfectly with the container, forming a new and whole soul, completely unrelated to his original body. Although he would still have his memories, his thoughts and personality would shift to a certain extent. This meant that Gaud was Gaud and no longer EsGod; he had entirely abandoned his past and was truly reborn.

Back when he was captured by Han Xiao and the others, in that brief moment before the Spacetime Amber completely sealed him up, only [Esper Ability—Rebirth] could save him. Hence, he had unflinchingly torn his soul apart and escaped. Using this ability to turn into High Dimensional Information Form, he had escaped the soul seal from Lotus Swordsman and the others, entering Gaud's body.

Not a single person knew about this. After so many years of nothing happening, Gaud had not been worried since long ago. He felt that no one saw through his plan. However, to his absolute shock, his deepest secret got brought up by Han Xiao this easily.

A tsunami was going on in Gaud's mind. He had utterly no idea at which part of the plan he got discovered.

Due to how unstable his mind was, even his defenses became weaker. He was blown away by the mechanical army, adding a few more wounds to his body.

At this time, Gaud's thoughts spun quickly. He suppressed the shock in his heart and said,

"EsGod? What are you talking about?"

"You still don't want to admit it? Looks like you still have some meaningless hope. Do you think you can possibly escape now that you're in my hands?"

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes and instantly knew what Gaud was thinking.

Even in such a desperate situation, Gaud would never admit he was EsGod. He believed that if he went missing, the dynasty would most certainly search for him intensively and thoroughly, and Black Star might also be investigated. He felt he still had a chance to escape.

However, if he admitted his identity, what Black Star did would be justified. He could wait for the dynasty to rescue him as long as he did not leave any evidence.

Therefore, no matter how absolutely shocked he was inside, no matter how much Black Star tried to make him talk, Gaud was never going to admit it.

"Black Star! This is completely ridiculous! At least find a better excuse if you want to kill me. How am I related to EsGod? You're probably worried that I'll threaten your position when I'm stronger, so you want to get rid of me beforehand. There's no one else here anyway. Why bother making up something nonexistent‽"

Gaud clenched his teeth and spoke with a tone that sounded like he was furious from being accused.

"Why didn't I notice in the past that your acting skills are on par with Kasuyi's?" Han Xiao curled his lips.

Gaud ignored what he said as if he was submerged in rage and yelled, "I got it! You're the one who leaked my ability to the black market! You must have heard it from inside the dynasty and want to muddy the waters, so you can frame it on someone else! Don't think for a second you can deceive everyone; the dynasty won't let you run away with this!"

"Since you don't even dare admit it, there's nothing much more to talk about."

Han Xiao shook his head.

He originally wanted to speak with Gaud heart to heart. After all, they had known each other for decades; he wanted to at least give him the chance to say a few last words. However, Gaud was clearly not going to admit it no matter what, so there was nothing more to talk about.

As soon as he said that, Han Xiao activated his Mechanical Force without hesitation, releasing the troops in his original body. He then fused some of the mechanical soldiers into a Mechanical Deity.

This sealed Deep Layer secondary dimension was undisturbed, so Han Xiao did not have to hold back anymore.

Swoosh!

The Celestial Punishment Edge slashed down, shattering multiple layers of shields and smashed Gaud from the sky down to the ground like slapping a fly. He plummeted like a falling meteor, creating an enormous crater.

A shockwave erupted with Gaud in the center. Cracks opened up on the pale earth that extended all the way to the end of the horizon.

Plop…

Gaud was bleeding from every pore on his skin. His shirt was instantly painted red.

An intense pain flooded all his nerves. Before he could even catch a breath, his sights were filled up by dense black silhouettes. The next moment, the barrels of the machines in the sky all lit up.

Gaud hastily jumped up and backed away. The next second, countless psionic cannon beams fused into a gigantic light beam and penetrated the pale earth.

The ground instantly cracked and bulged like a mountain rising from the ground. It then shattered and exploded!

Boom!

The powerful aftershock spread rapidly. Though Gaud created layers of shields, the shockwave still blew him away.

He was only halfway up the sky when the Mechanical Deity caught up to him and smashed him back to the ground, shattering god knew how many more bones.

Although Gaud's Esper Ability had an extraordinary potential, potential was not the same as actual strength. His current Grade was still too low. Before Han Xiao, who was at his peak performance, he was as weak as a child and completely powerless. The battle was entirely one-sided; Gaud could only barely stay alive while getting thrashed!

While Han Xiao beat up Gaud, he took the time to look at the combat information on the interface.

Since his level was much higher than Gaud, he could see all of Gaud's abilities, so he could confirm that Gaud had no way of escaping this situation.

Although he had seen Gaud's interface the last time, he looked through it again now just in case.

Then Han Xiao discovered that Gaud had acquired a new ability.

[Energy Control—Evolution Energy (Unactivated)]: You are analyzing the energy structure of the Evolution Energy. You will master this energy when the analysis is complete. Current analysis progress: 50.2%.

This b*stard is still thinking about the Evolution Cube?

Han Xiao frowned.

This guy is really persistent. It's a shock he still hasn't given up on the Evolution Cube!

Gaud's ability was too stealthy. He only started the analysis after leaving the palace, so Han Xiao did not notice it back then.

Luckily, he indirectly shattered this plan of his because of other reasons, or Gaud would have secretly obtained this technology.

Han Xiao suddenly realized a sensitive problem.

Did Gaud do this only on his own, or did the dynasty ask him to do it?

Han Xiao's eyes gleamed as he thought with a heavy heart.

Although the dynasty had not mentioned the Evolution Cube recently, Han Xiao knew that some people in the dynasty would never give up on obtaining it. Gaud was now a direct member of the dynasty, so the dynasty's upper echelons knew his ability. It was very likely they secretly sent him to crack the Evolution Energy and then claim that their research succeeded so that he would have no reason to be angry.

Han Xiao had nothing to say about the dynasty's doings. They were just trying to acquire what they wanted. There was no right or wrong. What he cared more about was how this piece of intelligence would affect his plan.

If the dynasty asked Gaud to do it, the risk would increase for him. In the dynasty's eyes, he would have a valid motive and not be someone who they had no reason to doubt; he would become a suspect too.

On the other hand, this gave him a new excuse. Since the dynasty played tricks on him first, as long as he did not kill Gaud, even if he got found out and the dynasty held him responsible for it, things would also not end up in the worst scenario.

Looks like it's not all bad… I shall take him down first!

Han Xiao shook his head, suppressed these thoughts, and focused on bullyin… no, fighting Gaud.

As time passed, Gaud's state became worse and worse. Although his Esper Ability gave him an infinite amount of energy, it did not give him the ability to regenerate health quickly. His wounds accumulated, and his regenerative speed could not keep up anymore.

Dragging his exhausted and wounded body, Gaud tried to escape time after time, but he failed each attempt.

The strength difference was too great, and Han Xiao was very well prepared. There was nothing Gaud could do.

As a few more light beams penetrated his body, Gaud could not hold on any longer. Like a bird without wings, he plummeted and landed on the wrecked pale ground. Blood flowed out from all over his body, quickly forming a puddle.

Han Xiao deactivated the Mechanical Deity and slowly landed beside Gaud. Gaud still had yet to give up. He dragged his heavily damaged body and crawled on the ground, leaving a trail of blood behind.

"… Give up."

Han Xiao looked at the interface and confirmed that Gaud was already in the near-death state. He shook his head, sighed, bent down, grabbed Gaud's neck, and lifted his entire body up.

Gaud's feet were hovering above the ground. He had no strength to resist. He stared at Han Xiao; his eyes were filled with hatred.

He had finally returned to the Beyond Grade A realm after so long. He had a hopeful future filled with infinite possibilities, and he was looking forward to it.

However, he had never thought that after keeping a low profile and growing for so long, as soon as he appeared in the world full of hope, he would meet Black Star, who figured out his identity and shattered his plan in the womb.

He could not admit this loss!

He still had a bright future!

He still had a big goal!

All the planning in the past years, his lifelong ambition…

All of that was going to perish…

He could not accept it!

He could not lose!

Han Xiao looked at Gaud's twisted expressions and shook his head.

"Whether you admit that you're EsGod or not, it won't change the facts. I did this to you not because of personal reasons. If that thing did not happen, I couldn't care less about you wiping your history and joining the dynasty. After all, I'm no saint. I'm no one to judge your sins.

"But I know exactly how determined you are about what exists on the other side of that wormhole. I can't let you move freely inside the dynasty. That will not only threaten me but the entire explored universe.

"Although that day will come sooner or later, not only will your existence bring that day forward, it'll even cause unpredictable impacts… because you're too pure. As long as there's the slightest opportunity to become stronger, you won't care who you fight for. As for me… I don't like to act only when the threat has already erupted."

Gaud's pupils constricted.

He subconsciously wanted to ask Han Xiao what he knew and opened his mouth but did not speak in the end. He did not want to leave any evidence that might cause suspicion.

"Black Star… the dynasty won't let you get away with this!"

Gaud repeated this sentence again.

Seeing that Gaud was still not admitting anything, Han Xiao knew it was not going to happen. As he activated his Mechanical Force, nanoparticles extended onto Gaud's body and quickly shrouded his body, turning into a spherical mechanical imprisonment device.

Then, Han Xiao activated the Spacetime Amber and slowly covered this imprisonment device up. He then thought about it and said, "Including this time, this is the third time you've fallen into my hands."

Before Gaud could respond, Han Xiao completed the Spacetime Ember seal.

Buzz!

The next moment, the amber was complete.

The entire device got sealed up. From the outside, only the spherical mechanical prison could be seen in the amber. What was inside it was not visible.

At this moment, Han Xiao finally heaved a sigh of relief and relaxed his taut nerves.

"It's finally done. No accidents happened…"

One reason he did not kill Gaud on the spot was to give himself some room for explanation if he got exposed; another was that he did not want to give Gaud an opportunity to be revived by the Sanctums any time soon; last but not least, he did not want to waste the Super High Risk Esper Ability EsGod spent countless years to create, [Energy Control]!

When the Spacetime Amber wiped out Gaud's soul, he could have Feidin use the Soul Swapper and shift the soul of someone he thrust into Gaud's body. Using these two Universal Treasures in combination had always been something he wanted to test out.

Or he could wait for 'Little EsGod' Evans to grow and suck away Gaud's Esper Ability.

He could even wait till he mastered the Felon technology and secretly make Gaud into a Felon. However, the side effects of that were too huge, so it was not the best choice.

As for whether Gaud could still revive after he did all these, Han Xiao did not know either. He never tried it, so he had no way of knowing.

If Gaud could revive, there would indeed be a chance he could get exposed. In the future, when the dynasty discovers the Sanctums, they would certainly try to revive this 'direct member' of theirs.

However, who knew what things would be like then? Furthermore, he could infinitely delay the arrival of that day, and it was easy. Before he was confident in dealing with the dynasty's accusations, he could simply not kill Gaud and only imprison him, letting him out once in a while to beat him up and make sure his soul was not wiped!

This way, Gaud would not die, and of course, he could never be revived!

Merciless, cruel, ruthless, fearsome. Why is my style becoming more and more like a villain?

Han Xiao rubbed his cheeks.

He silently made a joke about himself in his mind before becoming serious.

Capturing Gaud was only a start. The more important thing to do was to deal with the storm the dynasty's rage would stir up not long after that would sweep across all advanced civilizations!

"I've done what I need to do. Now I'll just have to wait for the storm to start… Sigh, I didn't expect myself to start the fuse this time."

Thinking about the various possibilities he had speculated not long ago, Han Xiao exhaled lightly, turned on the interface, and looked at the mission.

The hidden mission [Gaud's Secret] was surprisingly complete. The mission requirement was to find out Gaud's secret, and Han Xiao did not know what the criteria of that was. He clearly did not find any solid evidence, nor did Gaud admit anything. Did he just have to call out his real identity in front of him? Was it really so easy?

Hmm, the fact that I thrashed him is probably the main reason it's considered completed…

The mission completion criteria of hidden missions was quite confusing. Han Xiao did not think too much about it and went to clean things up.

He controlled the mechanical army and bombarded this secondary dimension till the entire dimension collapsed, eliminating all traces.

After completing that, Han Xiao did not waste any time there. He retrieved his machines, put on the King suit, directly returned to Black Star Palace, and found Feidin in the library right away.

Feidin only looked up and glanced at Han Xiao before putting his focus back on reading the book in his hands, letting Han Xiao touch him all he wanted.

After getting plenty of luck in his hands, Han Xiao returned to his personal training room, rubbed his hands with excitement, and chose to conclude the mission.

[Gaud's Secret] completed!

You have received [Character Summon Card - Gaud]!

Character Summon Card - Gaud: [Energy Analysis]—You can efficiently analyze the principles and structure of an energy form, gaining control of the energy. Usage: 0/4

You have received: Draw one of Gaud's ability/talent.

Note: Gaud is an Esper. Parts of the possible abilities have been automatically adjusted to your class.

Randomizing… complete!

Please select one from the five options below as the reward:

[Plasma Shockwave] - Ability: Release a plasma arc beam and deal damage to the enemy. The power of it relies on your INT, MYS, and energy output efficiency. Minimum cost per second: 5 energy. Cooldown: 4 seconds.

[Kinetic Strengthening] - Ability: Using energy, strengthen your cells and continuously enhance your close-range combat capabilities. The effects rely on your STR, DEX, END, MYS, and energy output efficiency. Minimum cost per minute: 10 energy. Cooldown: 12 seconds.

[Spiritual Growth] - Talent: +15% MYS, +10% CHA.

[Energy Collecting Ring] - Ability: Absorb the energy around you to rapidly recover your energy. Cost: 2 stamina per second. Cooldown: 0. Can be turned on at all times.

[Perfect Energy Affinity Physique] - Talent: You have astounding affinity toward all forms of energy. +120% basic energy senses, +90% basic energy resistance, +60% basic energy absorption efficiency, +30% basic energy attack damage, +20% maximum energy.

Chapter 1228: Sorokin's Confusion

Seeing the last option, Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

"Yoho, nice!"

Among the options, only the last one was valuable. This was one of Gaud's Molding Talents.

The bonuses this talent gave were all basic bonuses. The increase would be very considerable. To Han Xiao, the three most useful bonuses to him were the additional ninety-percent basic energy resistance, thirty-percent increase to basic energy attack damage, and twenty-percent increase to maximum energy.

His Indestructible Body was only strong because his regenerative speed was extremely quick, but his resistances were not outrageously high. However, this talent directly almost doubled his resistance to energy attacks!

As he became stronger, the attack damage of his mechanical army became stronger too. Hence, the 'die together' combo also became riskier for himself as time went on. The last time he used this in the Celestial Star Alliance, he almost sent himself away.

With this talent, if he did the same time again, he would not be in danger at all. This was another big step forward on the path of a Mechanic Tank.

Without this ability, Gaud would have lost consciousness long ago.

The basic energy attack damage bonus only increased Gaud's own damage output, but in the hands of a Mechanic, it was much stronger. It could increase the damage of all energy type weapons. Its most direct impact would be the increase to the army's long-range attacks. The thirty-percent increase was also quite ample.

At this point, with so many talents, Han Xiao had already discovered one trait—when the Molding Talents of other classes were possessed by a Mechanic, the effects would be astronomically enlarged. This was the advantage of using the Army Style.

Of course, the extra twenty percent maximum energy was incredible too.

His current maximum energy was around 290,000, so this gave him 50,000 energy right away. It was more than enough for him to acquire the bonuses of a new Energy Rank, maybe even two ranks!

In the later stages, Energy Rank bonuses and Race Evolution were among the main sources of attributes, giving thousands of points easily every time, substantially more than simply leveling up.

At his current Energy Rank, the attributes he would receive every time his rank increased were enormous. His attributes would increase for about seven thousand in total once he gained just one more Energy Rank.

The way the Energy Rank bonuses worked was that when his current energy depleted throughout battles, the bonuses would decrease along with the Energy Rank too. Therefore, the Supers who had infinite energy or could convert between energy and health had a tremendous edge. They could always maintain their energy level at their peak. Han Xiao, Kasuyi, and Oulou were all like this.

You have received the talent [Perfect Energy Affinity Physique]!

It was an easy choice. Han Xiao chose the last option without hesitation.

The next moment, an intense pain erupted in his body. Luckily, his nerves were tough, and he instantly regained control of his body.

This talent changed his physique; all the cells in his body were becoming stronger. The pain only faded after quite some time. His senses of the world changed again. It felt refreshing.

Han Xiao realized that he could now sense the stray universe energy everywhere around him without having to use any ability. It was as if he was suddenly no longer short-sighted; he could observe the world more clearly.

Furthermore, his body was even automatically pulling the stray energy in. The stray energy around was gathering unconsciously, moving around his body like pets.

Anyone who has this physique can be considered a talent. They'll grow extremely quickly. This talent should also be one of the reasons Gaud became a Beyond Grade A so quickly.

Han Xiao's body was filled with energy. He glanced at his attributes, his Energy Rank had already surpassed the 100,000 level.

However, there was no additional notification on the interface, so he was not sure if 100,000 Energy Rank was a new stage.

He was not concerned about it. Based on experience, the benefits of achieving a new Energy Rank would only show during Promotion. That was how it was for the bonuses of 52,000 Energy Rank and 78,000 Energy Rank. Therefore, having higher Energy Ranks at lower levels meant having high potential.

As for the effects of the Character Summon Card, Han Xiao had yet to try it. However, based on the fundamental mechanics of the Character Summon Cards, the effects of [Energy Analysis] were most certainly not permanent. He had two guesses about it.

One possibility was that once he chose which energy to gain control of, he would lose the control when the duration of the Character Summon Card ended. Another possibility was that it was similar to Jayz's [Mechanic—Insight] Character Summon Card; although he would lose the ability after the Character Summon Card duration ended, he would still remember the knowledge he gained by analyzing the energy, which would make studying this type of energy easier in the future.

However, he, of course, did not have the [Energy Control] Esper Ability, so he could not convert energy like Gaud could and would only be able to simulate the process using machines, which would be much more difficult. Espers did not have to understand the principles and mechanisms of their Esper Ability at all; they could use it right away. While the others could not duplicate the same process, they had to analyze the process and find another way to carry it out.

Basically, Espers only had to know that one plus one made two, while the others had to find out why one plus one was two and understand it. The difference was huge.

If the special energy created by Esper Abilities were so easy to break down, the advanced civilizations would have mass produced them long ago, and [Energy Control] would not have been seen as an overpowered ability.

Nonetheless, at least there are four uses. There's room for mistakes.

Han Xiao nodded, he was quite passionate about research.

Although I can fight Pugilists with my fists, I know I'm still a good scientist.

After browsing his attributes for a while more, Han Xiao turned off the interface and entered the quantum network.

For the time being, he did not plan to go anywhere and only wanted to monitor the galactic network at him, waiting for the storm to arrive.

…

"Gaud and his fleet have all gone missing‽"

Inside the Crimson Dynasty, Urranrell, who had just received the urgent report, suddenly stood up. Her expression changed drastically.

Before her was the remote projection of the marshal of the exploration army, Tarrokov. His expression was extremely serious as he said with a deep voice, "Yes, it happened just now. The remote link between Gaud's guard fleet and Planet Lighthouse's artificial intelligence center suddenly broke. We tried repairing it, but all attempts failed. We can't contact Gaud or anyone in the fleet now!"

The artificial intelligences of the dynasty fleets in the Flickering World were all monitored by the Planet Lighthouse headquarters. Once disconnected, Planet Lighthouse would instantly find out where that team went missing. This formed a highly responsive military system that covered most areas in the Flickering World.

"Where did they go missing?" Urranrell frowned heavily.

"Right at the edge of the Flickering World's Emerald Star Cluster, close to the stargate entrance of the third exploration phase. Using the nearest space buoy as a point, we have circled out the rough range of the area they went missing in. I've already sent the teams nearby to investigate."

Hearing this, Urranrell had no choice but to wait patiently. She asked with a grave tone, "What do you think is the cause of this?"

"There's not enough evidence to make an assumption." Tarrokov hesitated then said, "But personally, I'm guessing that the fleet was very likely attacked. Someone wants to kill Gaud. This is the most likely scenario."

Urranrell sat back down, her hands gripped together. The emotions in her eyes were flickering.

Not long after, Tarrokov received a report from his subordinates. His expression changed slightly, and he said, "Your Excellency Urranrell, the teams have sent back the message saying they did not discover any traces of the fleet, nor are there any signs of an anomaly within the area. The spaceships that passed by also said they did not detect anything unusual. It's like the fleet Gaud was in disappeared into thin air…"

Hearing this, Urranrell no longer hesitated. She instantly contacted the chief secretary and said with a firm tone, "Release an Emergency Summon Order. Notify all the upper echelons to drop everything on their hands and gather for a meeting immediately!"

…

About ten minutes later, the remote projections of the dynasty upper echelons came to the conference room one after another. The bosses of the various departments gathered and chatted quietly, not knowing what happened that made Urranrell summon all of them urgently.

Very soon, Urranrell entered the room with a serious expression. She looked around at the various upper echelons present and cut to the chase.

"This is an emergency. The dynasty's direct Beyond Grade A, Gaud, might have been attacked and is confirmed missing!"

As soon as she said that, the entire place became silent.

Shock appeared on the faces of every upper echelon. They did not expect to hear something so shocking.

At this time, Tarrokov stepped up and described the situation in the simplest way.

After understanding the situation, the various upper echelons present were all furious!

"Who dares to attack the dynasty's direct member‽ This is trampling the dynasty's pride!"

"We must investigate it thoroughly!"

"The dynasty is not to be provoked! No matter who did it, we must make them pay!"

Everyone had the same reaction; they were all extremely furious.

They were one of the ruling civilizations, yet someone dared to attack their direct member and wipe out their talent. Whoever was behind this had absolutely no respect for the dynasty at all!

For someone to do something like that, in their eyes, that person was asking to be killed!

An intelligence department high ranking official said with a deep voice, "Since the fleet is missing too, we can assume that the enemy succeeded. We have to first verify if Gaud is still alive. If he's still alive, we have to prioritize saving him."

"That's right. Gaud is an important direct Beyond Grade A. Even if there's only a tiny chance, we must protect his life!" another military official agreed.

"Gaud is a Beyond Grade A. To be able to take him down so quickly, the enemy definitely had to use a lot of forces. I suggest checking the space buoys nearby immediately. There should be witness reports of large fleets passing by!"

"Don't have too high hopes. If the enemy could easily cut off the fleet's remote link, they'd definitely be able to modify the records of the space buoys. The enemy was definitely fully prepared and wouldn't leave any obvious clues since he dared mess with the dynasty."

"The enemy could make our fleet disappear without a trace. There's a high chance that a Beyond Grade A Mechanic is involved!"

"That's right. The enemy might have left clues in the quantum network. I suggest getting Quantum Demon Judith to investigate, or we can even request help from Black Star if it really comes to that point. Black Star is a top Virtual Mechanic. Not many people in the universe can hide from him in the quantum network!"

The people planned and discussed the matter for a while. The topic then went back to the suspect.

An officer said, "Some time ago, an unknown force spread information about Gaud's real ability on the network. This might be the fuse; someone wants to eliminate our talent or has eyes on this Super High Risk Esper Ability."

"Not many organizations have both the ability and motive to do this. The federation and the church have been our competitors forever. They don't want to see us have someone as talented as Gaud, so they both might act… especially the Federation of Light. They have the Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device, so they can kill Gaud without anyone noticing!"

"No, it is now the development stage of the Flickering World, and we're still at war. The federation and the church wouldn't break our temporary partnership for something like this. In fact, the Super Star Clusters civilizations are the most suspicious. They might feel that since they have no way of turning the war around, they had to erase a future threat before losing completely!"

"I heard Black Star has been protesting about Manison's Felon technology, so the Mechanic Emperor is suspicious too! Don't forget, Ninjia from the Arcane Church is suspected to have been killed by Manison, leading to the church's Ten Thousand Deity Scepter falling into the federation's hands… This guy has done something like this before!"

Everyone present had the same three speculations. These three sides had both the ability and the motive. Other than them, no other organization would have the guts to attack the dynasty's direct member.

Looking at everyone's excited expressions, Bekorodi's expression changed slightly as he suddenly thought of something.

No… one more person has the motive.

In the past, he had told Gaud to analyze the Evolution Energy. If Black Star discovered what Gaud did, Black Star would have a reason to attack him too. Black Star was a suspect!

However… Bekorodi could not bring that up!

The plan to analyze the Evolution Cube got called to a stop by Urranrell long ago; Bekorodi only approached Gaud behind Urranrell's back because he received the subtle approval from the next ruler. He was carrying out this plan secretly; this was not something he could point out in this situation!

It did not matter whether Black Star was actually the one who did it. As soon as what he did got exposed, not only would he be most likely demoted, it would impact the next ruler negatively too.

If Black Star really did it, although Black Star would certainly be held responsible, he would take much more blame. After all, he acted against the orders and placed the dynasty at the moral low ground.

All kinds of plots flashed past his mind. Bekorodi opened his mouth a bit but chose to stay silent in the end.

Even if Black Star was the culprit, he was not going to say it.

Bekorodi thought things through very clearly. It was the next ruler who hinted for him to carry out the plan. The two of them had a silent agreement to have the new ruler break this case open after Urranrell's term ended, so the new ruler's reputation and image would be increased.

However, although Bekorodi had this plan, what made him stay silent was more the fact that he did not believe Black Star was the culprit.

With Black Star's position, even if he did notice what Gaud was doing, he had no reason to make it into such a big deal. He sure had the motive, but it was too weak.

Furthermore, the way Bekorodi looked at it, the title of National Pillar and the three Universal Civilizations' consultant were more than enough to tie Black Star up. After enjoying the benefits of them, Black Star would not want to lose them, so he would not do something as rash as this.

While Bekorodi was brainstorming, the others quickly came to a decision.

Urranrell made the decisive call.

"Announce Gaud going missing on behalf of the dynasty immediately. Tell the entire universe that the dynasty will find the culprit no matter the cost!"

Swoosh!

The upper echelons present stood up simultaneously and nodded.

"Understood!"

…

At a border stargate transit station of the Emerald Star Cluster, a man wearing the uniform of the Limitless Financial Group stood at the scenery observation area and looked at the galaxy outside the porthole. The border stargate was not far away. Belts of light extended from inside the blue space vortex. They were all spaceships entering and leaving the border.

"Based on the time, the fleet guarding Gaud should arrive in a day at most…" this Limitless Financial Group employee murmured.

It was not the original owner who was controlling this body but Sorokin's manifestation.

According to the route the dynasty fleet was taking, they should be leaving the Flickering World through the Black Star Army's territory. Hence, Sorokin had possessed this person many days ago and waited at this stargate, wanting to observe the size of the fleet Gaud was in. He could only come up with a detailed plan after obtaining enough information.

However, although he was already making preparations, he was still hesitant as to whether he was going to make the move or not. After all, the matter was too huge.

"If I do it, it's best to do it in the Black Star Army's territory, it'll be easier to frame it on Black Star this way… even if I fail, Black Star will be held responsible if something happens to Gaud in his territory."

Sorokin pondered.

Beep beep beep!

At this time, his communicator suddenly rang.

Sorokin took it out and glanced at it casually. It was an announcement the dynasty had made in the public channel, which forced a notification to pop up on every communicator.

According to the General Quantum Network Communication Laws, only the civilization that ruled over an area had the right to do this, not any other organizations, especially not consortiums.

"Tsk, how great would it be if this could be used for advertising…" Sorokin mumbled and opened the message.

With just one look, his expression froze on his face, and his entire body turned stiff.

"Gaud was attacked and is already missing‽"

Sorokin was stunned, his mind was filled with question marks.

Wait, what? I haven't started moving yet!

Which hero did my job for me‽

Marvelous!

I thank you!

The sudden turn of events astonished Sorokin totally.

Not only him, as soon as this enraged announcement from the Crimson Dynasty was publicized, the entire galactic society was absolutely shocked!

It all happened so suddenly. No one was mentally prepared!

Chapter 1229: The Thief Calling the Cops

Somewhere in the Emerald Star Cluster, a small fleet was slowly sailing. The symbol on the exterior armor of the spaceships showed that this fleet belonged to 'Ancient Snake', which meant this was the person who called out Gaud's Esper Ability during the welcome meeting, Lucie.

Lucie stood before the porthole at the bridge and looked into the galaxy outside the window. Beside him was another neutral Beyond Grade A who was also someone who frequented the black market.

"How long till we arrive at the Star Cluster's border stargate?" Lucie asked without turning around.

"About a day, boss," the captain hastily answered.

Hearing this, the neutral Beyond Grade A on the side sighed and said, "I don't think we can catch up to Gaud. Lucie, do you really have to spar with him?"

"I must find out what his ability really is."

"Sigh, he's a direct member of the dynasty. He can totally not accept your request. It's not like you can force him to fight, right?"

"Humph, I'm going to try it at least." Lucie looked determined.

After the welcome meeting, he had brought his fleet along with a Beyond Grade A friend and chased behind Gaud along the route they took, hoping to stop Gaud and ask for a spar.

Of course, he did this not just to satisfy his curiosity. As a secret member of a Super Star Cluster civilization, he received a secret order from the upper echelons that asked him to find a way to force Gaud to fight and verify if Gaud's ability was really [Energy Control]. This was why he kept chasing after Gaud.

The Super Star Cluster civilizations did not want to attack Gaud, but a test of this degree was doable. They all wanted to know Gaud's real ability.

At this time, the spaceship's radar suddenly rang.

"Alert! Spacetime stabilized area ahead. Hyperdrive will be shut down. Please stop hyperdrive mode or go around the area…"

The two of them were surprised.

Spacetime stabilized areas usually meant trouble. Neutral Beyond Grade As did not like getting into unnecessary trouble.

Lucie was just about to have the fleet go around the area when the spaceship suddenly received a message.

"This is the Crimson Dynasty exploration army. We're carrying out a check on all passersby. Please stop your ships immediately and cooperate. I repeat, please stop your ships immediately…"

Hearing this, Lucie told the fleet to stop. He looked outside the window and saw a line of defense formed by the dynasty's battleships that seemed to have locked up a large area ahead.

Three dynasty spaceships quickly approached and activated all kinds of detection devices to scan Lucie's fleet.

At the same time, a projection of someone who looked like a dynasty military officer appeared on the communication screen. He looked at Lucie and the Beyond Grade A beside him and said expressionlessly, "Please show us your IDs, spaceship sailing certificate, crew list, logbook…"

Though unhappy, Lucie told the captain to do as he was told. After all, his real identity was sensitive. Plus, he did not think there was anything he had to hide.

The military officer started checking through the information provided. Having realized that Lucie and the person beside him were both Beyond Grade As, his expression changed slightly. A strong sense of suspicion flashed past his eyes.

"What are you doing here? Why are you passing by this area? Where are you heading?"

"The dynasty needs to know that too? This is one of the routes leading to the border stargate station. Is it weird for me to pass by here?" Lucie frowned. "In fact, why are you guys locking this area down?"

"To search people." The dynasty military officer did not want to say much and went back to checking through the records.

At this time, he suddenly realized that there were records of tracking Gaud in Lucie's logbook. His pupils instantly constricted, and he yelled with an indisputable tone, "Everyone, leave the spaceship immediately for further checks!"

The neutral Beyond Grade A on the side frowned. "Isn't this too much? We're just passing by."

"I'll repeat myself one more time. Leave the spaceship immediately for further checks, or we'll do so forcibly!"

After that, the dynasty fleet at the back activated their weapons and aimed at Lucie's fleet immediately, clearly ready to fire at any time.

"Are you threatening me?" Lucie was annoyed.

The dynasty was powerful. Forget their officer not showing him any respect, how dare an officer attempt to order around him, a Beyond Grade A, like that? Did he really think Beyond Grade As were easy to mess with‽

Sure, as a neutral Beyond Grade A, he did not have the strength to mess with the dynasty. However, he did not think that just anybody in the dynasty had the right to disrespect him. Furthermore, with the Beyond Grade A Association behind his back, he was not someone who had absolutely no backup at all anymore!

Beep beep beep!

Just as Lucie was about to vent his anger, the communicator of everyone in the ship rang.

Lucie frowned, suppressed his anger for the time being, and took out his communicator. Only then did he see the dynasty's announcement that popped up, and his expression changed drastically.

Gaud is missing‽

Who did it? Who had the audacity to do it‽

Lucie's body suddenly shook. It suddenly occurred to him.

Wait a minute, I've been tracking Gaud all this time, wanting to spar with him…

If nothing had happened to Gaud, this would have been completely normal and would not lead to the dynasty's hostility. However, now that something had happened to Gaud, anyone who was related became a suspect. Although he was only trailing behind Gaud and did not even meet him, he was still suspicious in the eyes of the dynasty. The dynasty was not going to let go of any leads!

No wonder the dynasty military officer had that attitude!

Lucie knew how huge the matter was. This was not the time to be concerned about whether that officer disrespected him or not. He had to find a way to clear his suspicion.

If he did not cooperate with the dynasty's investigation, he had absolutely no doubts that the dynasty would vent their anger on him—this was not the time to be stubborn.

Lucie's rage instantly extinguished. He did not dare explode and could only tell everyone to leave the spaceship and obediently cooperate with the dynasty's checks. He was extremely frustrated.

Who's the b*stard that did this‽ Now I've been dragged down too!

"What? Gaud is missing? Someone really attacked him‽"

The Federation of Light's president, Bader, stood right up from his chair, stunned.

What, who's the idiot‽

No, this isn't an idiot. It's a maniac!

The Chief Elder was in dismay too. "Who's so daring as to really attack a direct member of the dynasty? This will affect the entire explored universe's situation, create a huge storm and cause problems for everyone!"

Bader frowned tightly and said with a deep voice, "If we didn't make a move, nor would the church… so it's most likely the Super Star Cluster Alliance's doing."

"Yes, it must be the Super Star Cluster Alliance." The Chief Elder nodded.

Before it happened, the two of them did not think the Super Star Cluster Alliance would dare act. However, when it really happened, to the two of them, since they did not do it, it could only be the Super Star Cluster Alliance!

Who gave them the guts! They dared to attack the dynasty's direct member today. Are they going to attack ours tomorrow‽

"The Super Star Cluster Alliance is getting cocky. Looks like the Tragedy of the Pinnacles was not an effective enough of a lesson. Looks like it's time to educate them again…"

Bader's eyes flickered.

He was actually secretly happy about the dynasty being the one that took the hit. He basically enjoyed the benefit of the dynasty being weakened without having to do anything. However, on the other hand, the dynasty represented one of the ruling civilizations, and the federation was also one of the ruling civilizations. Seeing their authority get challenged, he was still angry. These two emotions were not in conflict.

The Chief Elder thought for a moment and said with a heavy heart, "Although we're not the culprit, our specialty is assassination since we have the Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device, so we'll most likely be one of the suspects to the dynasty."

"Hmm, this is a problem. Therefore, we have to make a stand and actively help the dynasty investigate the case. However, we're not the only ones who have this kind of teleportation technology. Who knows if the Mechanic Emperor stole it? Plus, Black Star also has a type of mechanical suit that has similar teleportation abilities…"

"The Mechanic Emperor is suspicious indeed. He's still the federation's ally. If he did it, we'll be responsible too. As for Black Star…" The Chief Elder laughed. "Hehe, as long as the dynasty upper echelons have not gone crazy, it's impossible for them to suspect Black Star."

"You're right." Bader sighed and shook his head.

"Who the f*ck did this‽"

The Star Arc Civilization leader was dumbfounded, as if struck by lightning.

Although this was indeed something they wanted to do, the Star Arc Civilization leader knew that no matter who attacked Gaud, the Super Star Cluster Alliance would certainly be the dynasty's top suspect.

This was pushing them into the flames!

The Star Arc Civilization leader was puzzled. Possible suspects flashed through his mind one after another.

"I didn't do it. Is it another Super Star Cluster civilization? Who has the motive to do so… Modo‽"

Modo had exited the war long ago. The current battle had nothing to do with, so they would really not be afraid of doing something like this. Even the possibility of them wanting to burden the Super Star Cluster Alliance was not out of the question. They had lost the chance to compete, so they wanted to make the other Super Star Cluster civilizations fail just like them!

The brain of the Star Arc Civilization leader's spun quickly.

Was it the plan of the federation and the church, killing the dynasty's talent and framing them‽

Was it the dynasty's own plot, making Gaud go missing and framing it on the Super Star Cluster Alliance, giving their direct members a reason to participate in the war and using it as an excuse to start another Tragedy of the Pinnacles? If not, how could it happen so suddenly, and how could Gaud possibly not be able to resist‽

The Star Arc Civilization felt as if he had seen through everything.

This was a plot against the Super Star Cluster Alliance!

The three Universal Civilizations wanted them dead!

"We're too passive. We must do something! We can't allow the three Universal Civilizations to make things up!"

The Star Arc Civilization leader clenched his teeth.

You want to frame us? We know how to do that too! We must find a scapegoat that'll shut the three Universal Civilizations up!

Names quickly flashed through his mind, and suddenly, it stopped at one name.

This person did not lack motive, had more than enough ability to do it, and was very suspicious…

I choose you, Manison!

In just a few days, the dynasty's announcement swept over all Star Fields like a storm, causing sensations in countless areas.

Some thick and overconfident local terrorist organizations claimed to be responsible for it. Then, in less than a day, the dynasty's fleet arrived at their bases right away and wiped them all out, not leaving a single survivor!

Everyone could feel that, this time, the Crimson Dynasty was really furious!

Many organizations smelled that a storm was about to come…

The Beyond Grade A Association held an emergency meeting to discuss how to deal with this matter too.

In the large round table conference room on Planet Finn, the remote projections of many Beyond Grade As gathered and discussed intensely.

"How could this happen? It's so sudden!"

"It's only been a few days since we last saw Gaud, and now he's… sigh!"

"It has to be someone in the association who did this. Who did it? Step forward!"

They were infuriated.

Although Gaud was a direct member of an advanced civilization, what happened to him impacted the others too. They glanced at Gaud's empty seat from time to time, feeling sympathetic.

The meeting was as noisy as a wet market. This time, Sun Hunter opened his mouth. His thunderous voice covered everyone else's voices.

The others looked over and saw that he was staring at Manison with a suspicious expression.

"Mechanic Emperor, tell us the truth, did you do it?"

"Nonsense! Have you people been brainwashed by Black Star‽ I'm the president. Why would I possibly take the lead to violate the rules‽" Manison's face twitched. He was frustrated.

However, the others still stared at Manison and did not trust him.

Han Xiao had never stopped damaging his reputation. He had planted the seed of doubt in everyone's heart long ago.

Seeing this, veins popped up on Manison's forehead. He was extremely irritated.

No matter how much he explained himself, he would not be able to clear the suspicion. The Beyond Grade As would still suspect him… and Black Star was the one who caused all of this!

Manison glared at Han Xiao and almost wanted to fight him right here in front of everyone till he could vent all his anger out.

This time, Clotti slowly stood up and said with a freezing tone and expressionless face, "No matter who here caused Gaud to go missing, we will drag you out and make you understand the consequences of challenging the dynasty!"

As he was speaking, he glanced at Manison faintly.

The three Universal Civilizations' direct members usually did not speak, but now, they all made serious statements, expressing that they would catch the culprit no matter what. Many glanced at the Mechanic Emperor from time to time.

Manison's expression became worse and worse.

However, Sorokin was looking at Manison more and more gently.

If not because this was not the right time, Sorokin would have given Manison a thumbs up and praised him.

At this time, Han Xiao, who had not said much, cleared his throat, attracting everyone's attention.

"Gaud joined the association before this happened. He's also one of our members and is protected by the association. Now that he's missing, this isn't just an act of provoking the dynasty but also the association's authority. It's our duty to find the culprit. This is the purpose of the association!

"Therefore, I propose that the association shall announce to the public that we'll be investigating this case thoroughly. All Beyond Grade As will be searching for leads together and releasing a kill order across the universe!"

After he said that, whether sincere or fake, everyone expressed their approval and agreement.

"The vice president is right. The association must not be excluded!"

"Who dares target our member? Do they think we're all decorations‽"

Han Xiao's proposal matched how the majority of people felt. Some were worried that if they did not make a stand, the dynasty would take revenge like the Tragedy of the Pinnacles and threaten their lives.

Since Han Xiao had proposed to provide assistance, it would more or less direct the dynasty's hatred somewhere else so that they would not be the target for the dynasty to vent its anger.

Furthermore, protecting its members was one of the association's duties. Most people were glad to see the association make a move. This meant that they would receive the same treatment in the future.

The atmosphere in the room suddenly became united.

Clotti glanced at Han Xiao. His expression became slightly less cold as he nodded at Han Xiao and sat back down.

He had intended to acquire the association's help. After all, this many Beyond Grade As was an extremely powerful force. Gaining their help would largely increase the chances of finding the culprit.

Black Star was the dynasty's ally, and he had given them a lot of face by making the decision on the spot to provide assistance. Seeing this, Clotti agreed more with the dynasty's strategy.

Letting Black Star control the association was definitely a good thing for the dynasty.

Looking at everyone's reaction, Han Xiao maintained a serious expression on the surface while secretly heaving a sigh of relief in his mind.

This was the effect he wanted to achieve—having all the organizations suspect each other while not knowing that the true culprit was right under their noses…

He had completely muddied the waters.

Chapter 1230: Werewolf Becoming the Detective

The next day, with the Beyond Grade A Association taking the lead, all the Beyond Grade A organizations made a joint announcement. They claimed that this was an insult to the association and that the association would assist the Crimson Dynasty in finding the culprit to avenge Gaud.

As so many Beyond Grade As used their influence to search for clues, it instantly caused chain reactions in the Flickering World, affecting countless normal organizations.

The dynasty also made a public response based on the Beyond Grade A Association's announcement, praising Vice President Black Star's act of taking the lead, not at all mentioning Manison, the actual president. The difference in treatment was clear.

At the same time, the Beyond Grade A Association publicized a universe kill order. Every member chipped in some money, making up an outrageous reward as high as four billion Enas. Among them, the Black Star Army alone contributed half a billion, expressing their determination to find the culprit to the outside world.

The outrageously high reward immediately triggered the enthusiasm of the entire Flickering World. Almost everyone was guessing who the real culprit was every day.

Plus, the dynasty exploration army dispatched a ton of manpower and resources to search for clues, causing the focus of the Flickering World to shift. Although the Flickering World was still the main focus of the galactic residents, the search for Gaud also attracted a lot of attention. Other than fighting in the war, these organizations were also sending their men all over to look for clues.

The federation and the church did not only watch either. They both made announcements stating that they felt just as provoked as the dynasty was and would be sending forces to assist the dynasty in their investigation.

Organizations in the galaxy got questioned one after another. The dynasty collected all kinds of information related to the time surrounding the incident, but they had yet to find any clues.

…

In the remote conference room of the Super Star Cluster Alliance, a meeting was being held.

"… After this, there's no way the dynasty will put it behind them. They'll have to settle it no matter what. Never mind if they solve it, but if they end up not being able to solve it, they'll undoubtedly find a temporary 'culprit' to take the blame, save the dynasty's reputation, and vent their anger. We're the best choice for the dynasty."

The remote projections were all of the Super Star Cluster civilization leaders. Listening to the Star Arc Civilization leader speak, everyone had a serious expression.

At the start, they had doubted one of their own and asked if they did it as soon as they met, thinking this was the stupid act of one of their allies. However, after sharing their internal information, only then did they clear each other's doubts and unite on this matter.

The Star Arc Civilization leader brought up his opinion at the right timing, receiving agreement from many other leaders.

Everyone knew that their situation was against them. Whether the dynasty could find the real culprit or not, the Super Star Cluster Alliance would still very likely take the blame. The three Universal Civilizations would definitely not mind using this opportunity to frame them for a crime they did not commit.

The Tragedy of the Pinnacles was a bloody lesson. No Super Star Cluster civilization wished for that to happen again, so they had no choice but to let the three Universal Civilizations take the moral high ground among the public and toy with them. Therefore, the Star Arc Civilization leader spoke to their hearts.

The others nodded. "That's right. We can't sit and wait for our doom. We have to turn the situation around. Explaining ourselves won't work. It's best to find a clear 'culprit' and announce it so that the three Universal Civilizations can't use this against us… Manison is a suitable target."

Seeing this, the Star Arc Civilization leader heaved a sigh of relief and smiled with satisfaction.

He had brought this proposal up in the meeting because he wanted the help of the entire Super Star Cluster Alliance.

They would only have a higher chance of making Manison take the blame if they worked together; the Star Arc Civilization alone was not enough.

Now, the entire Super Star Cluster Alliance had come to an agreement to frame Manison.

…

In the Mechanic Emperor's secret base, Manison did not look happy. He hung up the call from the federation and frowned slightly.

"The dynasty's request is too much, telling me to show all my Felons, submit the logbooks of all the spaceships under my command, and even open up the memory database of all my mechanical soldiers for them to check… Hehe, they say they hope I can cooperate with the investigation, but they've actually already marked me as the main suspect. The only thing that's left to do is to bring me over and interrogate me."

Manison shook his head. He could clearly see that the three Universal Civilizations were also planning to use this opportunity to find out the coordinates of his various bases.

Although he did not do it, he was not so naive as to think he could stay out of it completely.

From Manison's perspective, the Super Star Cluster Alliance was most likely the culprit. The Super Star Cluster Alliance would certainly not be willing to sit and wait for their doom, so they would definitely do something about it. Manison, however, happened to be between the three Universal Civilizations and the Super Star Cluster Alliance and was the most suspicious. He was the most suitable sacrifice; someone was probably going to pin the incident on him.

"I must prepare some way to fight back and make the Super Star Cluster Alliance take the blame they deserve… Hmm, speaking of which, if they try to frame me, that should prove they're the real culprits."

Manison's thoughts were very clear.

If possible, he might have wanted to frame Black Star and teach that b*stard a lesson.

However, that was way too difficult to do, almost impossible really, so he could only forget about that idea.

…

In the Holy Accord organization's base…

"To think that this happened in the outside world…"

The various revived Primordial Ones gathered, watched the images on the communicator in Oathkeeper's hands, and chatted continuously.

"The times are so terrifying now. Even an Esper Ability as powerful as Energy Control has appeared."

"Pity, he got killed right after he entered the Beyond Grade A territory. Black Star is indeed right. The world outside is dangerous.

"This culprit messed up. No matter how perfectly he executed the plan, as soon as the dynasty figures out the Sanctums and revives Gaud, the truth would be revealed…"

The others nodded.

Oathkeeper, however, was a little worried. "If the dynasty can't find the culprit, once you revivors appear, the dynasty will suspect you guys too. This isn't good news."

Beiger sighed and said, "So, we're affected by the culprit too. We'll have to be more cautious when we decide to go public."

The people sighed and felt that the problem had just fallen down the sky out of nowhere.

…

In the Black Star Army Commander's office, Han Xiao said in his chair. Virtual screens hovered before him, displaying the activities on the quantum network.

Over the past few days, he had been doing this to pay attention to the direction this matter was taking. He had witnessed the spark he lit spread like wildfire, affecting bigger and bigger areas. He felt more and more like a mastermind behind the curtains stirring up storms in the universe.

"This is probably going to be the norm for some time. The dynasty will not stop till they find the real culprit, it's like a hornet nest."

At this time, his communicator suddenly rang. He took it out. It was surprisingly a call from Tarrokov.

As he picked it up, Old Tar's remote projection appeared in the room.

"Old Marshal, it's been some time."

Tarrokov nodded and said with a serious expression, "Black Star, I'll keep things short. The dynasty needs your help now."

"Go ahead."

"Gaud has been missing for many days. The dynasty has already searched all the records of the area within a month's duration before and after the incident, but we have yet to find any solid evidence. Therefore, the upper echelons have decided to form a task force especially in charge of this matter. The dynasty hopes to invite you to join as an expert, relying on your abilities to search for leads on the quantum network. What do you think?"

Han Xiao almost laughed out loud.

"Ahem, I'm the consultant of the three Universal Civilizations. This is my duty. I'm ready anytime."

"Okay. The task force will gather online in a day's time. If you can find any clue, the dynasty will reward you generously."

Tarrokov did not waste any time. He pointed out a few more things and hung up the call right after. He had been busy as hell lately; he really had no time to stay for a chat.

Han Xiao put the communicator down and smirked.

As a werewolf, I successfully got others to believe I'm the seer and even got voted as the detective!

By inviting him, the mastermind, to investigate this case, anyone could be captured but the real culprit…

Furthermore, he would even join as an expert, meaning he had a lot of control over the direction of the investigation. With his capabilities, doing something without anyone noticing was too easy.

This way, he had more targets he could frame…

However, forging clues was still risky. Han Xiao planned to be cautious and see how the 'suspects' reacted.

While he was being secretly glad, a notification suddenly popped up on the interface.

You have triggered the mission [Wanted Order]!

Mission Introduction: An important member of the Crimson Dynasty is suspected to have been ambushed and is now missing. The dynasty trusts your capabilities and has asked you to join the investigation team.

Mission Requirements: Solve the case and capture the culprit.

Reward: Depends on the Mission Rating.

What the hell?

Han Xiao's expression froze, he was stunned.

The situation now was still within his control, but the interface gave him a surprise.

Excuse me, I'm the one who did it. How can I still trigger this mission?

How am I supposed to complete it? By capturing myself‽

Chapter 1231: Werewolf Detective

"I wonder what the reward is."

Han Xiao was curious.

The mission requirement was to catch the 'culprit', not the 'true culprit'. He wondered if the mission was based on the truth or the dynasty's perspective.

If it was the latter, did this mean that as long as he could prove someone was the culprit to the dynasty, the mission would be considered complete?

If that was the case, he would have a chance to complete it.

No way was he going to turn himself in, not in this life. A werewolf would not kill himself, only frame others. That was the only way to live.

Han Xiao shook his head. He did not have the compulsion to clear out every mission. From the way he looked at it, it would be best if he could complete this mission, but it would not matter if he could not complete it.

According to the nature of the mission, the reward was most likely going to be mainly the dynasty's Contribution Points. If this was in the past, he would have needed them to acquire more blueprints from the dynasty. Now, however, with Jayz' treasure, the dynasty's Contribution Points were no longer valuable to him. The only thing that was still useful would be Political Assets.

…

The next day, Han Xiao entered the online channel of the dynasty task force on the dot. His remote projection appeared in a conference room.

As soon as he entered the room, projections appeared one after another, sizing each other up.

Han Xiao saw familiar faces like Clotti, Kant, Ravenlaude, and so on, as well as unfamiliar faces.

Before they started chatting, Tarrokov appeared, attracting everyone's attention. "Everyone here is a member of the dynasty's task force, so I won't waste any time. You all know what needs to be done. This team has gathered the experts of various fields. You guys are authorized to use all resources the dynasty has in the Flickering World. The dynasty only has one requirement; find the culprit and Gaud's whereabouts."

The next moment, Clotti said, "I'm the team captain for the task force for the time being. Any requests to utilize resources can be made through me. As for the detailed arrangements of your jobs, the vice-captain will decide."

This time, a tall, skinny dynasty officer stepped up, looked at everyone, and did a dynasty style greeting.

"You can call me Sherlock Dillman. I work for the dynasty's intelligence department. Pardon me for not sharing the details of my work. For this task, the upper echelons have sent me to be the vice-captain. I'll be in charge of the investigation work. My power alone is limited. Everyone will have to work together."

Han Xiao raised his brow.

Sherlock? The name sounded like a famous detective. This person was definitely not ordinary. He should be the dynasty's special talent in the investigation field.

The task force did not need muscles, only expertise. Therefore, Sherlock was the vice-captain, and the Beyond Grade As in the team were experts in different fields. In simple terms, the Beyond Grade As were acting as tools.

The rest introduced themselves one after another. There were three experts in charge of the quantum network search, Kant, Judith—the dynasty's direct member—and himself.

Sherlock allocated different jobs for the experts in different fields one after another. Very soon, he came to the three of them and quickly pointed out the requirements.

"… That's the situation we're in. The Virtual Domain is a key area of the search. Please find clues to the best of your abilities. I'll leave it to Your Excellencies."

Sherlock bowed. His attitude was very respectful. After that, he turned away and went to assign tasks to the others.

Seeing that Sherlock had left, Kant scratched his head and said, "You two are more than enough. I'm not a Virtual Mechanic, so why did the dynasty call me here?"

"The dynasty was probably just being nice and did not think you'd agree, but to their surprise, you're actually thick-skinned enough to really come," Han Xiao joked.

Kant's mouth twitched. "… Black Star, you'll lose me as a friend like this."

"Ahem, ahem, Your Excellencies, we've already received the authorization. We better get to work," Judith said from the side.

Han Xiao focused and received the quantum network authorization shared by Judith.

The dynasty had called them, the experts, of course, not to let them fight alone. The dynasty had opened up almost all the resources in the Flickering World for them to use.

For example, the three of them could command all of the dynasty's Virtual Mechanics in the Flickering World. The backdoor of the quantum network stations the dynasty had set up in the Flickering World was also open to the three of them. They could log in to the Flickering World's quantum network as administrators.

Furthermore, even some permissions of the dynasty's main artificial intelligence 'Heroic Soul' were temporarily given to Han Xiao and Kant, despite them being 'outsiders'. Other than to investigate the case, Judith's mission also included preventing the two of them from doing anything out of the line while they had such high-level authority.

Han Xiao logged into the network through the backdoor. His mind sank into the quantum network vision, and everything seemed so clear.

The network of more than half of the Flickering World was clearly laid out in front of him, all within his control. He felt like he had become the processor of the network. He had access to any and all data in every station. With so much power, he almost felt all-mighty.

"Nice." Han Xiao enjoyed it quite a lot.

No matter how strong his Virtual Intrusion ability was, he would still be a thief sneaking into someone's house. Now, however, it was like the owner of the house had directly rented the entire house to him; he could do almost anything he wanted.

Although Judith and Kant were beside him, with his abilities, he should be able to do some things without them noticing. However, the best thing to do for the time being was to observe how things were going first.

More importantly, with this level of authority, he could totally wipe out the possible flaws he might have left, erasing any evidence that could lead to him even more thoroughly, completely making his alibi legit.

Since the dynasty had given him this chance, he was certainly going to 'treasure' it.

Han Xiao spent the next few days submerged in the quantum network, carrying out the investigation with Judith and Kant.

Initially, Han Xiao thought he would not be able to find any leads. However, to his surprise, this was not the case. He discovered that the situation had taken a slight turn.

He did not have to do anything. The Super Star Cluster Alliance and Manison were already fighting with each other. They had started forging evidence and framing each other.

Both sides were doing it very discreetly. If not because he had the administrator authority of the Flickering World's quantum network, Han Xiao would not have discovered what the two of them were doing.

With the authority and his incredible Virtual Technology, their tricks did not escape his eyes.

Tsk, you guys didn't even do it, but you're already trying to frame each other…

Han Xiao's mouth contorted slightly.

Never mind if the others discovered this, but since he was the real culprit, from his perspective, this situation was like two villagers accusing each other of being the werewolf, while he, the real werewolf, was not suspected at all.

However, with some thought, he understood what the two of them were thinking.

The Super Star Cluster Alliance was afraid that the three Universal Civilizations might claim they were the culprit without any evidence, so they decided to act first. Manison knew this, so he took countermeasures. Hence, both sides immediately discovered each other's tricks, and they started fighting.

This is exactly why I muddied the waters.

The plan worked!

The two sides are trying to frame each other. Both are suspicious. Since there's no way the real culprit is going to be discovered, one side will definitely be deemed as the culprit by the dynasty…

Han Xiao's eyes shifted quickly.

Currently, the two sides were at a stalemate, unable to completely frame each other. This was where he could interfere.

Since the situation had developed in this direction, to him, framing someone else became easier than he had expected.

With his current level of authority, he only had to play a little trick, and the dynasty's judgement would be affected. He could easily help one side beat the other side, which meant that he was the one who could make the decision.

Who should I help? Han Xiao pondered.

He had always been against Manison, but on this matter, he planned to help the old man.

After all, Manison was the current Beyond Grade A Association president. If he took the blame, though his personal reputation would be damaged, the Beyond Grade A Association would be affected too. The impact would be very negative. If the president had secretly attacked the association's newest member, many members would feel threatened and much warier, which was bad for the association.

On the other hand, if the Super Star Cluster Alliance took the blame, it would have the opposite impact on the association. The Beyond Grade As would feel that Gaud's tragedy was because he was involved in the conflicts between factions. They would think that the same thing would not happen to them if they chose not to join any faction but the Beyond Grade A Association. It would instead increase some Beyond Grade As' sense of recognition for the association, which was beneficial for the association's growth.

Most importantly, the three Universal Civilizations and the Super Star Cluster Alliance were already at war. If they took the blame, the others would not be impacted.

Although the dynasty would not stop searching for the real culprit after, for the time being, letting the Super Star Cluster Alliance take the blame would minimize the risks for him.

Humph, old Manison, I'm not helping you; it's for the association.

Han Xiao curled his lips.

Mumbling a little in his mind, he started to execute the plan right away.

No matter how these two villagers accuse each other, in the end, I, the werewolf detective, will still be the one to make the call.

…

"It feels like a mysterious force is helping me…"

Inside the Mechanic Emperor's secret base, Manison had a weird expression on his face.

In the past few days, he had discovered that the Super Star Cluster Alliance was indeed trying to frame him. Hence, he retaliated.

Originally, both sides were only suspects, and there was no evidence. They had now added quite a lot of 'flaws' to each other's alibis.

In this silent war, Manison was actually at a disadvantage. After all, the opponent was the entire Super Star Cluster Alliance. Although his Virtual Technology was strong, he was alone.

However, not long ago, he discovered something abnormal. Some of the evidence the Super Star Cluster Alliance forged surprisingly suddenly disappeared, as if someone was helping him fight against the Super Star Cluster Alliance.

"To be both able to discover my conflict with the Super Star Cluster Alliance and interfere… is this the doing of the three Universal Civilizations?"

Manison thought about it.

The reason the three Universal Civilizations were doing this should be that they had confirmed the Super Star Cluster Alliance's guilt, so they did not want them to successfully frame him… Or thinking one level deeper, if the dynasty could not identify who the real culprit was, this would have been a strategic decision to accuse the Super Star Cluster Alliance.

If he went one level deeper…

Manison pondered and fell into a cycle.

…

About a week later, on the Crimson Dynasty mother planet, Urranrell browsed the report of the task force and rubbed the bridge of her nose.

"After the investigation carried out in the past few days, you guys have found a chain of evidence that seems to be legit, all pointing toward the Super Star Cluster Alliance… but this isn't the dynasty's initial intention."

Before her was the remote projection of an intelligence department upper echelon who sighed and said, "Whether it's real or not isn't important now. As long as this chain of evidence is more than enough to convince the outside world, it's enough."

"I want the real culprit and Gaud's whereabouts. Why else would I need the task force?"

"But time waits for no man. The real culprit did not leave any traces at all. If we keep investigating like this, the truth will remain out of reach. The outside world is already doubting that the dynasty can find the culprit. There are even people on the internet starting to admire this culprit who enraged the dynasty but still has yet to be punished… We can take all the time we want to find the real culprit in the future, but what the dynasty needs now is results."

Urranrell frowned slightly.

After the tricks Han Xiao played, the task force found a complete chain of evidence that led to the Super Star Cluster Alliance. However, after carefully verifying it, the task force knew this was forged, most likely by Manison. These two parties' act of trying to frame each other did not go unnoticed by the dynasty.

However, even though this was the case, after some discussion, the task force still decided to submit this result to the upper echelons. The dynasty upper echelons all knew about this, but still, this report was placed on Urranrell's desk.

Currently, the public opinion of the outside world was becoming worse. What the dynasty urgently needed was a 'result', real or fake. The target this chain of evidence led to matched the dynasty's war strategy too; the Super Star Cluster Alliance was the best target.

Furthermore, the Super Star Cluster Alliance was trying to create a 'culprit'. They were the ones that started this. If things were delayed for too long, they would succeed, and the dynasty did not want to see that.

Urranrell hesitated for a few seconds. She did not approve it immediately, sighed, and said, "Call Clotti and Sherlock here. I want to hear their opinions…"

This time, she paused and added, "Call up Black Star while you're at it."

Chapter 1232: Master of Tempo

Not long after, the remote projections of Han Xiao, Clotti, and Sherlock appeared in the office.

"Your Excellency Urranrell." The three nodded respectfully in greeting.

Urranrell nodded in return, pointed at the report on the virtual screen, and cut to the chase. "Is this the result of your work? I'm not very satisfied. You guys know this kind of evidence that'll only fool outsiders isn't what I want."

Sherlock stepped up, knowing he would be scolded, and said, "Your Excellency Urranrell, we've been trying to find the whereabouts of the real culprit, but the culprit left absolutely no flaws at all. We have found zero leads. While doing that, we discovered that the Super Star Cluster Alliance and Manison were fighting each other, so…"

He explained the progress of the task force's work. In simple terms, they did not find a single lead or clue, only a ton of forged evidence.

Seeing that the outside world was having more and more doubts, with the mounting pressure from the upper echelons, Sherlock had no choice but to reluctantly pick out some of the forged evidence and form an evidence chain using his deductive skills. Though fake, after he arranged and analyzed them, it at least sounded real.

Urranrell frowned. "Tell me the truth, how long do you think it'll take to find the real culprit?"

"… For now, never, unless we find a breakthrough." Sherlock sighed and shook his head.

"Do the two of you feel the same way?" Urranrell asked.

Clotti did not speak and nodded slowly with a poker face.

Han Xiao shrugged as if he was saying that there was nothing he could do either. "The person who attacked Gaud is very slippery and did not leave any clues. Even I have not found any leads. Based on the current situation, I feel that the dynasty can look at the matter from another perspective. Based on the perspective of benefits, the dynasty needs to find a suitable target to take the blame to calm this matter down for the time being, and the Super Star Cluster Alliance is perfect… Furthermore, since they're in such a rush to clear their suspicion, they might be involved somehow."

Urranrell shook his head and said, "But there'll definitely be people in the outside world who'll see through our plan. The Super Star Cluster Alliance won't easily admit it either. To the dynasty…"

Han Xiao interrupted her. "I know your concerns, but that is not important. The dynasty already lost when Gaud was attacked. All you can do now is save the situation as much as possible. What the dynasty needs now is results. Display its stand and muscles. You can't shut people up, but you can make them afraid. This way, even if someone mocks this result, they'll still be afraid. Thus, the goal is essentially achieved."

"But if we do this, won't the real culprit laugh all day seeing that the dynasty has accused the wrong side? Won't some people with ulterior motives think they can use the dynasty to their advantage because of this?" Urranrell said with a deep voice.

This was what she was worried about. Once the outside world saw through what the dynasty was doing, some people would think the dynasty was easy to fool, which would also damage the dynasty's reputation.

"That's inevitable, but a choice has to be made. Not everything can be done based on one's likings, right?" Han Xiao's skin was as thick as metal. He chuckled and said, "Plus, this might not be a bad thing. This will more or less make the real culprit lower their guard, increasing the chance of them showing flaws, which might one day give us a breakthrough."

An intelligence department upper echelon agreed and said, "His Excellency Black Star is right. We'll have to make a choice sooner or later."

Urranrell sighed, signed the order, and said, "Do it then."

The moment this proposal was placed on her table, Urranrell already knew that this was the silent agreement of the dynasty's upper echelons. They only needed her signature. Even the ruler could not do whatever she liked; she still had to compromise here and there. Her term was nearing its end. She could not dictate things anymore.

After signing the order, Urranrell felt weirdly relieved. She shook her head.

"Looks like the mission to find the real culprit can only be passed on to the next ruler. It's good, I suppose. I have an easier time."

Han Xiao's eyes flickered, and he said, "Actually, we might have missed something. There's another possible scenario that might explain how Gaud went missing. Did the dynasty consider it?"

The others instantly turned toward him.

"Oh? Tell us about it." Urranrell was interested.

"Is it possible that this is Gaud's own doing?"

Hearing this, the intelligence upper echelon laughed uncontrollably and said, "Your Excellency Black Star, we made this assumption long ago. We came to the conclusion that it's not possible. Gaud doesn't have a motive to do that."

"I don't feel the same way." Han Xiao shook his head. "Just because he's a direct member doesn't mean he's totally loyal. Is it possible that he only wanted to use the dynasty's resources to become a Beyond Grade A, then fake his death and free himself from the dynasty's restrictions and hide?"

After saying that, he subtly glanced at everyone and saw the unconvinced looks on their faces. He then added, "Of course, this is just speculation based on logic. I don't know Gaud's origins nor personality, so I don't trust him completely. Anyway, in my eyes, it's not completely impossible for something like this to happen. After all, it has happened before."

Sherlock thought for a moment and said, "Hmm, your suspicion makes sense. The amount of time Gaud has served the dynasty is too short."

Urranrell gave him a glare and said with a typical politician's tone, "You don't have to worry about that. The dynasty has its own system of checking through its direct members and won't take in anyone suspicious. The dynasty trusts the loyalty of its direct members completely…"

Han Xiao glanced at Clotti's poker face and understood that Urranrell did not want to continue this topic here.

He shook his head, smiled, acted casual and said, "Alright, I'm just saying."

Sherlock, however, continued asking. "I'm curious, why do you think Gaud might have faked his death? Something must have caused you to have that speculation. Did he act suspicious on any occasion?"

Han Xiao looked at him surprised.

Are you really that interested? I don't know if I should say that you have a strong desire for knowledge or that you don't know how to read the room. Didn't you see the look on that upper echelon's face?

Han Xiao suddenly realized that this was an opportunity to set the tempo. He fake-coughed and said, "One reason is that we could not find any clues at all. It's way too clean and doesn't look like he was attacked. Another… well, it's not that Gaud acted suspicious or anything, but I just happen to know someone who successfully faked his death, so it came to mind."

"Who's that?" Sherlock was curious.

"This person is quite famous actually. You guys definitely know him. It's that Limitless Financial Group's Sorokin."

Before the others asked anything, Han Xiao continued. "I coincidentally discovered his little secret. He's not as weak as he looks. I sensed danger from him. He might not be any weaker than me, yet he has always presented himself as being very weak. No one knows what his plan is. Plus, his soul's true age seems to be much higher than his current age. I tested him a bit and discovered that he might be a Beyond Grade A from history who possibly faked his death and lived till now using different identities…"

He kept some of the key information and exposed Sorokin's identity using ambiguous words, making the others doubtful.

"How do you know?" Urranrell wondered.

"This involves a certain Universal Treasure I acquired not long ago. It has special uses in the soul field." Han Xiao smiled and did not give any details.

Urranrell knew that Han Xiao did not want to share, so she did not continue asking. Thinking of Sorokin's actions in the past, she said, "If this is true, Sorokin definitely has a big plan. We'll have to adjust our approach for him…"

She would not instantly believe what Han Xiao said. However, Han Xiao's Political Asset count was quite high. He even had the bonus from the weird [Civilization Leader Slayer] talent, so what he said was taken more seriously.

Urranrell planned to secretly investigate Sorokin. Compared to Black Star, Sorokin was even more of an outsider.

Seeing this, Han Xiao stopped talking about this topic. He did not want to say too much; getting the dynasty interested in Sorokin was enough.

After all, making the Super Star Cluster Alliance take the blame was only the dynasty's temporary solution. They would continue to search for the culprit in the future. Therefore, Han Xiao wanted to use this opportunity to mess with Sorokin.

This guy was a master in knowing when to be a coward. He was way too well hidden, so God only knew what he was planning. If Han Xiao could expose him, it was definitely a good thing.

With what had happened to Gaud, once Sorokin's real strength was exposed, he would also be a suspect.

Although, from the way the Great Mechanic Han looked at it, Sorokin did not have any motive. However, at least he could disgust this b*stard…

Humph, who told you to plot against me secretly all the time. Did you think my little notebook is empty‽

"Alright, that's the situation for now. I don't have anything more to ask, so if there's nothing else…"

Urranrell was just about to end the communication. However, before she finished, she heard Han Xiao speak again.

"Wait, one last thing."

"… Go ahead." Urranrell clenched her teeth in her mind.

She thought Han Xiao was about to make another report, but saw that Han Xiao suddenly put on a serious expression and said,

"Your Excellency Urranrell, I'm now speaking to you as the vice president of the Beyond Grade A Association. I fully support the dynasty's decision to target the Super Star Cluster Alliance, but I hope this won't impact the association's members."

Hearing this, the others looked at Han Xiao with surprise and became serious too.

"Go on." Urranrell narrowed her eyes.

"I believe we both know that there are direct members of the Super Star Cluster civilizations hidden among the neutral Beyond Grade As. I am all for the dynasty's plan to target the Super Star Cluster Alliance, but I don't wish to see the Super Star Cluster Alliance's Beyond Grade As included in the revenge target. I'm not covering the culprit. I'm asking the dynasty not to vent its rage on some neutral Beyond Grade As who might be direct members of the Super Star Cluster civilizations. The culprit might be among them, but before the real culprit is found, they'll be protected by the association."

Han Xiao spoke with a serious tone that felt like he was going to fight for this even if he would offend the dynasty for it.

Urranrell and the others understood what he meant immediately. Black Star knew how the evidence had come about. Though he supported the dynasty's decision, he did not want it to become an excuse for the dynasty to target the Beyond Grade As. He was planning ahead.

You can beat up the Super Star Cluster Alliance, but you can't drag down the unrelated Beyond Grade As!

His identity swapped smoothly. One second ago, he was the dynasty's ally giving suggestions for the dynasty's sake, the next he became the Beyond Grade A Association's vice president thinking ahead for the association.

"You're really thoughtful." Urranrell had a complicated look in her eyes.

"If I don't speak for the association, when word gets out, how can I remain vice president?"

"… Alright, I understand. The dynasty's target is only limited to the Super Star Cluster Alliance's forces. Before we acquire solid proof, we won't target their hidden direct Beyond Grade A members. After all, the association has made a stand to help us too."

Urranrell sighed.

Seeing this, Han Xiao finally smiled again. He thought for a while and said with a chuckle, "Alright, if the dynasty doesn't mind, can you help me promote it? Just say that the dynasty initially wanted to investigate the neutral Beyond Grade As or even forcibly interrogate them, but I quarreled with the dynasty using logic, protecting the association's members, and in the end, convinced the dynasty of only targeting the Super Star Cluster Alliance. And please emphasize the fact that I played a crucial part in the dynasty's decision."

"…"

Although the others did not speak, they had the same looks on their faces.

Wow, just how f*cking shameless can you be!

"… Okay."

Urranrell took a few deep breaths to calm her emotions, or she was worried she might grab the cup on the table and throw it at Han Xiao.

Although she complained about how shameless Black Star was in her heart, she still decided to help him to promote, increasing Black Star's position and reputation in the association. There were more pros than cons to having Black Star control the association.

Having received a definitive answer, Han Xiao only then bade farewell with a smile.

After deactivating the remote projection, his sights returned to the office where his original body was. He heaved a sigh of relief.

"This tempo I've set has finally completely deviated the dynasty's direction…"

Han Xiao felt much more relaxed.

Luckily, he had enough Political Assets, which made making the dynasty accept his proposals easier.

If not because Manison and the Super Star Cluster Alliance were going at each other's throats, he would have had to spend more effort. It could be said that these two sides helped him to make things easier. He grabbed the main conflict and did not need to make any flashy moves.

Furthermore, making the association's members see that their vice president was so responsible he argued with the dynasty to protect their interests would increase his reputation considerably. This would probably make more people see the benefits of letting him lead them.

Even Han Xiao could not say how many birds he killed with this one stone. He only knew that the negative impact caused by Gaud being attacked was tremendously reduced. When the dynasty announced their plan to act against the Super Star Cluster Alliance, this matter should be considered settled for the time being.

As for the other unknown chain reactions, the only thing he could do was find out in the future.

…

On the other side, Urranrell and Clotti were the only ones left in the ruler's office.

Urranrell pressed her fingers subconsciously with a hesitant expression. After some time, she finally softly said, "Do you think he'll be the next Mechanic Emperor?"

Clotti glanced at her and shook his head.

"He's a hundred times more dangerous than the Mechanic Emperor."

Chapter 1233: Dust Settled

The state of the Flickering World was extremely tense, like a volcano that was about to erupt.

Ever since Gaud was attacked, the investigation of the dynasty attracted the attention of the entire universe. A month had already passed since then. The dynasty made such a big deal out of it but still had yet to achieve anything. Voices of doubt started to appear in the outside world.

As the public opinion was getting more and more intense, the dynasty finally made a new announcement, producing a full chain of evidence that pointed directly at the Super Star Cluster Alliance. The public opinion was stirred up once again.

The dynasty claimed that this chain of evidence was carefully verified. They had discovered that the Super Star Cluster civilizations planned the attack on Gaud. Hence, the dynasty used a harsh tone to question them, demanding these three Super Star Cluster civilizations open up their databases and cooperate with the investigation, or the dynasty would take further actions.

The Super Star Cluster Alliance originally wanted to make Manison take the blame, but their moves against Manison were defused by a mysterious force time after time. In the end, it led to the dynasty being one step ahead. Facing such an obvious method to divide them, the Super Star Cluster Alliance strongly denied it and refused to cooperate with the investigation. They also made an announcement claiming that the Crimson Dynasty was only using this opportunity to accuse them of something they did not do. Since the two sides were already at war, they even stated the unfair treatment the three Universal Civilizations had been giving to the Super Star Cluster civilizations all these years, hoping to gain the moral high ground in the eyes of the public.

The federation and the church came to support the dynasty too.

The two sides' conflict stirred up a storm in the galactic civilization. Most people trusted the three Universal Civilizations more, but there were some who saw through the dynasty's plan. However, even though they knew something was going on, the situation would not be affected.

No matter how much was said, fists still spoke the loudest. After a few days of the situation fermenting, the dynasty took further action. They claimed that since the Super Star Cluster Alliance had already attacked a Beyond Grade A, the agreement they had made in the past was considered voided. The dynasty announced that they would be sending direct Beyond Grade A members into the Flickering War. The federation and the church followed and did the same after.

The Beyond Grade A Association who had made an agreement with the three Universal Civilizations long ago expressed their support, claiming that it was the Super Star Cluster Alliance who broke the rules first.

Very soon, the direct Beyond Grade A members of the three Universal Civilizations were heading toward the frontlines one after another.

With the Beyond Grade As joining the war, the intensity of it rapidly escalated. The three Universal Civilizations penetrated one stronghold after another. The Super Star Cluster Alliance was losing territories even quicker.

Originally, the outside world thought the Super Star Cluster Alliance would also send in direct members, but that did not happen. The Super Star Cluster Alliance only relied on the troops they had to fight the direct Beyond Grade As of the three Universal Civilizations. Even though they were losing quickly, they still did not bring out any hidden Beyond Grade As.

Questions related to this matter got brought up and spread on the internet, secretly guiding more galactic residents to feel curious about. When this matter attracted enough attention, a 'mysterious person' finally appeared and explained the reasons behind it with so-called 'inside information'.

According to the information, the Super Star Cluster Alliance's direct members might be hidden in the Beyond Grade A Association, and one or more of them might be the culprit who attacked Gaud. The dynasty planned to thoroughly investigate all neutral Beyond Grade As. However, when Black Star found out about this, he went to argue with the Ruler, despite knowing it would put him at a bad spot in his relationship with the dynasty. He insisted on protecting the association's members' interests, stating that unless solid evidence was found, he would not allow the association's members to be affected.

After a negotiation that went on for days and nights, the dynasty was finally convinced by Black Star and decided to cancel this plan. Because of Black Star's hard work, the Beyond Grade A Association did not receive the forced investigation treatment. The public speculated that the Super Star Cluster Alliance's hidden members could only remain hidden because of this. Therefore, the Super Star Cluster Alliance would rather get beat up than expose their identities.

This news shocked countless organizations. In the face of the dynasty's furious investigation, almost everyone would obediently cooperate. However, Black Star dared to reject it. Furthermore, the dynasty clearly knew that the culprit might be in the association, but they still agreed to Black Star's request. Just how much weight did Black Star's words carry‽

The galactic residents were dumbfounded.

No wonder he became the first ever consultant of the three Universal Civilizations. The dynasty had to give him face even when they were furious!

…

In the Super Star Cluster Alliance's remote conference room, the leaders of the various civilizations had gathered. The atmosphere was tragic.

"We guessed right. The three Universal Civilizations decided to make us take the blame… Everything feels like it was planned!"

The Star Arc Civilization leader clenched his fists with rage.

Originally, Manison alone could not stop them. However, they discovered that a secret mysterious force was obstructing them and supporting Manison, slowing their plan down by a large extent.

The mysterious force that was helping Manison could only be the three Universal Civilizations!

"The three Universal Civilizations planned to make us take the blame. Therefore, after discovering what we were trying to do, they obstructed us secretly so that we wouldn't have a chance of escaping the accusations and would have no choice but get targeted!" a leader said with an enraged tone.

The Super Star Cluster Alliance guessed what the three Universal Civilizations wanted to do. They were afraid of taking the blame, so they tried to frame Manison. Manison knew what the Super Star Cluster Alliance wanted to do, so he tried to protect himself. The three Universal Civilizations were one step ahead. They guessed that the Super Star Cluster Alliance had guessed what they wanted to do, so they helped Manison. Their final goal was still to target the Super Star Cluster Alliance.

Their hearts were filled with a strong rage and sense of powerlessness. It felt like the three Universal Civilizations had knitted a huge net. They had nowhere to run and no way of struggling.

"What do we do now? The three Universal Civilizations have sent their direct members, and we have limited reinforcements. If we don't bring our direct members out, our loss is certain," someone said with a worried tone.

The people exchanged looks and all looked troubled.

Someone sighed and said what everyone was thinking. "Forget it, don't we all see the situation? Even if we bring our direct members out, we'd have no chance to turn the tables. We'd only be exposing their identities for nothing.

"Instead of that, we might as well let our direct members continue to hide their identities… Things are different now. Black Star is protecting the Beyond Grade A Association, so as long as our men's identities are not exposed, they won't be affected."

Everyone else nodded.

Without the Beyond Grade A Association, the three Universal Civilizations would definitely thoroughly investigate most of the neutral Beyond Grade As, and no one would dare object. The result of that would very likely be another Tragedy of the Pinnacles.

With the Beyond Grade A Association, the three Universal Civilizations could no longer do whatever they wanted. Due to Black Star's existence, the dynasty could not target the neutral Beyond Grade As without any consequences. This way, their secret members would also be protected.

"Black Star…"

Many civilization leaders felt complicated.

They did not like this guy at all, but what Black Star did protected their men. This was the indisputable truth.

The Star Arc Civilization leader sighed in his mind and said, "Our days are past. Don't make any unwise moves. The three Universal Civilizations are forcing us to expose our direct members. Once we fall for it, they'll have reason to carry out checks… Don't waste the safety Black Star fought for. Let them continue hiding in the association."

…

At the Beyond Grade A Association headquarters…

"It's all thanks to Black Star this time, or we'd all be affected."

Inside the round table conference room, the atmosphere was joyful. Many normal Beyond Grade A members had relaxed looks on their faces.

Ever since the incident happened, many neutral Beyond Grade As had been worried they might be affected by it. Now, the dust had finally settled. If not because this information got out, they would not even know that Black Star had argued with the dynasty and successfully protected their interests.

This really touched many Beyond Grade A. Only a leader who cared about the interests of his subordinates could be considered a good leader. Although they were not bosses and subordinates, it was exactly why they admired Han Xiao so much. Their sense of recognition increased too.

Facing everyone's enthusiasm, Han Xiao waved with a 'Sorokin smile' on his face.

"I'm the vice president. I only did what I should have done. Don't have to be so formal, guys.

"That won't do. I have to properly thank you!" Lucie suddenly bowed toward Han Xiao. He said with an appreciative tone, "If not for you, God only knows when I'd be free. You're being too humble."

He had been caught tracking Gaud by the dynasty, and the dynasty had captured him. Lucie had spent many days in fear and only been released not long ago.

With such an experience, Lucie knew more clearly than anyone that without Black Star's help and the association's protection, he would most likely have died in the dynasty's hands. There was no way he could regain freedom. Therefore, although he was a secret member of a Super Star Cluster civilization, the appreciation he was displaying now was not fake.

Lucie's words were recognized by the others. Everyone had a balance in their heart. By placing the president and the vice president on the two sides of the balance, they could easily see that Black Star had brought more benefits to the association than the Mechanic Emperor.

Putting those purposes and claims on paper aside, they had joined the association for safety and benefits. They were willing to have anyone who could bring more benefits as their representative.

Not only was the president, Manison, of no use at all, he even caused the association to be suspected. The comparison was way too stark.

"Alright, alright, don't get so excited guys. It's good to not be wrongly affected. At least Manison cleared his suspicion. Don't target him for today. Wait till tomorrow."

Han Xiao coughed and interrupted.

Although this was an act of building his reputation, this was enough. He was worried that if these members got too excited, he would be wearing a golden robe very soon.

Hearing this, the others had extremely dumbfounded looks on their faces.

Black Star spoke for Manison‽

Our youth has ended!

The others could not believe it. Manison glanced at Han Xiao with a complicated expression but was less hostile than before.

The others had no idea, but how could he not know? After the Super Star Cluster Alliance took the blame, he knew that the mysterious force that secretly helped him was most likely Black Star.

He probably did this for the sake of the big picture.

Manison sighed.

Back when Hila was attacked, he had helped Black Star. Now, Black Star helped him in return.

The two of them had been in conflict for many days, but at this moment, Manison uncontrollably felt an indescribable emotion in his heart.

Han Xiao noticed Manison's look too. He glanced at him and said, "What you looking at?"

"…Nothing."

Manison looked away, closed his eyes, and hid his emotions.

Han Xiao ignored him, looked to the other side, and saw Sorokin.

Sorokin did not have his signature fake smile on but instead looked very concerned and was dazing off.

From the way he looks, the dynasty has probably made moves secretly.

Han Xiao snickered in his mind.

Letting the Super Star Cluster Alliance take the blame was only a short-term solution; his mission was not shown as completed. However, he was not very concerned about it.

Things had settled. The storm caused by him secretly beating Gaud up finally came to an end for the time being. Overall, he was quite satisfied with the current situation—he had cleared the hidden threat and did not get impacted. This result was quite good.

After the people spoke among themselves for quite a while, Han Xiao suddenly put on a serious expression and said, "Guys, we can't be glad yet. The situation is clear now. The three Universal Civilizations will certainly win the war, and the Super Star Cluster Alliance won't be able to last long. Once they lose, they'll at least keep a low profile for many decades. When the three Universal Civilizations have more time on their hands, we'll be their next target!

"Don't forget, the three Universal Civilizations have been planning to do that since the start. It was only delayed by the Flickering War. We've been growing smoothly in the past years because the real obstacle has yet to arrive. Be mentally prepared… The day the three Universal Civilizations pressure us isn't that far away."

Hearing this, the others nodded with a serious expression.

…

After the direct members of the three Universal Civilizations joined the war, like the last straw, the battle rapidly became completely one-sided.

Most people predicted that the war would still go on for two to three years. However, due to the impact of what happened to Gaud, this duration was tremendously reduced.

In only eleven months, the three Universal Civilizations cleared out the Super Star Cluster Alliance's military power in the Flickering World's fourth exploration phase area, retrieving all territories.

The Flickering War ended with the Super Star Cluster Alliance's tragic loss. They invested countless resources and ended up crushed. In the end, they could not change their fate and could only lick their wounds in the dark.

The Crimson Dynasty redistributed the fourth exploration phase's territories. Those who participated in the war could keep their territory. Part of the remaining territory would be developed by the dynasty. The rest would be leased, sold, or rewarded to organizations who made contributions. This time, no Beyond Grade A ally was rewarded any territory.

Han Xiao, however, successfully bought the venue of the players' national war, Planet Milton. He stationed a regiment of the army on the planet and only slightly modified it, keeping the marks left by the players during the national war.

As the flames of war extinguished, the Flickering World temporarily entered a time of peace. The three Universal Civilizations started to deal with the aftershock of the war, recover the law and order of the various territories, and rest.

However, the impact of what happened to Gaud did not end with the Super Star Cluster Alliance's loss but continued to ferment where no one could see.

In this atmosphere, more than half a year passed.

On this day, the big event finally arrived for the Crimson Dynasty.

Urranrell retired. The new ruler had taken office!

Chapter 1234: The New Ruler

On the Crimson Dynasty's mother planet, Tarunamir Palace's biggest auditorium was the venue for all kinds of large ceremonies. All the handover ceremonies for the dynasty's rulers were held there and broadcast to the entire universe.

The venue was already set up. All the seats were filled, and most were remote projections. There were dynasty officials, leaders of their subsidiary allied civilizations, and the envoys of the federation and the church.

The Beyond Grade A allies were also invited to attend. They sat toward the back of the middle area, beside the dynasty's direct members.

Han Xiao sat between Kant and Milizaus. The ceremony had yet to start, and the three of them were chatting.

"Time passed so quickly. Urranrell is retiring too." Kant sighed.

"Now that I think about it, I've already met four different dynasty rulers. Although Urranrell wasn't the wisest among them, she was definitely the friendliest," Milizaus mumbled. As a member of the Ancient Ones, his life experience was rich.

"Well, it's the first time I've witnessed the change of head of state."

Han Xiao was quite interested.

In his previous life, players could not reach this level, so it was the first time he had experienced this kind of event himself. He found it refreshing.

Although I'm stronger than most Beyond Grade As in the universe, I'm still a curious boy.

At this time, Kant subtly pointed forward with his mouth and whispered, "See that? That's the new dynasty ruler. Any idea who he is?"

"Nope." Milizaus shook his head.

Han Xiao looked over too. The new ruler's seat was right beside. From Han Xiao's perspective, he could only see the new ruler's broad back.

Long before the handover ceremony, the personnel taking over the top positions in the dynasty had already been decided internally. The path had been set long ago. The new ruler's identity was kept a secret to the outside world only because of the dynasty's practice. The allies of the dynasty had no way of finding out before the day.

However, Han Xiao was not one of them—he knew who this new dynasty ruler was long ago.

After chatting for a while, the starting time of the ceremony approached. The voices in the venue gradually lowered, and people started to sit up straight.

When the time came, the entire place was already completely silent. The official hosting the ceremony stood up, expressed the dynasty's welcome toward the people there, and announced the official beginning of the ceremony.

The dynasty ruler's handover ceremony adhered to the civilization's theme completely. The process was short and simple, not flashy and complex like the Federation of Light.

After a few programs, it was finally time for the focus of the ceremony, the handover. Urranrell first had to give a speech.

Under the attention of everyone present, Urranrell walked up to the podium. She wore a simple dynasty uniform. Her hair was tied up high, and there was nothing unusual.

She looked around the venue for three seconds before slowly saying, "Today reminds me of the day I took the position as the dynasty's ruler. I was confident, proud, and firmly believed I could make the dynasty better. After so many years, the things I wished to do have already been achieved in different ways. I can proudly tell myself that I did not fail the beliefs I initially had, nor did I fail the dynasty.

"Looking back, we've accomplished many feats in many fields such as politics, economics, order of the universe, and so on. Our biggest achievement was the development of the Flickering World. This will determine the dynasty's rapid growth in the future. Along the way of the dynasty's growth, we were lucky enough to meet many friends and allies that share our philosophies. The dynasty has been able to achieve what it has achieved today not because of me alone, it's the result of the hard work of all of the dynasty's allies and friends. For that, I would like to show my sincerest appreciation to all of your contributions."

Urranrell bowed and made a dynasty gesture. Thunderous applause sounded in the venue.

The applause lasted for a few seconds. Urranrell straightened her back, raised her hand, and pressed down, signaling that they did not have to continue clapping any longer.

"Of course, the dynasty's path is also filled with obstacles. Our path has never been a smooth ride, and we've faced a lot of challenges.

"The dynasty rose from nothing. Our predecessors fought through hardships and disasters. In the end, it led us to standing as a universal civilization, becoming one of the foundations that maintains the order of our galactic society. The golden spirit of the dynasty has been passed on through generations. It's deeply scorched in our genes. We don't fear hardships. We solved many difficulties including the Intelligent Plaque, not only protecting our civilization but also the safety of the entire universe. What doesn't kill us makes us stronger.

"The trend of the world always is filled with twists and turns. There'll be new challenges and new opportunities in the future. I sincerely wish for all the dynasty's people to forever maintain the dynasty's spirit—no matter what difficulties lie ahead, never fear and face them with a smile.

"Today, my term ends. My duties will be smoothly passed on to the next leader of the dynasty, who will continue to carry on our divine responsibility of our civilization and the universe.

"I believe, the dynasty will reach new heights in his hands, just as I believed in myself.

"Last but not the least… long live the dynasty!"

Then, Urranrell bowed again. Her speech was not long, nor did she boast about her achievements. It was simple and clean.

Clap clap clap!

The next second, thunderous and deafening applause sounded in the venue, giving the highest approval and praise to a ruler who was about to retire.

Han Xiao clapped too. Memories of his interactions with Urranrell flashed past his mind as he sighed.

He had known her for decades. Putting aside their identities, they were more or less friends.

We'll probably rarely ever see her again in the future…

After a dynasty ruler retired, they would still continue to enjoy the same level of privileges and treatment, only they no longer had any political power. They would usually live on the dynasty's mother planet and hardly ever show their faces at any public events. After their life span ended, they could choose whether or not to upload their backup memories into the dynasty's main artificial intelligence, Heroic Soul.

The thunderous applause lasted a full minute before stopping slowly. Urranrell stepped aside, and that hefty new ruler walked up to the podium and showed his face in front of everyone.

This man's face was tough and angular. His hairline was rather high, showing his smooth forehead. He was tall and muscular. His huge chest muscles and biceps stretched out his uniform tightly, outlining his body shape. He was giving off an assertive and firm vibe all over his body, like a cluster of walking male hormones. He was confident, proud, and ambitious.

Marbruce Peel Stanson, the dynasty's new ruler. He used to be an officer in the dynasty's military. He then moved into the political field. Starting as a planet manager, he rose all the way to becoming the manager of a Star Cluster before moving to the central department of the dynasty. During Urranrell's term, he qualified to be trained by the Doyens, becoming one of the candidates for the next ruler. In the end, he surpassed everyone else and was confirmed as the next ruler.

Related information flashed past in Han Xiao's mind. This person was the dynasty's ruler the players in his previous life were most familiar with.

Urranrell was considered a semi-special case. Someone like Marbruce was actually the norm for the dynasty rulers. Of the many dynasty rulers throughout history, most had the same vibe.

Marbruce looked around, introduced himself briefly, and said with a serious tone, "I give my highest admiration to the contributions Urranrell has made in the past years. She's the key reason the dynasty stands where it stands today. For many years in the future, I'll be leading the dynasty. Just as she believes in me, I believe in myself too. I will not fail my duties and will lead the dynasty to continue forward…"

His tone was filled with a strong sense of confidence.

Compared to Urranrell's speech at the end of her term, his speech to kick-start his term was different. He analyzed the current situation, talked about his plans for the future, shared his political philosophies, emphasized on the growth route of the dynasty, created political goals for himself, and so on. It was much longer than Urranrell's speech, lasting for more than an hour.

If Han Xiao had to conclude what was said, the key words were 'strengthen centralized political power', 'reinforce area control', 'expand military power', 'encourage partnerships in multiple fields', 'reduce unnecessary resource wastage', and so on. This was quite different from the dynasty's policies when Urranrell was in office, emphasizing the dynasty's control over different fields.

Though they did not show it on their faces, many guests were already impacted by his new policies.

As the dynasty changed its policies, many forces would be severely impacted, and the firm philosophy of the new ruler was, of course, not good news for them. This was only a heads-up.

The eyes of many Beyond Grade A allies were also flickering.

"I didn't expect the new ruler to be so firm. I thought he'd choose to take the steadier path at the beginning of his term," Kant mumbled softly.

Milizaus shook his head. "What he said has definitely been approved by the internal members of the dynasty. Since they have no problems with it, it's not like us outsiders can influence who will become the leader of the three Universal Civilizations. His position is rock solid to begin with."

"Sigh, my honeymoon period with the dynasty is probably going to end."

Han Xiao shook his head and had this feeling.

Urranrell trusted him so much because they had experienced many incidents together, so they had built a trusting relationship. Marbruce, however, had never met him. Even if he heeded him, he would not be as friendly as Urranrell.

Nonetheless, it was enough. Having benefited from the partnership for many decades, the Black Star Army had already completed its rise. As long as he could maintain the current situation, he would be quite happy about it.

Everyone had their own plans, but they all looked like they were paying full attention to the ceremony, not showing anything on their faces.

Not long after, the handover ceremony finally came to its end. Urranrell and Marbruce shook hands firmly, announcing the completion of the handover of the dynasty's power. This moment would forever be recorded in the dynasty's history as a photo.

On Galaxy Calendar Year 740, February 15th, the ruler of the Crimson Dynasty changed. Urranrell retired, and the dynasty entered the age of Marbruce.

Two days later, the Federation of Light hosted a handover ceremony too. Bader retired as the president, and the new Federation of Light president took over. His name was Louis Rocky.

Two of the three Universal Civilizations changed their leaders in just a few days, attracting the attention of the whole galactic society. The majority of the galactic residents were speculating how this would change their everyday lives.

On the third day, Han Xiao finally received Marbruce's invitation to meet in private.

…

Han Xiao's remote projection appeared in the ruler's office. Marbruce was sitting on where Urranrell once sat, but his personal guard remained the same. It was still Clotti.

"Black Star, I've heard a lot about you." Marbruce gave a manly smile.

"Your Excellency Ruler Marbruce." Han Xiao nodded respectfully too.

"You're a legend in the universe. I've always wanted to meet you, and today, my wish is finally fulfilled." Marbruce's tone was liberal and somewhat friendly.

Seeing this, Han Xiao praised Marbruce in reply.

The way Han Xiao looked at it, as Marbruce just became the ruler, he had to meet with every important member of the dynasty. This meeting was just purely to get to know him; there was no special agenda.

The two of them chatted for a while before Marbruce brought up the key point.

"I won't make any changes to Urranrell's agreement with you, nor will the dynasty interfere with the territories that have been given to you. I also won't stop the support and assistance we've been providing to you. So, you have nothing to worry about."

"Hehe, I've always believed the dynasty is fair and just. I've never had any doubts." Han Xiao gave a formal and standard reply.

Marbruce grinned, suddenly changed the topic, and said, "About the issues with the Beyond Grade A Association, the dynasty is still discussing it. If you have any suggestions, feel free to bring them up to me anytime. I'll consider them carefully."

Han Xiao maintained his smile, nodded, and did not reply.

The two of them chatted for a while more before Marbruce expressing the intention to end the conversation.

As Han Xiao was just about to bid farewell, he suddenly looked at Clotti, smiled, and said, "Can Your Excellency Dark Lord escort me out?"

"Escort a remote projection?" Clotti frowned.

This time, he suddenly noticed Marbruce nod at him, so he led Han Xiao out of the room.

Closing the door, Han Xiao looked at Clotti and asked curiously, "How's Urranrell?"

"Her? She joined the Doyens," Clotti said. "Why ask?"

Unlike the Federation of Light, the dynasty's doyens had no power. They were only responsible for raising the successors of the ruler at most. It was really a place for retirement. The doyens hardly had any contact with the outside world.

"Just curious. Anyway, why are you still the ruler's personal guard?" Han Xiao smiled.

"Well, originally, Gaud might have taken over after he grew stronger. Now he's gone, and the other direct members all have their own tasks, so I can only continue as the ruler's personal guard."

Clotti shook his head. Although he still had a poker face, his tone had a hint of resignation.

While the two of them chatted outside the door, Marbruce, who was in the ruler's office, looked at the closed door, and a tint of worry flashed across his eyes.

"The ex-ruler really left me a difficult problem. You've given Black Star way too much…"

As the representative of the hawk faction, Marbruce did not like an ally who was too strong to be controlled, like Black Star.

However, for now, he did not plan to do anything to Black Star. He was going to maintain the current situation till further in the future.

Marbruce still remembered Bekorodi's report—Gaud, whom they had high hopes in, might have fallen into Black Star's hands. Although he was not sure if it was true, with the Mechanic Emperor as a prior example, he was already cautious toward Black Star.

Chapter 1235: Inheritors of the Underworld

After deactivating the remote projection and returning to his room, Han Xiao opened his eyes and sighed.

"Marbruce has quite a lot of thoughts about the Beyond Grade A Association… Well, I suppose it's his duty to do that since he's in that position, and he just so happens to need achievements at the early stages of his term."

Han Xiao shook his head.

Urranrell was so much better. Sadly, he had no choice but to adapt.

The benefits he gained in the past few decades of his honeymoon period with the dynasty was a crucial factor in the Black Star Army's rise. For various reasons, there was no way the dynasty was going to take these benefits back. Even if Marbruce wanted to, he could only follow the partnership agreement Urranrell had signed with Black Star. Therefore, Han Xiao had absolutely no need to be concerned about him. Even if he would not acquire any more benefits in the future, the benefits he would continue to gain from these agreements were enough.

You can't divorce me, so we might as well put up with living together.

While Han Xiao pondered about this issue, he left his office, came to the secret area inside Black Star Palace and walked into a combat training room.

Clank!

As soon as he entered, he saw a tall mechanical suited warrior fighting two virtual opponents. Every step this warrior took, the entire room shook.

As soon he saw Han Xiao, this mechanical suited warrior stopped and stood in a respectful manner.

Han Xiao smiled. "Working hard, I see. Come out and let me see your progress."

The mechanical suit split up from the middle, showing the user inside. It was Lothaire.

Ever since Lothaire assassinated Modo's leader, Han Xiao had hidden him, and he had been training all this time. This mechanical suit was training assistance equipment Han Xiao had specially made for Pugilists. It had zero combat capability and would instead add an extremely high load to the user, enhancing the effects of the training.

Almost a decade had passed, and Lothaire's strength had been growing steadily, unlike those officers who had been stuck in the same place in Calamity Grade. Clearly, Lothaire had more potential. Han Xiao had high hopes for him.

Han Xiao raised his hand. Golden sparks of electricity jumped around his fingers. He placed his hand on Lothaire's shoulder, sending a highly-stimulating electrical stream into Lothaire's body.

Lothaire's body shivered, but he endured the pain and remained still as Han Xiao electrocuted him.

Han Xiao only lifted up his hand after quite a while. Seeing the combat information, he smiled and said, "You've become stronger again than the last time I checked, but your energy is still your weakness. You need to make up for it…"

He pointed out a few things. Lothaire listened carefully, writing down Han Xiao's suggestions on his training schedule from time to time.

This was an assistive training method Han Xiao had come up with. By looking at the person's attributes through the interface, he could point out a direction the person should take. Since he could see all of their attributes, he could always give very constructive suggestions that not only gave them a clear direction but even clearly conveyed how much they had grown, making them more motivated to train.

Through this method, he could help others grow. Han Xiao had already used it on some important officers in the past years. After realizing just how incredibly effective it was, Lothaire treasured all the opportunities he could learn from Han Xiao.

After giving the suggestions, Han Xiao patted Lothaire's shoulder, smiled, and said, "Keep up the good work. You might be the next Beyond Grade A of the army. Then, if you want to found your own force outside, I'll support you."

Lothaire shook his head. "I'll always be your blade in the dark."

Even if he could become a Beyond Grade A, it would be thanks to Han Xiao's teaching. Lothaire was very appreciative of this, and he was not so cold-blooded that he would forget how much Han Xiao had helped him, or he would not have joined the army to repay Han Xiao.

"I appreciate the thought."

Han Xiao was quite glad. He said a few more words before leaving the room.

Han Xiao followed the corridor in the base into another room. Aurora sat in the room with her legs crossed. Vital energy filled her body. She was training her energy. The moment she saw Han Xiao, she joyfully pounced over.

Pa!

Han Xiao pressed onto her head, stopping her a few feet away. He sighed and said, "Come on, how old are you? On Planet Aquamarine, you're already old enough to be someone's grandma."

"Humph, I don't care. I'm forever eighteen!" Aurora became unhappy right away. Don't mention my age and we're still good friends.

"Alright, alright, let me see how much your body… ahem, your strength has grown." Electric sparks appeared on Han Xiao's fingertips, and he poked Aurora's forehead with it.

Combat information appeared on the interface. Han Xiao mainly looked at her Energy Rank and maximum energy, then nodded in his mind.

In the past decade, Aurora had been harvesting the Holy Light Seeds and accumulating energy. Not having any growth limit was really an incredible trait, her strength had been growing steadily.

Furthermore, Aurora did not even have to study her abilities too much. The information the last generation of the two sisters left in the Esper Ability was basically like an ability tree that had already matured; she inherited it directly.

What's hacking? This is hacking!

Han Xiao was bitter.

He had had his eyes on the life energy for quite some time and used [Energy Analysis] on Aurora long ago.

The results were just as he expected. He could control this type of special energy during the duration of the Character Summon Card, but he lost it after the duration ended. However, part of the understanding of the very nature and principles of the life energy remained in his mind, which would help in studying it afterward.

The [Perfect Energy Affinity Physique] he had obtained from Gaud played a big role in this, largely increasing Han Xiao's efficiency in analyzing the life energy. Although creating life energy with machinery was still extremely difficult, at least he had a direction.

Han Xiao's current focus was Jayz's technology treasure trove. It was the most valuable thing to study. Before he depleted the essence of Jayz's treasure, he was not going to spend too much time studying other things.

These thoughts flashed past his mind in a second. Han Xiao removed his hand, smiled, and said, "You've been working hard lately, no less than your sister."

Hearing this, Aurora smiled brightly. She loved hearing Hila, Ames, or Han Xiao praise her.

At this time, Aurora suddenly thought of something and said, "By the way, sis told me to ask you to go to the Underworld dimension a few hours ago. Go and take a look."

"Why did you only tell me now?" Han Xiao gave her a stare.

"Sis said so… She said to tell you later if you're busy. It's nothing urgent anyway," Aurora murmured softly, tapping her index fingers on each other.

"Got it. Her skin is probably itchy and needs a beating. Alright, I'll go eat her up now."

Han Xiao waved, activated the King, and disappeared.

The next moment, he was in the Underworld dimension.

Compared to the last time he came, the size of the Underworld seemed to have expanded quite a lot.

"Where is she?"

Han Xiao looked left and right and did not see Hila, so he lifted his leg and stomped the ground.

"Come out, Onicelu!"

As soon as he said that, Onicelu came out from under the ground.

"You're finally here. Hila has been waiting for you."

"Where is she? Let's start the fight quickly. I've brought all the tools. I still have other things to attend to." Han Xiao took out a ton of weapons and looked around.

Onicelu sighed. "She's not asking for a fight. The Underworld was fully repaired yesterday. Hila plans to wake up all the Hero Spirits and is worried about something happening, so she wanted to ask you to watch her do it."

"Oh, so this is why she called me here."

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled. He waved his hand and stowed the weapons away. He calculated in his mind. Judging from Hila's charging speed, repairing the Underworld would indeed take about a decade.

He still remembered that he had a mission called [Inheritors of The Underworld]. Once the Underworld recovered to its peak, he would receive the [Mark of The Underworld] reward. That would enable him to use the Underworld's powers to a certain extent and send souls into the Underworld.

"The Hero Spirits are all sleeping in my energy core. Hila is already waiting there. Take my hand, I'll guide you there." Onicelu raised her arm.

Han Xiao grabbed her hand. The next second, he felt a space energy erupting around him, and one moment later, he already arrived at a place that looked like an underground cave.

At the middle of the cave was a dimly lit white energy sphere that had dark-red patterns on its surface like blood vessels. The patterns were even moving slightly.

This was the energy core of the Underworld. Only the dimensional consciousness entity could lead the way and enter easily. The part of the Underworld outside was like Onicelu's skin, and coming here was like entering her body.

This was Han Xiao's first time entering, while Hila had already come in and out countless times. She was resting with her eyes closed sitting beside the energy core. As soon as Han Xiao arrived, she sensed it. She opened her eyes and looked at him.

"Shall we?"

Hila had no intention of chatting and cut to the chase.

Seeing Han Xiao nod, dark red death energy flowed out from Hila's palm into the energy core. Onicelu, who stood to the side, also controlled the Underworld to work together.

Ohm!

As the place started to shake slightly, the energy core became brighter.

When their sights were filled with a blinding light, an enormous beam of light suddenly rushed up, penetrating the thick ground and the grayish sky.

Han Xiao looked up at the beam of light. Through his sharp senses, he noticed that blurry silhouettes were being shot into the sky along with the beam of light. In his senses, soul presences appeared one after another.

The beam of light extended all the way up until it hit the interior wall of the Underworld. It then spread in all directions. It looked like a fountain that connected the ground with the sky. Awakened Hero Spirits fell like rain, landing on the Underworld's ground.

This process lasted for more than ten minutes. Very soon, the quiet and unpopulated Underworld became boisterous. Hero Spirits were everywhere on this desolate land.

The light on all the Hero Spirits gradually faded. From the outside, they surprisingly looked no different from living individuals. They were all looking around with confusion, seemingly yet to regain focus after their long sleep.

"It was very successful. Let's go meet them."

Onicelu was relieved. She led the way to fly out. Hila and Han Xiao followed right after.

The three of them flew up into the sky. All the Hero Spirits sensed it and looked up at them. Seeing Onicelu's familiar face, almost everyone looked like they were searching through their memories.

Not long after, seven unique Hero Spirits dashed into the sky and stood around the three of them.

"Onicelu, the Underworld has recovered? Have Nerkese and Eros returned‽" one Hero Spirit asked hastily.

"Hmm, it has recovered but not because of the two sisters. Let me introduce you. This is the new Lord of Death, Hila. She inherited Nerkese's ability and is now the new master of the Underworld."

Onicelu then pointed at the seven Hero Spirit and said, "These seven are the seven Hero Spirit Kings of the Underworld. They were all Beyond Grade As and are the seven strongest beings of the Underworld."

Hearing this, Han Xiao sized the seven of them up and realized that they were all Primordial Ones whose names had been recorded in history. He nodded in his mind.

No wonder those revivors of the Holy Accord organization once said that not many people were willing to mess with the life and death sisters during the exploration era—they could summon seven Beyond Grade As in every fight who were unkillable. Who could deal with that?

Even now, this level of strength would be the top tier in the universe.

However, Onicelu was not finished. What she said next made Han Xiao's heart skip a beat.

"Although the Underworld is a place for souls to rest, there are way too many Hero Spirits, so we created a management structure to have the seven Hero Spirit Kings help manage the others. There are 3,600 Calamity Grades, 1.8 billion Grade Bs, and billions of other Hero Spirits. They are all the residents of the Underworld."

Han Xiao subconsciously took a deep breath.

What the f*ck‽ That's so many souls!

This was a total of 3,600 Calamity Grades. It was a horrifying force anywhere! Without the players, the Underworld would be the biggest undead army!

He could indirectly feel how bloody the exploration era war was just from this number. Some of these souls were collected by the two sisters, and others were ones who requested to enter the Underworld and gain eternal life.

While he was being shocked, the seven Hero Spirit Kings were sizing Hila up. Feeling the death energy Esper Ability on her, they knew Onicelu was telling the truth, but they were troubled.

Never mind working for the two sisters, they now had to work under a new master. They were not very willing to accept it deep in their hearts, but they had no choice, so they were quite bothered.

However, since they were willing to enter the Underworld for eternal life, it meant they cared more about their lives than working for someone else. Therefore, they were not bothered for long before they convinced themselves. Furthermore, Nerkese and Eros had committed suicide, which really ripped off these Hero Spirits who trusted these two sisters. They were all not happy about it.

This time, the seven Hero Spirit Kings turned to Han Xiao and looked confused.

"Who's this guy then? The new Lord of Life?"

"No, my name is Black Star. Actually, I…"

Before he finished introducing himself, he got interrupted by Hila.

"I'm all of your boss, and Black Star is my boss," Hila said calmly. "You guys can call him big boss. You're all now his men."

"What's with you?" Han Xiao was surprised.

Hila turned to him. Her tone became gentler as she said, "My powers are yours. These Hero Spirits are for you to command too."

"I'm quite touched by you saying that, but…" Han Xiao pointed at the seven Hero Spirit Kings, who looked unhappy. He sighed and said, "You didn't have to be so direct. At least think about how they feel…"

They're the Primordial Ones who once stood at the top of the pyramid, yet you're giving them to me like cargos. Don't they want face?

A Hero Spirit King who had a bad temper was annoyed. "New Master of the Underworld, we're indeed controlled by you, but you have to respect us too. Even your predecessor did not dare speak to us like this… I'll let this time go, but don't do it again.

"However, we'll never listen to anyone else. With us, you're among the strongest people in the universe. You don't have to work for anyone anymore. If you want, we can get this guy called Black Star right away and give him to you to do whatever!"

Han Xiao was unhappy.

This little b*tch, trying to mess with my relationship with Hila as soon as he came out. If not because you don't have a physical body, I'd make sure you live the rest of your life eating from a tube.

Hila frowned and said with a deep voice, "Shut up. You can beat it if you're not happy, or I can send you back to sleeping forever."

The expressions on the seven Hero Spirit Kings' faces froze. They exchanged looks and were shocked.

Even the previous two sisters treated them with respect and would not offend them because they were the ones controlling their bodies during battles. The two sisters could only revive them temporarily but not control them in combat, so they could totally choose not to fight for them.

However, this new master was completely different. It was like she did not care about their strength at all. She supported her boss even though it meant she would offend them…

You're a Beyond Grade A!

The seven of them looked back and forth between the two of them. Suddenly, they thought of something, and their expressions became enigmatic.

Hehe, we've seen a lot of things and are very experienced. In this situation, either you owe him many favors, or the two of you… hehehe. These are the only possibilities for why you're so loyal.

This time, Onicelu eased the tension and said, "You guys have slept for too long. Many generations have passed. Black Star is one of the strongest people in the universe. You guys might not be able to defeat him even if all of you fight him at the same time… Plus, the Underworld now only has the Lord of Death. The Lord of Life is still growing. Therefore, you guys can't have physical bodies and can't fight."

Hearing this, the seven of them immediately threw away the thought of being tough and laughed.

"Hahaha… we were just joking with you, man."

"That's right. Don't be so serious."

"I can tell brother Black Star is talented and has a bright future just by looking at him. It's our honor to work for him."

"Exactly, if not because we can't revive for now, we would showcase what we've got right here!"

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes, and his lips twitched.

That's it?

What bullsh*t Hero Spirit Kings? You sounded so noble and all, but you're just a group of people who gave up all your dignity to not continue sleeping! I shouldn't have had any hopes!

Although he detested the personalities of these Hero Spirit Kings, he had to admit that the Underworld was extremely powerful. This was the biggest inheritance the two sisters had left, and the life and death Esper Abilities were the keys.

However, for now, since Aurora had yet to become a Beyond Grade A. The Underworld could not be put to use yet. Furthermore, reviving them required energy and had a time limit.

Compared to the Sanctums, the biggest specialty of the Underworld was that it was not only limited to the Beyond Grade As. Plus, it would not reduce their strength much.

However, the disadvantage was also very clear. Those who took this path could only work under the master of the Underworld forever and no longer had freedom.

While the few of them chatted, the countless Hero Spirits on the ground started to regain focus too. They started to modify the Underworld using the core energy.

On the desolate black earth, buildings rose from the ground one after another. The Underworld quickly became prosperous.

At this time, a notification popped up on Han Xiao's interface.

[Inheritors of The Underworld] Completed!

You have received 50,000,000 EXP and +20 Onicelu Favorability.

You have received [Character Summon Card - 'Underworld' Onicelu].

Character Summon Card - "Underworld" Onicelu: [Thousand Soul Stream] - Become immune to all mind attacks. At the same time, absorb any mind attacks to recover energy and health. Uses: 0/1.

You have completed the bonus mission requirements.

+40 Onicelu Favorability.

You have received ability [Mark of The Underworld]!

Chapter 1236: A Path Never Thought of Before

This mission is finally complete. It wasn't even difficult, just took too long.

Han Xiao looked down at the back of his palm. A mark that was the same as the one on Hila's hand was slowly appearing.

He looked up and saw Onicelu smiling at him.

"This is the Mark of the Underworld. You can use some of the Underworld's power with it. Without your help, the Underworld would never have recovered to its peak. I don't have anything I can repay you with but this."

"I know. I'll make good use of your body… ahem, the Underworld."

Han Xiao coughed.

The Underworld was Onicelu's body, so was this her saying, "I'll repay you with my body"?

No, no, I'm a pure person…

Suppressing these weird thoughts, Han Xiao sensed the Mark of the Underworld. Black streams of air flowed out from the mark and circled around his hand.

This was the second secondary dimension that had a connection with him. Comparatively, the link with the Void Dimension had a higher level, as he could only use part of the Underworld's power with this mark. Nonetheless, it gave him some bonuses.

At the same time, with this mark, he could choose to have the Mark of the Underworld absorb the souls of the enemies he killed and turn them into Hero Spirits.

When Aurora stepped into the territory of the Beyond Grade A and the Underworld regained the ability to revive souls, he should be able to summon Hero Spirits using the Mark of the Underworld. However, it would still consume Hila and Aurora's energy.

This means that the more Hero Spirits the Underworld has, the more I'll benefit from it, so I'm not working for free.

Han Xiao mumbled in his mind and looked at the other reward, Onicelu's Character Summon Card.

The effects of [Thousand Soul Stream] were outrageous; being able to be immune to all mind attacks and even absorb them was completely overpowered.

Although he could only use it once, it was undoubtedly a trump card.

While he was looking through the mission rewards, the Underworld was undergoing a big change. Hila was speaking to the seven Hero Spirit Kings.

After the seven of them accepted their position, coming to agreements became much easier.

"From today onward, you're all members of the Black Star Army, understood?" Hila said.

"No problem. His Excellency Black Star's words are absolute!" the seven of them promised. The change in their attitude was very smooth.

"Are they always like this?" Han Xiao was curious.

Onicelu whispered, "The former masters did not have any plans to expand the Underworld. Among the seven of them, two of them challenged the two sisters, got killed, enslaved, and tortured for a very long time. Their edges were rounded long ago. Three of them fled here, and two begged the two sisters to take them in… So, you can imagine what kind of people they are."

"Damn…" Han Xiao's mouth twitched.

From the actions of the two sisters, they were carefree and never thought of being responsible. The Underworld only had so many souls because these souls wanted to obtain eternal life. They did not care if the two sisters were reliable or not and begged to join, giving up their freedom. Clearly, they did not have much dignity left.

This explained how creating platforms was better than selling products.

The nature of all fortune was planting and harvesting leeks.

Although the seven Hero Spirit Kings joined for different reasons, after so many years, they could no longer let go of their eternal life. They did not dare offend the master of the Underworld. Plus, they were looking forward to the Lord of Life reviving them so that they could tour the outside world.

Currently, the strongest among the Hero Spirit Kings was a Primordial One called Rega. According to data, his Energy Rank was around 65,000 Ona, not a peak Beyond Grade A but above average. With an undead body, his actual strength would increase quite a bit.

Han Xiao thought for a moment, stepped forward, and asked, "Do you guys know anything about the Sanctums?"

In the past, he originally wanted to ask about the Sanctums from the Hero Spirits in the Underworld. However, he had already established a partnership with the Holy Accord and had been searching for the 'keys' of the Third Sanctum, so he no longer needed the Hero Spirits' help.

Plus, these Hero Spirits definitely did not know as much about the Sanctums as the Holy Accord, so Han Xiao was just asking to try his luck.

"Sanctums? I didn't expect you… to know about this, big boss."

The seven Hero Spirit Kings all looked over with a slightly complex look on their faces, as if they were reminded of something in the past.

"Before we entered the Underworld, there was a rumor among some of the Beyond Grade As. It was said that some people could occasionally sense a kind of special existence outside the spacetime of the universe. Some called it a Sanctum. However, most people never experienced such things, so there was no way to verify if it was true. It was always seen as a fake rumor," a Hero Spirit King said.

"Some said the Sanctum is the staircase to the next level; some said that all the technology and knowledge of the universe is hidden in the Sanctum; some even said the Sanctum can bring people back to life. No one knows what's real and what's not," another Hero Spirit King said.

Rega sighed, shook his head, and said, "We don't know much really. However, during the exploration era, I remember that there was a group of Beyond Grade As who founded an organization and apparently wanted to use the Sanctum to revive in the future. We didn't think that'd work, so we didn't join them. They should have failed by now."

Han Xiao raised his brow. "What's the name of that organization?"

"The Holy Accord, I think."

"…"

Han Xiao's mouth twitched. He did not know what expression to show.

I knew it. They did not fail at all. Their plan was a huge success!

Of course, most of the merit goes to Oathkeeper. God knows why these revived Primordial Ones were so lucky to find such a reliable partner.

I'd better not tell this to these seven Hero Spirit Kings… They'll probably never be able to be revived by the Sanctum after entering the Underworld. If they find out about this, they probably die of regret.

It's better to let them think the Holy Accord organization has failed. Keeping this cruel truth from them will keep these leeks healthy…

No matter what, these Hero Spirits also achieved eternal life in another way. Although they took different paths, they reached the other side all the same.

All kinds of thoughts flashed through his mind. Han Xiao suppressed these thoughts and listened to Hila and the seven Hero Spirit Kings communicate.

The few of them chatted for a while. The seven Hero Spirit Kings bade farewell and left to manage the Hero Spirits.

Seeing that the seven of them had left, Hila turned and asked, "What do you think of them?"

Han Xiao smiled and said, "Although they don't have the best personalities, their strength is real. The Underworld is an extremely powerful force. Although it can't be used now, Aurora will eventually become a Beyond Grade A with how quickly she's becoming stronger. By then, there won't be many people in the universe who can be a threat to you two… Speaking of which, the Underworld is like an exclusive Universal Treasure for the two of you. Tsk, I'm quite jealous."

In Han Xiao's previous life, Hila had no chance to accept this inheritance, so it was wasted. This time, however, as long as no accidents occurred to the two of them, they would be more than strong enough to be in the top tier in the explored universe.

As soon as Aurora became a Beyond Grade A, these two sisters would become tremendously stronger.

"What about compared to you then? Will I be able to defeat you?" Hila's eyes were glowing.

"What, you want to overtake me?" Han Xiao joked. "Don't dream of it. I'll still crush you."

"Humph, I don't believe it." Hila grinned. "You never know till you try."

She secretly decided not to do anything else after she returned other than push Aurora to train harder so that the Underworld could be used sooner.

After the official matters were over, Hila sensed the strong and firm presence of Han Xiao and felt an itch.

"You have nothing to do now, so you want to do it with me?"

"The Underworld has just recovered. You still have many things to do. It's best for you to make a list for the Hero Spirits. Leave the sparring for next time." Han Xiao waved.

"Alright." Hila had no choice but to endure the itch.

Han Xiao said a few more things, put on the King suit, and left the Underworld.

Returning to the office in Black Star Palace, Han Xiao changed into casual clothes, summoned Phillip, and added the Underworld's data into the confidential plan documents.

While recording, he started to analyze the situation. Although this was good news, he still felt a little worried.

"With this, I have another powerful secret force in my hands. In the future, the two sisters' position in the universe will most certainly rocket. They'll acquire high positions in the Beyond Grade A Association for sure.

"When the Holy Accord comes out, the entire universe will find out the two ways of reviving—the Sanctum and the Underworld. The Beyond Grade As will have a choice between the two. However, for now, only Oathkeeper and I know that the Sanctums can revive them an infinite number of times; he others all think it's only once. So, there's a possibility some might join the Underworld because of this misinformation. As for the Supers below Beyond Grade A, they'll only have one choice, the Underworld.

"These two reviving methods are both connected to me, so I'll certainly become the focus of the entire universe and the three Universal Civilizations. The dynasty's power is in the hands of the hawk faction now. The new president of the federation seems to be a muscular man too… Tsk, things are not looking great. The importance of the Sanctum and the Underworld is far above the Evolution Cube. The advanced civilizations will not let them go easily. I might become the starting point of a storm.

"When one grows to a certain stage, he's not allowed to stop, or he'll walk backward. The advanced civilizations will never stop targeting the Beyond Grade As…"

Han Xiao frowned and thought about the future.

Due to the extremely complicated and intricate profit relationships, way too many things had no solutions. Suddenly, a brief but daring idea appeared in his mind.

If he could make the Beyond Grade A Association and all the Beyond Grade As fuse together to form a new organization, completely splitting the ordinary people and Supers…

This might be a path he had never thought of before, a revolution that would turn the world upside down. Many people would die from it.

At his current position, he already had the ability to guide the direction of the universe. Many things that looked impossible were no longer unimaginable.

However, once he made the decision, quadrillions of lives would be affected. He only had a brief thought and did not plan to act on it.

The shadow of the World Tree still shrouded the explored universe. This was not the time to make this kind of plan.

"I shall decide after dealing with the exterior enemy. Sigh, I really don't wish to take this step…"

Han Xiao exhaled, calmed the storm in his mind, and suppressed these thoughts at the bottom of his heart.

Right at this moment, his communicator rang.

Beep beep beep!

He took it out. It was surprisingly a call from Sylvia.

"Army Commander, the Crimson Dynasty has sent an official letter. They will be sending emissaries to inspect the progress of the cultural education of the Kunde Race. If standards are met, they can consider opening up parts of the sealed areas and allow some of them into the galactic society."

"Oh? It has only been less than thirty years. This is quite a lot earlier than I expected."

Han Xiao's eyes lit up.

He still remembered the Kunde Race's mission. Modo was already devastated, so only the cultural education part had yet to be completed.

Once this mission was done, he would finally acquire the abilities he had been working for the whole time.

Chapter 1237: Sorokin's Big Plan

Usually, the cultural modification movement targeted at a large civilization would last for two to five generations. However, it had been less than thirty years since the Kunde Race started accepting the cultural transformation. It was still quite early to talk about letting them out.

The dynasty probably had a certain reason to do that in advance.

Han Xiao had a rough guess.

Although the Kunde Race lost, the billions of their remaining population were quite a considerable amount of manpower. Now that they were settled in the Black Star Army's territory, they basically belonged to the army. Plus, while the cultural transformation was carried out, the Black Star Army was also promoting the benefits of the army, trying to make the Kunde Race loyal and yearn to join the army.

The dynasty probably did this to stop the Black Star Army's advertising in the Kunde Race as soon as possible so that the Kunde Race would not completely become the army's talent reserve. At the same time, they likely wanted to make the Kunde Race members who were not completely transformed cause some trouble for the army.

"Tsk, feeble trick…"

Han Xiao curled his lips.

He had only met Marbruce not long ago, and the response had already come so quickly. This was certainly backed up by the dynasty's upper echelons. The dynasty's attitude change toward him could clearly be seen from this.

Han Xiao did not mind it really. It was good news for him. He pondered for a few seconds and said, "Reply to dynasty. We welcome the inspection. Get someone to arrange a time with the dynasty. We'll form an inspection team on our side and have them accompany the dynasty's emissaries to carry out the inspection."

"Understood." Sylvia nodded. "One more thing, the Limitless Financial Group owes the Germinal Financial Group three months of payments. I told the finances department to talk to them, but they are not giving a reply. Would you like to ask them personally?"

"The Limitless Financial Group owes me money? Are they having problems with their capital flow?"

"Iapetus already had someone investigate. The Limitless Financial Group's businesses are all stable. They've even achieved new records in some fields. Their capital flow is very healthy, but they're just not paying us."

"How much exactly?"

"There is a total of thirty-four projects. The total amount owed is 48.2 billion Enas. You…"

Before Sylvia finished, Han Xiao's eyes widened, and he stopped her.

"Yoho, this b*stard dares to not pay up. I'll speak with him personally."

Then, Han Xiao found Sorokin's private number and called on the spot.

It rang for a while before being picked up. Sorokin's projection appeared on the screen. His enthusiastic-on-the-surface voice sounded.

"Your Excellency Black Star, what a rare treat. I was just thinking why I am in such a good mood today. It turns out I've got an honorable guest. Can I do anything for you?"

"Nothing much, I just heard you owe me quite a lot of money, so I'm here to hurry you to pay up."

Han Xiao raised his brows.

Sorokin instantly looked troubled. He then said with a very sincere and helpless tone, "Sigh, the consortium is not doing well. Our capital flow is tight right now. You know, for people who have large businesses like us, we have to spend billions every day. I really don't have the money now."

"Stop lying. You think my finances department is a joke? The report on our side says you're doing very well. You even expanded quite a lot of businesses, and you're still telling me you have no money?"

"It's exactly because we're expanding our businesses. We're spending more money to open up new channels, and it's costing more money that I expected, so I really don't have the money."

"Bullsh*t. Don't blame me for not reminding you. If you don't pay up in the agreed period, you'll have to pay for liquidated damages. Don't regret it then… By the way, I heard some time ago that you were trying to poach Iapetus's team with a high salary. Is that true?"

"Hehe, I'm a businessman. These are all normal business operations. Don't take it to heart."

The two of them went back and forth a few more rounds, and Sorokin was still not saying he would pay up.

Seeing Sorokin's unusual responses, Han Xiao had some guesses in his mind. He suddenly said meaningfully, "Looks like this is not a business issue. It seems we're having some problems in terms of our positions."

Hearing this, Sorokin smiled faintly and said, "I thought we'd work well together, but I seem to be wrong…"

Both used very ambiguous words because they did not want to leave any evidence, but they both understood what the other meant.

Ever since Han Xiao reported Sorokin's oddness to the dynasty using the opportunity when Gaud went missing, Sorokin had been investigated and targeted by the dynasty both on the surface and secretly. In the past two years, he had needed to be careful, scared, and worried all the time. It was very irritating.

At the start, Sorokin thought the dynasty was just investing all suspicious personnel, so he put up with it. However, the dynasty's recent actions had made him feel more and more like something was not right. Through his connections, he asked around and shockingly discovered that the dynasty's motive for investigating him was actually because they doubted his identity.

Currently, Black Star was the only person in the entire universe who knew about his secret. Initially, the Limitless Financial Group partnered with Black Star to shut him up. However, Black Star having exposed his secret to the dynasty was the only possible reason the dynasty was targeting him now. Sorokin was furious.

Since Sorokin was already betrayed, he did not want the Black Star Army to continue draining blood from the Limitless Financial Group.

"If there's nothing else, I'll be off. Hehe, I still have other things to attend to."

Sorokin gave a fake smile and hung up.

The screen turned black. Han Xiao put the communicator away with a snicker.

He did this on purpose to force Sorokin to expose his identity. He was curious about how Sorokin would deal with it.

"You thought I was just messing with you, but I'm actually hoping you'll lose your cool. If you fight me, that'd be for the best. Beating you up would be justifiable."

Han Xiao's eyes flickered as he chuckled.

Sorokin's identity was similar to Gaud's. It was a form of protection for them. However, Han Xiao dared to touch Gaud because his level was much higher, and he could see all of Gaud's abilities, so he had the confidence to take him down. Sorokin was different; his level was higher than Han Xiao's even now. Han Xiao still saw a ton of question marks on the interface and did not know what Sorokin was hiding. Han Xiao was worried about messing up.

Most importantly, getting rid of Gaud was because Gaud was involved in a matter that was way too big to be ignored. If he did not do it, everyone would be done for. As for Sorokin, his importance was not as high, so Han Xiao did not want to break the association's rules because of personal beef. This was the bit of virtue he had.

Of course, this was only limited to not attacking him first. If Sorokin came at him, Han Xiao would not mind playing 'Welcome to the Black Underworld' for him.

As soon as the call was hung up, Sorokin's expression turned gloomy.

He was a little regretful. He felt he should not have hesitated when his identity was pointed out by Black Star back then; he should have eliminated this threat as soon as possible.

Although gathering all Soul Seeds would cause this body to be destroyed, and he would lose this identity, letting Black Star be would still risk losing this identity.

Since he would definitely lose a ton of things no matter what, he might as well drag Black Star down.

Although he was furious, he was still hesitant. He was worried that he might be blowing the matter out of proportion, but he was also worried about if he could actually defeat Black Star.

"No matter what, I have to make backup plans. I need to find a way to inherit part of the Limitless Financial Group's enormous funds. If the cash flow is too large, it'll attract attention even if I use the black-market channels. It's best to turn the funds into actual items…"

Sorokin clenched his teeth.

Whether he was going to do it or not, preparing a way to back off was definitely not wrong.

"Black Star's body is indestructible. His soul is his only weakness, but even that is speaking relatively. He has peak Beyond Grade A mind resistance at the very least. Killing him is extremely difficult. He has the King, so exiling him into the unexplored universe will also not work. Based on my ability and the Universal Treasures I've secretly collected, only one plan has a comparatively high success rate, heavily damaging or sealing his soul so that he has to go into a long-term hibernation state.

"To do that, I'd best retrieve the Soul Flame. Only then will the success rate be higher. I wonder if the Soul Flame has a master now. If it has, I can only kill him and retrieve it…"

A few days later, the dynasty and the Black Star Army agreed on a date for the inspection. They sent emissaries and headed to the Flickering World from the Central Galaxy.

The dynasty's inspection team had to spend quite some time on the way, so Han Xiao told the troops stationed on the hundreds of residential planets of the Kunde Race to spread the message that the inspection team would arrive soon. He told them that they could be freed if they performed well.

Originally, inspections were usually carried out secretly. Once the inspection target knew about it in advance, in order to be freed earlier, they might 'cheat'. This had happened before.

This time, however, the dynasty did not react at all, as letting the Kunde Race out earlier was also their secret goal. Although what Han Xiao had done went against the rules, it matched what the dynasty wanted to achieve, so they turned a blind eye. Han Xiao, too, wanted to free the Kunde Race as soon as possible so that he could acquire the mission reward.

Both sides were trying to achieve their goal. The difference was that Han Xiao knew what the dynasty was thinking, but the dynasty did not know what his goal was.

The news that the inspection team would soon arrive spread out rapidly on every Kunde Race residential planet. The Kunde Race, who had spent their days meaninglessly, suddenly saw hope.

Kunde Race Residential Planet No.77, South of Sigaia City, Apartment F0044's rooftop…

Barton stood tall and looked over the entire city. Tall, rectangular apartments were neatly placed with the same height, shape, and distance between each other, like metal coffins. The city gave off a strong industrial vibe. The sky was dark, and the dawn hid behind the clouds, painting the city a depressed yellow.

Barton could not remember how many times he had seen this boring, forever the same, and depressed scenery. In his eyes, this was no city; it was more of a large prison.

Piercing cold wind swept past, bringing the voice behind.

"Brother Barton, the news said this is the first time the Crimson Dynasty inspection team has visited. Can we really leave here?"

Hearing this, Barton turned around. Hundreds of people stood on the rooftop, all young Kunde Race members.

He stayed silent for a while before nodding slowly.

"Definitely!"

They were all children of the residents in this apartment, born in the 'Age of the Big Lockdown'. Barton was the oldest. He was the acknowledged leader of all the youngsters there.

During the cultural transformation, everything in their lives was arranged. Their residence was arranged, and their neighbors were arranged. Leaving the house had to be reported to the local artificial intelligence management system, and they could only leave the area after it was approved. Everything they did was monitored.

The Kunde Race was not allowed to develop their technology. The only thing they could pass around was part of the Super knowledge, which came from the Black Star Army. The Black Star Army saw the Kunde Race as its talent reserve, so it did not want them to all become useless shut-ins.

The cultural transformation involved many aspects, including their daily necessities, the news they saw, the education they were given, and so on. After more than two decades, this had already become the norm of the Kunde Race's lives. They were receiving this information every day, and their mindsets changed subconsciously.

However, for the first batch of newborns during the Age of the Big Lockdown, the glory of the Kunde Race in the past only existed in words. They could not imagine it. While being educated in public schools, they were also influenced by the lingering hatred of the previous generations at the same time.

Some of the seniors who experienced the Kunde Race's defeat still had hatred buried deep in their bones, warning the younger generations to never forget about it. Some chose not to speak of it, to let the newer generations leave the past behind. Only then would their race be freed one day and have a new future.

Living on a planet in lockdown, a society that was depressed, and between divided beliefs, this generation was lost. No one knew where the path ahead led.

Now, the arrival of the dynasty's inspection team finally made them see something that was more important than anything else—hope.

Barton looked past the eyes filled with hope and said with a deep voice, "We might only have this one chance in our life… Anyone who causes problems will be a sinner to the entire race."

A young man sighed and said, "Brother Barton, maybe we won't cause any problems, but as you know, there are too many others who still are blinded by hatred just in this apartment… This is probably not what the inspection team wants to see."

Barton stayed silent for a while. He then slowly raised the pliers in his hands. Tiny electric sparks danced on his skin, and he softly said, "Someone will have to take the lead. We still have time to prepare. Go, talk to everyone in the apartment who is still filled with hatred. For the entire race, I believe they'll make the right choice.

"If there's anyone who is really blinded and twisted by hatred, not willing to make any change, a burden to everyone…"

Barton paused. Colors representing pain appeared on his carapace.

"Kill them, even if they're our family."

Chapter 1239: Sorokin's Senses

"Finally!" Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

He had been eyeing these three abilities for a very long time. Now, he had finally acquired them after almost a full version.

Both [The Enemy] and [Kunde Rage] consumed health. The former was a passive talent, giving him more damage with health lost during the battle, up to twenty-five percent. The latter was an ability, increasing his Psychological Resistance tremendously for forty seconds at most, as well as immunity to almost all negative psychological states.

Among these three, the strongest was [Proof of Leadership].

This was considered a 'Semi-Molding Talent' to players, meaning even the players could obtain it. The way it worked was that when the user was the leader of a faction, they would receive comprehensive bonuses. The bonuses increased with the size and level of the faction. The most incredible trait of this talent was that it had no upper limit.

No matter how strong the players' organizations were, they could not reach the Beyond Grade A organization level and would not be able to gain enough bonuses from this talent. However, Han Xiao was different.

The Black Star Army's position was unique and irreplaceable in the universe. After an entire mission, it was already much stronger than when he triggered this mission. He could benefit a ton from this talent.

The bonuses of [Proof of Leadership] were very comprehensive. It included but was not limited to basic attributes, health, stamina, energy, ability strength, class affinity, all kinds of resistances, attack damage, ability level, and so on.

Han Xiao looked at the talent and realized that it did not only include one faction he was in. Other than the bonuses brought by the Black Star Army, the talent showed that the Beyond Grade A Association provided some bonuses too. His vice president identity was also considered in [Proof of Leadership], only it was not complete. He would only gain the complete bonuses if he was the president.

All in all, [Proof of Leadership] gave him a huge boost. This single talent increased his Energy Rank by an outrageous 5,400 Ona!

With the increase of Energy Rank, the strength difference between every point increased too. His Energy Rank was more than 100,000; 5400 Ona was an enormous boost to his combat capability at this level.

Feeling the overflowing energy in his body, Han Xiao took a deep breath and was delighted.

"This talent really suits me very well. I'm a huge step closer to the higher territory."

Han Xiao looked through the effects of [Proof of Leadership] several times with a huge grin on his face. He loved this talent.

Having finally achieved his dream of so many years, he was relieved.

The Kundes had to join the army of their own volition, and the dynasty freeing them in advance would decrease the number of Kundes willing to join the army, but it led to him acquiring the biggest benefit in advance.

As for the future developments of the Kunde Race, as long as nothing huge happened, Han Xiao did not plan to interfere frequently.

Anyway, the Kunde Race was now living in his territory. If they recovered to a normal civilization, they would even have to pay taxes to him instead, like a protection fee. If the Kunde Race wanted to expand in his territory, they would have to rent or purchase planets from the army.

Controlling one area was indeed an amazing way of making profit. By providing all kinds of services such as renting and selling land, he could harvest the labor of the Kunde Race as a whole and take a bite out of their produce. He had the right to decide the prices of the planets in his territory, so he dictated how quickly he wanted to harvest. He could choose to dry the pool for the fish in it, or he could choose to slowly fish over the long term. Of course, Han Xiao liked the latter more.

"Hmm, in this case, I can attract the Kunde Race Supers into the army using special benefits. For example, all Kunde Race members of the army with relatively high positions can purchase resources for the Kunde Race at a discount…"

The dynasty had definitely thought of this too and did not want to see it happen. Only, they could not easily tear away the agreement they had signed in the past.

Therefore, when the Kunde Race was freed to a certain stage, the dynasty would find a way to make the Kunde Race request to migrate. The fighting happening behind the curtains was complicated and troublesome. Han Xiao could already guest what methods the dynasty would use.

However, in his position, he did not have to attend to every little thing personally; people below him would deal with it. Furthermore, this would almost certainly not happen in the next few decades, so he did not have to worry yet.

A few days later, the Black Star Army announced a system to the Kunde Race, stating that in respect of the Kunde Race civilization, the army would not give them benefits for free out of pity but instead provide the Kunde Race tons of job opportunities.

The Black Star Army claimed that one reason for this was to guide the Kunde Race to blend into galactic society, and another was to give the Kunde Race a channel to acquire resources. Through working, all Kundes could earn contribution points that would be put under the entire race. The Kunde Race could then use this special currency to purchase all kinds of services to speed up the rebuilding of their civilization.

As soon as the system was announced, it received overwhelmingly positive feedback from the Kunde Race. Putting aside Han Xiao's reputation, although these trillions of Kundes gained freedom, they were also lost. Many of them did not know how to blend into the galactic society.

Now, the Black Star Army provided them with a clear direction, and the results of that were countless responses.

Han Xiao was already extremely experienced at harvesting leeks. This was the exact method he used to harvest the Planet Aquamarine players during Version 2.0 back then, turning his faction into the guiding faction. It was effective on the Kunde Race too.

Tons of quality Kunde Race laborers swarmed into the Black Star Army. The number of base-level Supers rocketed.

Currently, the Black Star Army was focusing on growing the subdivisions in other Star Fields, and the manpower from the Kunde Race came just at the right time.

The HR department arranged to have the Kundes travel far away from their home to different Star Fields to work in the subdivisions. They would work 'overseas' to accumulate contribution points for the race. This would prevent them from sticking only to other Kundes and not blending in with the galactic society well enough.

The Crimson Dynasty announced a similar policy too. However, the duration of the transformation was too short, so only an extremely few were willing to work for the dynasty, far fewer than the number of Kundes the army recruited.

However, more Kundes decided to stay among their race to rebuild the civilization and not work for other organizations, so the dynasty's plan worked to a certain extent.

While the Black Star Army was digesting the Kunde Race's laborers, Sorokin started to move.

"I'm finally done with the backup plans. I can act anytime…"

Inside the office at the Limitless Financial Group headquarters, Sorokin sensed the movements of his various manifestations and looked relieved.

In the past few months, he had returned to the Limitless Financial Group headquarters in the Sea of Star Spirits and prepared backup plans, placing secret warehouses in many Star Fields and some secondary dimensions that stored large amounts of resources.

Sorokin knew the strength of Virtual Mechanics, so he left no traces in the database. This was all done by his manifestations.

As for the movements of the funds, he disguised them as normal business transactions.

However, the consortium was his to begin with. Its business was growing better by the day and had no difficulties, so there was absolutely no need for the boss to take the money and run. This was like him stealing his own things, so not many people would realize the issue.

At the same time, using several methods, Sorokin left many hidden problems for the Limitless Financial Group's cash flow. If he was fine, he could easily solve them afterward.

If something happened to him, the credibility of the Limitless Financial Group would plummet. Once the partners came to tell the Limitless Financial Group to pay up, the Limitless Financial Group would be tremendously damaged. By then, the other large consortiums would definitely try to eat up the businesses of the Limitless Financial Group and dissect its corpse. This way, what was left to the shareholders of the group would be a huge mess. Even if they wanted to continue the Limitless Financial Group, they would have to pay a hefty price to fill up this hole.

This was one of Sorokin's backup plans—he would rather destroy his hard work over many years than give it to someone else, especially when Black Star was one of the shareholders.

"I can use those Universal Treasures I've collected anytime, but the most useful thing for this mission is still Soul Flame…"

Sorokin's eyes flickered.

He was once the master of Soul Flame; he knew the functions of this Esper Ability Entity extremely well. From his perspective, if he could regain this ability, the success rate of the plan would increase by another twenty percent.

Back when he gave up the identity of Soul Flame, he had no idea where Soul Flame went. In order to keep his identity hidden and not get discovered by anyone he knew, he used the specialty of his Esper Ability to change his soul frequency. Basically, he gave himself soul plastic surgery.

However, he did not completely cut off his senses to Soul Flame but split it up into Soul Seeds that had been sealed all this time. Once he opened the seal, he would be able to sense the rough location of Soul Flame.

All this time, Sorokin had disguised himself as a common Psychic Esper and had never shown all the special traits of his Esper Ability. Therefore, although he was also a soul-type Esper, his abilities looked quite different from 'Soul Emperor'.

To not attract any suspicion, he never dared retrieve Soul Flame. Anyway, he had a method to sense it. From the way he looked at it, no matter where Soul Flame went, he could totally retrieve it any time he wanted.

Sorokin narrowed his eyes, found that sealed Soul Seed in his Esper Ability senses, retrieved it ignoring the distance between him and the Soul Seed, and unsealed it.

The next moment, Sorokin's gaze changed subtly. It was a little bit colder.

Every Soul Seed was a fragment of his personality. The more he retrieved, the more whole his personality would become, and the more he would be like the real 'Soul Emperor' Rovell Sissock.

The moment the Soul Seed was unsealed, a reaction that was far away appeared in his senses, pointing him in a direction.

Sorokin turned toward that direction. He looked at the dark cosmic space through the floor-to-ceiling windows.

"Soul Flame is in that direction… the Ancient Star Desert."

In the Holy Accord organization, Oathkeeper, who was playing Wayne Cards with the others, suddenly felt something. He turned and looked outside the window. Confusion appeared in his eyes.

Why does it suddenly feel like I'm being watched?

Before he could think further, Beiger, who was opposite, slapped the table impatiently.

"Stop dozing off. Mechanic Emperor, do you want it or not?"

Oathkeeper regained focus and threw out a card.

"Black Star, bigger than you."

"Tsk, dog luck… pass, pass, go on."

Oathkeeper's focus returned to the game.

The Wayne Cards included almost all organizations and important people in the world, so it was an extremely efficient way to figure out the current structure of the universe and its history…

It's most certainly not because we like to play cards!

Chapter 1240: Sorokin's Bizarre Adventure (1)

At a certain place in the desolate universe belt, an armed fleet was slowly advancing through the cosmic space. Sorokin stood in the command room of the main ship and looked into the galaxy.

This armed fleet was a mercenary group he had secretly founded in the Ancient Star Desert. Other than a few upper echelons, no one knew that their boss was the Limitless Financial Group. For this mission, Sorokin secretly created a manifestation that looked exactly like him and left it in the consortium's headquarters. He then slipped out, led this mercenary group, and headed to the location of Soul Flame.

This group did not know the exact goal of this trip; they only acted based on orders of the upper echelons. For safety reasons, Sorokin even wore a mask. Other than the leader beside him, no one else in the fleet knew that the renowned Sorokin was on their ship.

"The reaction is getting stronger, meaning I'm getting closer…"

Sorokin looked at the star map. Within a certain distance ahead, there was only one desolate planet. He was basically certain that Soul Flame was on this planet.

On the star map, this planet had no name, only a serial number. It was marked as a poor planet with no value for developing.

After the fleet advanced a while longer and was still quite some distances away from this planet, Sorokin stopped the fleet.

"All ships, stop advancing. Use astronomical observation instruments to observe the surface status of that planet."

"…Observation complete. Boss, everything is normal on the planet surface. It's desolate and has nothing worth paying attention to. The details still require field inspection."

Sorokin nodded and ordered, "Hmm, send out a recon ship to land on the planet first. Everyone else, remain in stealth mode and standby here."

He had a habit of being careful at all times. He was worried that Soul Flame might have a master, so he decided to test it first. Even if it was a desolate planet, he still had to repeatedly confirm there was no hidden danger.

The recon ship deviated from the fleet and quickly flew toward the planet. Sorokin secretly used his ability and possessed the captain of the ship.

A while later, the recon ship finally arrived on the planet. It activated all kinds of scanners and started to investigate the underground. However, after an entire hour, all results came back normal.

Sorokin immediately realized the problem and narrowed his eyes.

According to his senses, Soul Flame was right there, somewhere underground. There was no way it was not discovered unless someone had set up disguise devices underground, which would prove that someone was there.

"Even if the scanning can be avoided, the actual object can't be hidden."

Sorokin's manifestation drew out a rough area on the planet's underground model. He then ordered the crew to stop scanning and send robots to dig into the ground instead. He planned to dig a hole right toward the location of Soul Flame.

However, the moment the robots were dispatched from the ship, the recon ship suddenly became paralyzed. Its engine shut off, and it plummeted from the sky. The crew inside the cabin were bumping into everything around like they were inside a shaking tin can.

Sorokin suppressed his instincts and did not use any ability with his manifestation. When the recon ship was just about to crash onto the ground, a blue-purple magic gate suddenly appeared below it. The recon ship fell right in and disappeared.

At the same time, the mercenary group leader far away in the main ship hastily reported to Sorokin's original body.

"Boss, we've just lost communication with the recon ship. It's suddenly missing. Should we go take a look?"

"No need, move back for now."

Sorokin's eyes flickered.

It looked like there were indeed enemies near Soul Flame. Since he possessed the captain of the recon ship, he could now scout the enemies.

At this point of time, the vision and senses of the manifestation were being transmitted back to his mind.

After the recon ship fell into the magic gate, as if it had fallen onto a certain buffering platform, it did not crash, but the trembling of the cabin made the people inside fall down again.

The crew covered their bleeding heads. They hastily pressed on the operating table and said with panic, "Captain, all functions of the spaceship are frozen. We've lost contact with the others!"

Sorokin's manifestation acted panicked and said, "Go put on the land exploration armor. Open the hatch manually, and take a look at where we are."

As the order was given, the crew quickly changed and became land exploration armored warriors. Suppressing the nervousness in their hearts, they carefully pulled the hatch open.

Whoosh!

The sound of air pressure adjusting appeared as the hatch slipped open. After seeing what was outside, everyone froze.

This was a place that looked like an underground helipad. Outside was a group of mechanical suit warriors holding explosive energy firearms who surrounded the recon ship, aiming all their barrels at the hatch.

"What is this place?"

"Who are you?"

The crew of the ship were shocked.

The leader of the mechanical suit warriors outside coldly replied, "Disarm yourselves immediately, put your hands up, and walk out, or we'll fire!"

This is an unknown organization? They should have been hiding in the underground of this planet.

Sorokin did not see any organization's symbols on the mechanical suits of these people. He immediately acted nervous and cowardly. He yelled at the crew to throw away their weapons and led them out with his hands in the air.

Very soon, they were captured and imprisoned separately. Sorokin's manifestation was alone in an interrogation room.

After quite a while, the room door was finally pushed open. A mechanical suit warrior who was clearly there to interrogate him walked in, still wearing the helmet. It sat opposite and said, "I ask, and you answer, or you die. Understood?"

Sorokin's manifestation acted scared and nodded.

"I just searched your logs and found you belong to a mercenary group. Tell me, why have you come here?"

"I-I don't know. I'm just following orders."

Sorokin's manifestation deliberately stuttered, but he was secretly relieved.

Through checking the logs and interrogating the crew, this unknown organization definitely knew that the rest of the mercenary group was there too. Luckily, out of caution, he had kept the rest of the fleet quite far away and ordered them to back away even further when the recon ship lost contact.

The interrogator asked many more questions. Sorokin's manifestation's answers had both truths and lies, keeping to the amount of information this captain should know while shivering.

He had been acting across multiple lives, so he was already a top tier expert and a competitive candidate at the Oscars, so he did not cause any suspicion.

After a while, the interrogator was done asking questions and was about to stand up and leave the room.

At this time, Sorokin's manifestation's eyes suddenly lit up. Through his eyes, Sorokin's manifestation dashed into the interrogator's body and tried to possess it.

He had to know more about this unknown organization, so possessing one of them was clearly the best choice.

Sorokin activated his ability in the blink of an eye with no signs at all. It was extremely well hidden. At such a close distance, this interrogator who was not even a Calamity Grade, of course, was defenseless. His body was instantly taken over.

Right after Sorokin took over the body, before he could feel glad, he shockingly discovered a bright flame in the mind of this body.

"Soul Flame's seal‽"

The moment this interrogator's mind was occupied by an outsider's consciousness. As if it sensed something, this flame suddenly became volatile like it was about to turn into a sea of fire the next second and torch the mind of this body.

Sorokin's expression changed. In an instant, he adjusted his soul frequency, made a series of complex adjustments, and shrouded this flame with his soul energy.

The next moment, this flame slowly calmed down but still did not look fully stable, as if it could erupt any time.

Seeing this, Sorokin was relieved.

He knew all too well about the effects of Soul Flame. It could plant this type of surveillance seal on others to prevent them from leaking certain secrets or getting their memories searched. Once triggered, the seal would instantly burn all related memories. The master of Soul Flame would also sense it.

This was effective against most people, even Beyond Grade As, but not Sorokin.

He had once been the master of Soul Flame, so he already knew everything there was to know about its abilities. With the specialness of his Esper Ability, he could temporarily dodge the Soul Flame's seal. He was one of the extremely few who could infiltrate the Holy Accord in the universe.

Although he successfully made the Soul Flame seal misjudge him and did not erupt instantly, he knew that he would only be able to deceive the seal for a certain amount of time. If he retrieved his soul energy in this manifestation, the seal would erupt right away, and Soul Flame's current master would notice.

Also, he did not dare to read the memories of this body. Soul Flame sealed the related memories like a chain of traps. Once triggered, he would no longer be able to deceive the Soul Flame seal and would be exposed instantly.

"That was close. Don't tell me every member of this mysterious organization has the Soul Flame seal…"

Sorokin was on alert. He was surprised.

This meant that the master of Soul Flame should be the leader of this unknown organization, an upper echelon at the very least.

Using this method to make sure all its members did not leak the secrets… what kind of huge secret needed this degree of caution? What did this organization do?

While he controlled the new manifestation to leave the room, he pondered in his mind. Although he could not read this body's memories, he could observe the situation of this organization with it.

As soon as he walked out of the interrogation room, someone approached him. Following the rule of 'the more said, the more mistakes made', he handed over the interrogation report without saying a word. Seeing that no one gave him further orders, he left the area on his own.

He walked around for some time and very quickly realized that this organization's base was very huge and had a lot of members, but there was no organization's symbol anywhere.

Sorokin's manifestation did not dare ask anyone, so he could only walk around randomly. However, this body's authorization level seemed to be very low. Many areas were not accessible, especially the direction where he sensed Soul Flame was. It was in a forbidden area, which base-level personnel were not allowed to enter.

"This won't work. I won't find any valuable information, and I'll be exposed sooner or later… Looks like I need a push," Sorokin murmured.

From the way he looked at it, this mysterious organization was very serious about secrecy. Once exposed, it would very likely shift its location. Therefore, he planned to let the mercenary group attack this planet to force this organization to display its strength and start to migrate. Then, he would have more chances to discover the secrets of this organization and the identity of Soul Flame's master.

As for the possible casualties of the mercenary group, he did not care at all. They were sacrificial chess pieces to begin with.

Having thought of that, Sorokin's original body immediately said to the mercenary group leader, "Pass my order, send seventy percent of the fleet to bombard that planet. The remaining thirty percent, back away with me."

"Understood."

The leader gave the orders right away.

A portion of the armed fleet advanced right away, entering attack range after quite a while. They then activated all kinds of ranged weapons immediately. Enormous missiles were shot out and flew toward the target, dragging tails of flames behind.

Buzz!

Suddenly, a light-blue magic barrier shrouded the entire planet and stopped all the attacks. The missiles turned into fireworks in cosmic space.

Before the fleet made the next move, all the battleships that were sent to attack the planet lost control and started attacking each other like they were being controlled by someone else.

At the same time, a ring of fire as bright as the sun expanded from the planet like an illusion, quickly penetrating all the battleships.

The next moment, more than ninety percent of the crew's souls were incinerated, and they died right on the spot.

The armed fleet sent to attack the planet completely lost the ability to fight in less than a minute!

At this time, a hole suddenly opened up on the surface of the planet like the tracks of an airport. Spaceships with no symbols flew out and seized all the remaining battleships.

"This quickly?" Sorokin's expression turned grave.

He knew that the mercenary group would be no match, but he did not expect them to be annihilated so quickly.

However, though the battle was short, he still gained some shocking information.

Mage, Virtual Mechanic, and the master of Soul Flame… This organization has at least three Beyond Grade As!

Sorokin was intimidated.

This organization is way too unfathomable. Luckily, I was cautious enough. If I charged right in like a Pugilist…

Good thing I'm a coward!

Having thought of that, he immediately told the remaining fleet to back away at full speed.

At the same time, Sorokin's manifestation in the Holy Accord organization also received an emergency migration order.

In the underground base, members of the organization moved supplies, destroyed buildings, and activated spaceships quickly.

Sorokin's manifestation was also summoned by his boss. He quickly rushed over, did his job at the dock, and observed the surroundings.

Shortly after, he sensed that the location of Soul Flame was rapidly approaching.

Very soon, rapid footsteps came from a tunnel, along with many voices. To his shock, some of the voices sounded familiar.

"Odd, what was with that fleet? Why did they suddenly attack us?"

"Were they here for us? Did they discover us?"

"No way, they're way too ill equipped to have the guts to fight us. It seems to be a fleet that passed by and discovered our base…"

"Are we that unlucky? Did you not wash your face this morning?"

The voices got closer. Very soon, a group of people walked out the passage, complaining while walking toward the spaceship at the dock.

Sensing that the master of Soul Flame was in this group, Sorokin subconsciously turned and glanced at them.

With this one look, his mind went completely blank!

'King of War' Pangon, 'Mage God' Beiger, 'Violet Queen' Lady Lust… They were all Primordial Ones who were in the same generation as him. Even Beiger, who killed him, was there!

Didn't they die long ago‽

Why are they here, alive‽

While Sorokin's thoughts were going wild, the energy he used to suppress the Soul Flame seal also became unstable.

The next moment, the seal broke through the suppression and erupted, instantly incinerating the soul of this manifestation.

"Hmm‽"

Oathkeeper, who was leading the way at the front of the revived Primordial Ones, instantly turned around and saw the manifestation that collapsed to the floor.

"Someone just triggered the Soul Flame seal…"

Uncontrollably excitement appeared in Oathkeeper's eyes.

Could it be… the legendary spy has appeared?

Ha! It's been so many years I almost thought you really didn't exist!

You've finally shown yourself!

Chapter 1241: Sorokin's Bizarre Adventure (2)

The soul energy he used to possess the Holy Accord warrior was incinerated, but Sorokin could not be bothered with the fact that he had been exposed. Thinking of what he saw before his manifestation collapsed, disbelief appeared on his face.

Dozens of Primordial Ones, all alive till today… did they fake their deaths like me‽

Sorokin could not believe it.

Impossible!

Some of them were definitely dead. Even their ashes were scattered!

How did they get past the exploration era, hide their existence, and live till now?

Is this place actually the nursing home for the Primordial Ones?

Or have these people been hiding for so long and planning an astronomic conspiracy‽

Sorokin completely lost it. The more he thought about it, the more terrified he was.

He had never heard of this organization before. Could he be the only one in the universe who knew this secret?

This time, Sorokin suddenly shivered. He hastily ordered the leader of the mercenary group, "Split up the fleet immediately. Retreat in different directions and run at full speed!"

For the first time in a long time, Sorokin panicked.

He was confident in his strength. Originally, he felt that the success rate of retrieving Soul Flame was not low. He only got a bit more serious even when he saw three Beyond Grade As earlier and did not think he could not do it.

However, to his absolute shock, there were more than thirty Beyond Grade A there!

The situation far exceeded what he expected, who in the world could deal with this!

Dozens of Beyond Grade As far exceeded the limit of what he could deal with. Plus, he had triggered Soul Flame's alarm, which was basically the same as poking the hornet nest. Sorokin immediately lost any desire to continue his plan; all he wanted to do was immediately run out of this area as far as possible.

At this time, the mercenary group leader looked at the remote observation images and suddenly screamed, "Boss, their fleet moved and is heading toward our direction. Plus, dozens of high energy reactions suddenly appeared on the radar, all possibly Beyond Grade As!"

"What are you standing there for then? Run!"

Sorokin was furious and shocked.

He could secretly find out more about this organization in the future, but if he got caught now, there would be no 'future' to speak of!

The mercenary group split up right away. The main ship Sorokin was in sent all its energy into the engine, entered overload mode, and fled at full speed in hyperdrive. The starlight outside the window was stretched into lines.

However, only shortly after they started fleeing, a deafening alarm rang on the radar!

Boom!

The next second, the entire spaceship suddenly trembled and exited from hyperdrive mode. The huge inertia caused everyone but Sorokin to fall onto the floor.

Sorokin ignored the screams of pain of all the crew and hastily looked outside the window.

The cosmic space around was filled with magic arrays. Glass-like translucent arcane tentacles extended from within and tangled around the entire spaceship tightly. The arcane tentacles squeezed the spaceships continuously, and the sound of the metal armor tearing up could be easily heard in the cabin as cracks appeared and extended on the alloy walls.

At the same time, a magic teleportation suddenly opened up right in front of the spaceship. Beiger and the group of Primordial Ones walked out.

"Beiger!"

Flames of rage filled Sorokin's eyes. He ground his teeth.

Damn Mage!

This time, the spaceship was suddenly taken over by a Virtual Mechanic among the Primordial Ones and opened its communication.

The next moment, Oathkeeper's projection appeared in the cabin. He sized Sorokin up. His tone was thirty-percent curious, thirty-percent excited, and forty-percent annoyed.

"You're the one who dodged Soul Flame's seal and possessed my subordinate?"

"I don't know what you're talking about! Who are you?" Sorokin was on full alert.

"Interesting, you're not going to tell us you just happened to pass by, are you?" Oathkeeper narrowed his eyes.

"Listen to me, I…"

"You'll have plenty of time to explain later!"

Before Sorokin finished speaking, dozens of Beyond Grade As attacked at the same time. A shocking amount of energy headed right toward the spaceship Sorokin was in.

Boom!

The spaceship was instantly shattered into atoms. Sorokin dashed out the cabin at the last moment. Feeling the hopeless strength difference between him and the enemies, he was filled with despair.

He wanted to calm these people down with words first, but they attacked right away, and there was nothing he could do about it.

Although his physical body was not the core of his life, he did not want to end up in the hands of these people.

"There's no other way!"

Sorokin clenched his teeth and retrieved most of his Soul Seeds. Suddenly, his entire vibe changed and became cold and violent. An enormous energy shockwave erupted from his body, creating visible ripples in the cosmic space around him!

Feeling this energy, Oathkeeper's eyes turned serious. He pulled his teammates into a mind chat channel and said, "Careful, this guy is very strong. Don't let down your guard."

"Don't worry, there's plenty of us!"

They laughed and charged forward.

An intense battle erupted instantly. However, within seconds, Sorokin was completely overwhelmed, and the battle became one-sided.

His actual strength was indeed very strong, on par with even peak Beyond Grade As. However, he had yet to step into that higher territory and was still a normal Beyond Grade A.

With dozens of Beyond Grade As attacking him together, Sorokin could only get thrashed. Even if it was the evolved EsGod, he would still meet the same end.

All Sorokin could do was try not to die. Very soon, his mask was shattered, and everyone saw his face.

"This guy is… the Limitless Financial Group's Sorokin?"

Oathkeeper was surprised.

He did not expect the guy who infiltrated his organization to be the renowned head of the biggest consortium.

Isn't this guy known for being weak? Isn't he among the weakest Beyond Grade As? Why does he have this level of strength?

Has Sorokin always been acting weak and hiding his strength? Is he this cowardly?

While he was being confused, Beiger suddenly noticed something from Sorokin's combat style and exclaimed, "This Esper Ability… Are you Soul Emperor?"

"What?" The others were shocked. They hastily observed Sorokin, and everyone discovered some clues.

The modern people could only analyze Soul Emperor's abilities, whereas they were in the same generation as Soul Emperor and had fought him God knew how many times. They noticed it right away.

Hearing this, Sorokin was filled with frustration.

He had always avoided going all out because he was worried about being recognized, but in the end, it still happened.

He knew he could not deceive these people who were familiar with him. Plus, he already planned to give up this identity. Thinking at least they shared some common topics, he gave up acting and yelled, "That's right, it's me! Aren't you *ssholes dead? How are you here‽"

"It's really you, Rovell Sissock!"

The Primordial Ones were surprised and slowed down their attacks.

If it was a stranger, they would not have been affected at all. However, Soul Emperor was someone in the same generation as them, so he was at least a familiar face. They were all very curious about what was going on with Sorokin.

We didn't revive you. Did you not die?

Beiger's expression changed slightly. He recalled what Black Star said in the past that hinted Soul Emperor had always been alive.

"Did you fake your death?"

Beiger was shocked.

"I clearly beat you to death back then. You did not leave any sign of life at all. How did you do it?"

"You're one to bring it up!" Sorokin dodged another magic missile that had more than enough power to penetrate a planet. Veins popped up on his forehead as he was reminded of what happened in the past.

Back then, his physical body had lost its life, and he had indeed been on the brink of death. The strong sense of frustration and hate in his mind had pushed his potential to explode, causing his Esper Ability to evolve. In the last moment, he had acquired the [Immortal Soul] ability. Otherwise, he would have died during the exploration era war along with his physical body.

This time, Oathkeeper thought of something and suddenly started to doubt his thoughts on the spy.

From the way it looked, it does not look like Sorokin knew about us long ago. Is he not related to the leak of the organization's information in the past?

"I didn't expect you to be Soul Emperor from back then. You've hidden yourself really well… How did you find us?"

"I was just trying to retrieve Soul Flame and followed my senses. I didn't know about you guys at all." Sorokin clenched his teeth. "Stop attacking, let me go!"

Oathkeeper recalled what happened earlier and believed Sorokin mostly, but he still shook his head.

"It doesn't matter if you knew before or not. You've found our secret today, so there's no leaving. We're all people from the same generation. We can have a good chat… but that'll be after you lose the ability to resist. Stop resisting. There's absolutely zero chance you can escape, so why prolong your suffering?"

The others nodded in agreement. Most of them did not intend to kill Sorokin right there. After all, they knew him from the old era, and they all wanted to hear Sorokin's experience in the past years.

Bang!

This time, Sorokin's face got punched by Pangon again, blasting him away flying. He forced himself to stay focused and observe the battlefield. His heart kept sinking.

Dozens of Beyond Grade As formed an encirclement. He had no chance of breaking through it head-on at all. In terms of mobility, as a mind Esper, he was no match for the teleportation spell of a Mage. There was absolutely no way he could escape.

Is this really going to be the end for this shell I've spent so much effort raising? I was supposed to use it against Black Star, but I haven't even seen Black Star's face yet!

Although Sorokin was confident to a certain extent that he would not die there because of his Esper Ability, he did not want to take the risk if he could save his body too. After all, he had already faked his death before; these people would definitely be more careful.

How many years has it been since I was last in such a desperate situation‽ I'm still not 'cowardly' enough. If I knew I'd end up poking the hornet nest, why did I think about killing Black Star? Isn't just retiring quietly so much better‽

Sorokin was filled with regret.

"What, still not surrendering?" Beiger snorted. "Don't think just because we know each other, I won't kill you. I've killed you once, and I can kill you again!"

Suddenly, it occurred to Sorokin. Memories deeply buried in his mind surfaced.

"I remember now! Holy Accord, you guys are the Holy Accord!"

The memories of the exploration era became vivid again. Sorokin had heard of the Holy Accord back then but scoffed at it and did not join.

As so much time had passed and Primordial Ones died one after another, he thought that secret-association-like Holy Accord organization had long disappeared.

When he just saw the dozens of Beyond Grade As, he was too shocked and occupied with fleeing, so he did not think of this at all. However, when he tried to find a way to escape earlier, his mind had spun rapidly, and he finally recalled this 'rumor' that once circulated around the Primordial Ones during the exploration era.

Therefore…

"Reviving using the Sanctums is real‽ You guys succeeded‽"

Sorokin's expression changed drastically. His tone was filled with disbelief.

If they came back by being revived, everything would make sense. He never thought such a rumor with absolutely no proof or whatsoever would be true!

Seeing that Sorokin had figured out the truth, everyone present was surprised.

Soul Emperor was in the same generation as them, so it was not impossible for him to figure it out. However, although they were already mentally prepared for that, the moment their secret was exposed, they were still shocked.

At this time, bolts of lightning crisscrossed in Sorokin's mind and connected everything he had just experienced. A plan quickly appeared in his mind, followed by joy, as if he had seen light in a dark cave. He found the only hope he had of escaping!

The Holy Accord was so secretive definitely because they did not want the information about the Sanctum to leak, this was the only leverage he could use—he would only have a chance if he bet on these people being afraid of leaking this secret!

While thoughts flashed through his mind, Sorokin yelled without hesitation, "You guys have been hiding and protecting the secret of the Sanctums, but you guys definitely remember that I can possess others with my ability. Yes, I can't escape from this encirclement today, but before you guys kill me, I have the time to control my manifestations in other Star Fields to spread out the information about the Sanctums! Stop this immediately if you don't want your secret to be leaked, or I will share this information with everyone right now!"

As soon as he said that, the others' expressions changed, and they slowed down their attacks subconsciously. They turned to look at Oathkeeper."

"… Are you threatening us?" Oathkeeper's eyes flickered.

"You're leaving me no choice; I just want to live!" Sorokin wiped away the blood on his forehead. Although he had no confidence, he could only act firm. "You're the master of Soul Flame. You can try to see if you can stop me, but can you deal with the consequences? It's better if I'm the only one who knows this secret than the entire universe finding out about it," Sorokin said.

Oathkeeper sized Sorokin up for a while silently. As the atmosphere kept getting more intense, he suddenly raised his hand, signaling for the others to stop attacking. "All of you, stop."

As soon as he said that, the others stopped attacking but still surrounded Sorokin with hostile expressions, not letting him escape.

This indeed hit Oathkeeper's weak spot. He knew what exposing the information about the Sanctum would mean. Comparatively, Sorokin's life was insignificant.

Oathkeeper was an expert in the mind too, but he did not have complete confidence he could stop Sorokin from activating his Esper Ability to control his manifestations. God knew what new abilities this guy learned after living for so long.

Oathkeeper did not want to push Sorokin too hard and force him into a corner. He planned to take it slow and see how things went.

Chapter 1242: Sorokin's Bizarre Adventure (3)

Seeing that everyone had stopped attacking him, Sorokin finally heaved a sigh of relief. His body was covered in wounds.

Although the duration of the battle was not long, the strength difference was too huge. He was crushed by dozens of people the entire time and was quite heavily wounded. An ordinary Beyond Grade A would have been done for long ago.

Luckily, he had a flash of insight and found the Holy Accord's weak spot. Just knowing their weak spot was not enough; he had to be able to use it as a leverage and only an extremely few people in the entire universe could do that. Sorokin was one of them. No one knew how many manifestations he had and where they were hidden.

Furthermore, they were not sure of what method Sorokin used to fake his death, so they did not dare do anything impulsive.

This time, Sorokin endured the pain all over his body, suppressed his annoyance, and put up a stiff smile.

"Ahem, ahem. See, this is much better. We all know each other. We should use a peaceful method to solve our misunderstandings. There's no need to resort to violence."

Oathkeeper hovered in space and said, "What ideas do you have?"

Sorokin's mind spun quickly. "We can totally work together."

"Work together?" Oathkeeper sized Sorokin up.

"That's right. We're all from the old era. The conflicts we had in the past have dissipated with time. We're not enemies now. Today was just a misunderstanding. My goal is actually just Soul Flame, but I coincidentally discovered your secret. The biggest issue between us is that you guys don't trust me. You're worried that I, an outsider, will leak your information, so you want to capture me…"

Sorokin had calmed down, and using his magical mouth trained through his business experience over many years, he started negotiating.

He observed everyone's expression, paused, and continued. "However, you guys can't stop me from leaking your information now, and I'm also worried you might do something to me. We both have worries. Therefore, working together is the best choice for all of us. If we can peacefully come to an agreement, we can avoid escalating the situation that'll do neither of us any good."

"How do you want to work together?" Oathkeeper narrowed his eyes.

Sorokin smiled. "Simple. You guys are worried about me leaking the secret, so you don't trust me enough to let me roam outside. Therefore, you might as well let me join the Holy Accord and make me one of you. Then, isn't the problem solved?"

His core mindset was very simple. If he could not defeat them, join them!

This was not just a temporary plan to save his life but a carefully thought-out plan. Although what he experienced this time threatened his life, when he carefully thought about it, it might just be an incredible opportunity to explore the secrets of the universe.

He already planned to give up the identity of 'Sorokin' and was originally planning to go to the secondary dimensions and retire for some time. However, from the way things looked now, the Holy Accord organization might be a better place to go. Not only was there a group of familiar faces, but they also seemed to be carrying out some kind of big plan. Plus, if he stayed there, he could even convince the outside world that he had been revived.

After the initial shock, Sorokin had a strong interest in the Sanctums. Another of his goals was to reduce the number of Beyond Grade As in the universe. Now that he had realized that Beyond Grade As could be revived, he would not be able to sleep and eat well before he figured out how it happened.

At the same time, Sorokin inevitably felt bitter. Originally, he thought most Primordial Ones had disappeared, and he was the only one who had stayed alive till now. Although he never mentioned it, he actually had a sense of superiority in his heart, thinking that he was the only one who got the last laugh among all the Primordial Ones in the same generation.

However, now that he saw a big group of Primordial Ones still alive, his sense of superiority disappeared, and he was left with only bitterness. That was especially so when he thought of how he hid his identity and carefully lived all these years in the past. He could not help but feel jealous and envious of these revivors, which made him even more interested in the Sanctums.

"You want to join the Holy Accord?"

The others were surprised. The expressions on their faces became odd.

You didn't contribute anything, yet you want to take a bite off our fruit of victory?

Why is your dream so ambitious?

After so many years, how did that cold and powerful Soul Emperor in their memories become so smooth?

Oathkeeper frowned and pondered silently. It seemed like he was having difficulties making a choice.

Seeing this, Sorokin added, "Frankly, I was just planning to retire. If the Holy Accord is willing to accept me, I won't come empty handed. You guys should know that I'm the owner of the Limitless Financial Group. I can bring Holy Accord a huge amount of funds. You'll need money no matter what you're planning, right?"

He had eyes on the secret of reviving through the Sanctums too, so he was willing to pay a high price to join the Holy Accord. If he could also enjoy this privilege, his life would be insured.

Hearing this, Oathkeeper said, "The risk of letting an outsider join us is not controllable. You hid your strength so well, and we don't know much about you. It's very tough for us to trust you."

"I understand your worries, but I'm really sincere. As for what you said about me being an outsider, I don't think that's true." Sorokin smiled. "We all know each other and each other's personality to a certain extent, we don't lack the foundation of trust."

Beiger suddenly shook his head and said, "No, we never hung out and are not close."

Fu*k you! You even 'hung' me to death back then!

Sorokin wanted to cuss but still maintained a smile.

Oathkeeper slowly said, "So many years have passed; you've definitely changed your identity more than once. How do we know how much you've changed?"

Hearing this, Sorokin became silent, which was rare. Then, he shook his head and said, "Everyone has secrets. No matter what I experienced in the past, I'm just Sorokin now."

He did not want to expose the information of his other identities. The identities of Soul Emperor and Sorokin were still considered clean, but he had done many not-so-clean things with his other identities. If he shared this information, it would become new leverage. Hence, he refused to say what identities he used before, expressing his firmness to a suitable extent, reminding the opposite party that their positions were equal in this negotiation.

Oathkeeper thought about it, changed the question, and asked, "Let's put this matter aside first. Let me ask you, you say you can sense Soul Flame, but you have not done it in so many years—why are you suddenly trying to find Soul Flame? We can't believe what you say if you don't explain this."

Sorokin hesitated for a moment and said, "Actually, I've come across a very strong enemy. In order to fight him, I have to retrieve Soul Flame and increase my strength as much as possible."

"Who's that strong enemy?"

"Black Star!"

As soon as he said that, everyone's heart shook, but they hastily controlled their expressions and did not expose themselves.

Oathkeeper suppressed the shock in his heart, acted confused, and said, "Black Star? I know this guy. He only rose in the past few decades and seems to be among the strongest in the universe. It's said that his full strength is unfathomable. How did you get into trouble with him?"

When this was brought up, Sorokin's expression turned gloomy.

"He figured out my identity and came to blackmail me. I decided not to escalate the issue, accepted his request, and partnered with him in businesses at a loss, hoping to fill his appetite so he won't expose me. But that *sshole is too much. He took my money and still wanted to expose my identity, plotting against me behind my back. If I don't teach him a lesson, he's really going to think I can be easily bullied!"

This time, Sorokin's rage was not fake but his real emotions. It was as if he could not live with Black Star being alive and would grab tightly onto any opportunity to kill Black Star.

"So, this is why you wanted to abandon your current identity and retire?" Seeing that Sorokin's expressions were sincere, Oathkeeper pondered.

"That's right. I don't want the three Universal Civilizations to pay attention to me. He forced me to abandon the organization I've spent years building," Sorokin said with a hateful tone.

His hostility toward Han Xiao was extremely strong. Earlier, he even thought of threatening to leak their secret to make the Holy Accord organization help him kill Black Star. With such an unexpected and overwhelmingly strong force, he definitely could get Black Star by surprise.

However, after thinking about it carefully, he had given up on this thought. After all, Black Star had the King suit and would not be trapped. Also, threatening them would definitely make Holy Accord unhappy, and they might not let him join them.

Compared to the secret of the Sanctums, dealing with Black Star did not seem that significant. Therefore, Sorokin did not want to lose the opportunity of finding out about the Sanctum because of something less significant. Furthermore, he had already learned a lesson from what happened today—since he chose to be a coward, he should be a total coward!

Hence, Sorokin did not want to make things more complicated. With the big secret of the Holy Accord opportunity, he decided to abandon the plan of targeting Black Star and retired peacefully. Anyway, he felt that he would always get a better opportunity in the future to make Black Star pay for what he did to him.

Oathkeeper narrowed his eyes and suddenly said, "If you're targeted by Black Star, this is a risk for us too. If we take you in, Black Star might find our location one day by tracking you, leading to us being exposed like today."

Sorokin quickly said, "That won't happen. Black Star is not very obsessed with me personally; he just wants my money and assets. You guys don't know, but that guy is endlessly greedy, domineering, ambitious, slippery, shady, and extremely shameless… His goal is to take over the Limitless Financial Group's assets."

Damn, if not because we made contact with Black Star before, we might have really believed in your nonsense.

… But you're right about him being shameless.

Oathkeeper rolled his eyes in his mind, acted serious, and said, "That's just your speculation. You can't ensure Black Star won't do anything. If you want to join the Holy Accord, it's best to solve this problem first."

Sorokin was frustrated inside. He was already planning to cancel this plan, but to his surprise Holy Accord actively wanted to force him to target Black Star instead.

However, from his perspective, Oathkeeper's worry was totally sensible and logical. Sorokin did not find it strange.

"Honestly, I'm not very confident about fighting Black Star alone. He's too strong…" Sorokin said with resignation.

Oathkeeper gave him a glare and said, "What, are you asking us to help? Don't cross the line! If you think you can threaten us just because you have some leverage on your hands, we'll eliminate you even at the risk of exposing our secret."

He used a strong and firm attitude so that Sorokin would not suspect Holy Accord and Black Star were connected.

"What do you want to do then?" Sorokin asked. He felt that since Oathkeeper had said so many things, there was no way he was still thinking of resorting to such an extreme solution.

Oathkeeper narrowed his eyes and suddenly said with a gentler tone, "Anyway, you can't leave now. We have to ensure your original body is in our sights. However, we won't do anything to you. This is just an insurance measure to prevent you from leaking the secret. As for your request to join the Holy Accord… we'll have to consider it, weigh the pros and cons."

The other Holy Accord members all understood Oathkeeper's intention to take a step back from what he said. They had varied expressions.

"What, are we really going to take him in?" Beiger deliberately acted surprised.

"That is one option. If not, are we really going to let him leak the information?" Oathkeeper turned and glanced at him. He then scanned through everyone and secretly gave them a look. He then turned back to Sorokin and said, "This is my condition. If you don't accept it, there's nothing more to talk about."

Sorokin considered it for a while and realized that he did not have much of a choice. This was already a decent result. Hence, he exhaled and slowly nodded.

"Okay, I agree with your terms. I'm willing to stay under your control temporarily, but you guys can't secretly set up traps to seal soul energy. Although that doesn't work much against me, if you guys show signs of doing it, I'll see it as you guys being insincere about this partnership. I'll consider our agreement invalid and immediately have my manifestation leak your secret."

"Okay." Oathkeeper nodded.

As the two sides came to an agreement, the atmosphere calmed down.

The people approached Sorokin and escorted him toward the Holy Accord's fleet, planning to monitor this guy every second as a new entertainment other than playing cards.

Sorokin obediently let them take him away. He discreetly wiped away his cold sweat, felt that this experience was like a dream and was glad.

"Luckily, I'm convincing enough to earn a chance…"

After the others went away, Oathkeeper was relieved too. He was also planning to keep Sorokin stable first.

Actually, to Oathkeeper, if Sorokin was sincere about joining them, taking him in was not an issue. They had nothing against each other, plus, they were from the same generation and had common topics, and it would prevent Sorokin from leaking their secret.

Holy Accord was not a subsidiary organization of someone else, so there was actually no need to report to Black Star when recruiting a new member. However, Oathkeeper felt it was still better to tell Black Star about this.

After all, Sorokin and Black Star had conflicts, and Oathkeeper was more on Han Xiao's side in his heart. To him, the Black Star Army was a more important partner.

Having thought of that, Oathkeeper closed his eyes and secretly used his soul projection to contact Han Xiao.

…

Oathkeeper's soul projection appeared In Han Xiao's office and saw the person who was dealing with a pile of documents in his seat right away.

Noticing Oathkeeper's arrival, Han Xiao looked up and smiled.

"Yo, Oath, what a rare guest."

Oathkeeper, however, had no intention to chit chat. He said with a deep voice, "Black Star, an emergency situation just happened, and I felt I needed to tell you about it. This might severely impact our plan."

"Tell me then. I didn't cover your mouth." Han Xiao was not nervous at all and joked.

"Just earlier, Sorokin found us…"

Oathkeeper described everything that had happened without leaving any details.

"What? I thought my luck was trash enough. I didn't think yours would also be not much better."

Han Xiao laughed right away. He did not expect Sorokin to be so brave to break into this nursing home.

"How are you still laughing!" Oathkeeper was annoyed. "What do you think we should do about this? If you don't have any suggestion, I'm really going to take him into the Holy Accord!"

"Aiyo, don't be in such a rush. Isn't this very easy to solve?" Han Xiao casually waved.

"What ideas do you have?"

"You've mistaken the situation, which is understandable given how much it concerns you." Han Xiao rested his chin on his hands. "You're worried that he'll leak your information, but he doesn't know my connection with you guys. Therefore, in his eyes, leaking your information is only a threat to the Holy Accord organization, not to me. If you think about it from another perspective, you'll realize that this is good news for me."

"You're saying…" Oathkeeper had a rough idea.

"I never had the chance to secretly attack him. Now, however, you guys have helped me to trap the prey and even indirectly created a secret execution ground. Furthermore, Sorokin has no idea that the leverage he has is also effective on me. All it takes is for us to put on a show, and the problem will be solved. This is the reason for our partnership to exist, basically…"

Han Xiao smiled faintly. A Mark of the Underworld on the back of his palm flickered slightly.

"He's gone."

Chapter 1243: Holy Accord: We Are Serious About Acting!

Two days later, in the Holy Accord's fleet, a group of Primordial Ones sat in a circle around Sorokin, playing cards while keeping an eye on Sorokin at all times to make sure he did not do anything.

Sorokin sat on a small chair in the middle and watched them play cards, giving suggestions from time to time, not acting like an outsider at all.

This time, the door opened. Oathkeeper walked in, and the noise in the room suddenly disappeared. Everyone, including Sorokin, looked over.

Oathkeeper looked around, stopped at Sorokin, and said with a deep voice, "I've considered it over the past two days. I'll accept you into the Holy Accord."

Joy appeared on Sorokin's face. Just as he was about to speak, Oathkeeper stopped him and added, "But before that, you have to resolve your conflict with Black Star. I don't want you to bring problems to the organization."

Hearing this, Sorokin's expression turned serious. "What ideas do you have?"

Oathkeeper slowly said, "First, we have to test the risk, which is how persistent Black Star is about killing you. Therefore, we'll use your location as bait and see if Black Star chases after it."

"How do we do that exactly?"

Oathkeeper opened the star map, pointed at a transit hub planet in the Ancient Star Desert, and said, "We'll find a way to spread rumors saying you've passed by Planet Deere recently, then set up surveillance to see how Black Star reacts to it. If his men come right away to investigate, it means he's indeed hunting you. If Black Star invades Planet Deere's node using Virtual Intrusion, our men will discover it too… To show our sincerity in working together, we'll share the situation reflected by the surveillance with you."

Sorokin thought about it for a moment and agreed with this plan. Although he did not think Black Star would be hunting him, faking his whereabouts would not threaten his safety, so he had no objections. Instead, he was quite impressed by how cautious Oathkeeper was. It suited his taste.

From his perspective, he could totally just retire and not do anything, but Holy Accord was not going to agree with that. They were worried Black Star might find them just like he did. Therefore, they actively wanted to remove the hidden threat. He could not make the decision for the Holy Accord, so he could only cooperate.

"If Beiger is really hunting him, what do we do?" Beiger added.

"Then, there'll only be two ways to solve this problem." Oathkeeper looked at Sorokin, acted like he was troubled, and said, "Either we erase Black Star, or you fake your death to deceive Black Star."

"That makes sense," Beiger added. "Black Star will only give up hunting him if he thinks he's dead. After all, the dead don't speak. Anyway, Sorokin knows how to fake his death; he can just do it again."

Sorokin felt this was logical and nodded. However, thinking about it, he said with a reluctant tone, "But that's too risky. Black Star knows my identity, so he'll definitely be wary about me faking my death. I'm worried that if he discovers it, I'll really be dead…"

Oathkeeper shook his head. "Honestly, that's even more convincing. We have the Sanctums, so if you really die, we can revive you. Not only will the threat be eliminated that way, but you'll really become one of us."

Sorokin laughed awkwardly. "I'd rather pass on that. Plus, he has the Spacetime Amber. I'm worried he might seal me up…"

It sounded like a good plan, but how could he trust the Holy Accord? What if they did not revive him after he died?

Oathkeeper frowned and said with a displeased tone, "This plan has the lowest risk and highest success rate. In the end, you say you want to join the Holy Accord, but you don't see us as being on your side."

"I'm really very sincere about joining the Holy Accord, but trust needs to be developed over time…"

Sorokin looked troubled but complained inside.

This plan means you guys are only bearing the minimum risk. Basically, you don't have to do anything at all. The problem will be solved regardless of whether I'm really dead or not…

Conversely, fighting Black Star was very risky for Holy Accord but much less risky for him, so of course, he favored this plan more.

"Humph, so you're still forcing us to help you to kill Black Star." Violet Queen snorted.

Sorokin had nothing to say.

"… We'll talk about it when the time comes. Let's see if Black Star responds to the fake information first."

Oathkeeper purposely glanced at Sorokin with dissatisfaction. He did not say much and left.

Not long later, through secret channels, the intelligence that Sorokin passed by Planet Deere got spread out. At the same time, the Holy Accord organization set up many men on Planet Deere for surveillance.

Time passed day by day, and the information got spread further. As they did not know if Black Star had received the news yet, they could only wait and stare at the surveillance screens all day.

As this involved him personally, Sorokin was most concerned about it. He stared at the screens every second.

After almost ten days, the Holy Accord organization finally got the intelligence that one fleet from the Ancient Star Desert subdivision of the Black Star Army had arrived on Planet Deere and was searching for Sorokin's information on the planet.

…

"The situation is very clear. Black Star is indeed hunting you closely. You've brought us risk!"

In the remote surveillance room, Oathkeeper glared at Sorokin, his tone very displeased.

Sorokin did not reply. He looked extremely frustrated, and his heart sank.

He could not oppose this solid proof; he did not expect Black Star to want to kill him so much that he was hunting him secretly.

So, this guy not only wants my money but even my life!

What an evil man!

F*ck, although I tricked you several times in the past, I've already paid the price for that! Black Star, why do you want me dead so much‽

This time, Oathkeeper said with a deep voice, "You really are not willing to fake your death to fool Black Star?"

"No." Sorokin shook his head without hesitation.

Oathkeeper looked distressed. He walked back and forth, annoyed, as if he was hesitating.

After quite some time, he spoke reluctantly like he had finally made a difficult situation.

"Since that's the case, we can only eliminate Black Star!"

As soon as he said that, the other Primordial Ones were instantly 'appalled' and expressed their strong objection.

"We have no conflict with Black Star. Why should we mess with such a strong enemy just for Sorokin?"

"Wouldn't fighting Black Star also leak our existence?"

"This guy is just threatening us. Don't fall for it!"

The elevated emotions of everyone startled Sorokin. He did not dare express his opinion.

"Stop!" Oathkeeper argued with them for a bit. He then raised his voice and said firmly, "There'll be no next time!"

Then, he glared at Sorokin and coldly said, "Are you satisfied now?"

"Nonsense, I'm not the one forcing you guys to deal with Black Star. This is your decision. I'd rather ignore him." Sorokin sighed and expressed this was not his fault.

He was originally not planning to threaten the Holy Accord organization to fight Black Star because he would offend them that way. However, he was not the one making the choice.

In his position, he could not change their stubborn opinions and convince the Holy Accord to ignore Black Star. It was like someone who owed loan sharks a lot of money and took refuge in someone else's home, not only causing them trouble, but also attempting to convince them to put up with the loan sharks' harassment… Even Sorokin felt that was a little bit shameless.

Oathkeeper snorted and said slowly, "All and all, you brought the trouble, so you'll have to solve it. Since Black Star is hunting you, you'll be the bait to lure him into the trap."

"Alone?" Sorokin asked.

"Of course, three of us will accompany you, both to prevent you from escaping and to help you fight Black Star." Oathkeeper shook his head. "As for the rest of us, we'll set up an ambush far away and join the battle when the time is right."

"Will that even work? Black Star has the King suit and is not afraid of being outnumbered," Beiger added, displaying his expertise as an actor.

"Don't worry, Black Star will never expect there to be dozens of us, and that's our biggest advantage! The trap set up by Sorokin will only have four people. It's only our first measure but will seem like the whole ambush to Black Star. With Black Star's strength, he's unlikely to flee against four people and will definitely try to fight. Therefore, the team with Sorokin's mission will be to stall Black Star." Oathkeeper's tone sounded like this was real.

"Then?"

"Try to create an opportunity, of course! The dozens of us will be accumulating energy. As long as you can temporarily control Black Star and make him not have the time to use the King suit, Sorokin, we'll charge right in with Beiger's teleportation spell, attacking him all at the same time, while having those who excel in the soul territory try to heavily damage Black Star's soul!"

Oathkeeper's tone was very firm and filled with confidence. Even he almost believed it.

Sorokin analyzed the plan and felt that the success rate was much higher than for him to act alone.

He believed that as long as Black Star did not use the Spacetime Amber to guard against the attacks, even he would most likely not be able to endure the focus fire of dozens of Beyond Grade As.

Although Soul Flame was not in his hands, Oathkeeper could use it all the same. Furthermore, there were not just the two of them who excelled in the soul territory in the Holy Accord organization, which made Sorokin feel there was an even higher chance of succeeding.

"This plan should work. The success rate is probably above seventy percent. The entire galactic society practically sees Black Star as a god, but he definitely has limits no matter how strong he is."

Sorokin was relieved and expressed his support for the plan.

Seeing that the fish had bitten the bit, knowing the ways of fishing very well, Oathkeeper said with a warning tone and a deep voice, "Don't be glad so soon. You'd best pray this plan succeeds. Otherwise, if Black Star escapes, he'll definitely leak our information too. Then, your leverage will be meaningless, and I'll hold you responsible for it. You can make a guess on what we'll do to you… Therefore, for your own sake too, you'd better give your all in this mission!"

Hearing this, Sorokin's expression turned serious, and he nodded firmly.

…

Half a month later, in a certain desolate universe belt of the Ancient Star Desert, a small spaceship hovered. There were only four people in the spaceship—Sorokin, Beiger, and two other Beyond Grade As.

Beiger stood with his arms crossed. He glanced at Sorokin who was beside and said with an unsatisfied tone, "Tsk, I never thought I'd have to fight alongside you one day. Unlucky."

"Tsk, you think I'm happy to see your face?" Sorokin snorted. He did not want to argue with him. He changed the topic and said, "It's been so long—will Black Star really come?"

"Who knows? We've already sent the coordinates out; it all depends on how strong his love for you is," Beiger joked.

Sorokin was about to strike back when an unwelcome guest entered the range of his senses. His expression changed immediately.

"Someone's here."

The other three sensed it too and became silent. They looked in the direction of the presence they felt outside the porthole.

After a while, an asteroid approached extremely quickly. It seemed to have noticed the four of them too. It stopped not far away, and a familiar face appeared.

"It's Black Star! He's really here!"

Sorokin's expression turned grave. He flew out of the cabin and stood opposite Han Xiao. Beiger and the other two followed along.

Han Xiao scanned through the few of them and laughed in the public channel.

"Yoho, I see, you deliberately leaked your coordinates to lure me into a trap, huh? So, the information about your whereabouts some time ago was fake information you made up and spread purposely… Hehe, I don't know where you got the help from, but Sorokin, oh Sorokin, aren't you underestimating me too much, daring to attack me with just four people?"

"Black Star, I didn't expect you to be so persistent in chasing me. You're too much! Don't blame me. You left me no choice!"

This was what Sorokin was most irritated by. From the way he looked at it, he was the one who incurred much larger losses, yet Black Star hunted him nonstop. It was too excessive.

"Sorry, I'm not a forgiving person. You've plotted against me one too many times. There'll be quite a number of problems with letting you escape. Therefore, it's better for you to live inside my Spacetime Amber suite, safe and sound."

While speaking in the public channel, Han Xiao glanced at Beiger and the other two with mockery in his eyes.

There were only five people there and supposedly two sides, but there were three group chats. One was the public channel, and another was the temporary combat group chat Sorokin, Beiger, and the other two were in.

The third was the 'actor' group chat that Han Xiao, Beiger, the other two Beyond Grade As, and all the Holy Accord members ambushing far away were in. Basically, everyone except Sorokin.

"Do it!"

Sorokin did not want to bullsh*t with Han Xiao and attacked right away while also telling Beiger and the other two to attack together.

Seeing how much of a hurry Sorokin was in, everyone was laughing out loud nonstop in the actor group.

"He's getting impatient…"

"Hahaha, why do I suddenly feel pitiful for him?"

"It's so tragic. I can hardly watch."

"You'd better take a few more looks. I'm afraid we'll never see him again…"

The people joked around. The actor group chat was filled with a joyful atmosphere.

"Stop it. We're in the middle of a performance. Be serious about it," Han Xiao said while laughing. He summoned his mechanical army and charged into Sorokin's attacks.

Beiger and the other two hastily joined the battle. They did their best not to burst into laughter and fought alongside Sorokin as if they were really on his side.

The battle broke up instantly. The energy left by the five of them left scorch marks in space.

The opportunity only existed for the blink of an eye. If they could not annihilate Sorokin instantly, this guy would still have time to leak the information. Now was not the time yet, so the Holy Accord was still performing for Sorokin.

Sorokin thought victory was in his hands and focused entirely on fighting Han Xiao. However, what he did not know was that the teammates he had high hopes in were all actors ready to backstab him any second.

Chapter 1244: Suppressed

The mechanical army circled around like crows, releasing streams of energy, wrecking the battlefield. Han Xiao himself changed into one of the Black King series gears and fought intensely with four opponents.

The battle looked ferocious, but Sorokin was actually the only one fighting for real. His three teammates only used about sixty percent of their strength, and Han Xiao was slowly accumulating bonuses.

Beiger could clearly feel that the attacks of Han Xiao's army were several levels weaker than the last time and not as pressurizing as before. He instantly understood that Han Xiao was also holding back.

Han Xiao's strength had rocketed recently. In order to let Sorokin still have hope, he deliberately decreased the damage output of the army to only slightly stronger than the last time he showed his strength in public, creating a situation where both sides were on par.

He was not worried about Sorokin finding out—the two of them had never fought before, so Sorokin's judgement of his strength all came from the information on the internet. Since he had never experienced it for himself, he did not have a clear understanding of how strong Han Xiao was. Han Xiao just had to display about the same amount of strength as the information available to the public said he had, and Sorokin would think it was his actual strength.

Sorokin was indeed quite strong. His soul Esper Ability was very tough to deal with, applying all kinds of debuffs on Han Xiao. Han Xiao did not activate [Kunde Rage] and [Thousand Soul Stream] for the time being, so it was not a breeze for him either. Putting other things aside, Han Xiao estimated that this guy's Energy Rank was above 90,000, undoubtedly in the top tier of the universe.

Sadly, this guy is fragile.

Han Xiao curled his lips in his mind. No matter how incredible the fragile individuals were in terms of combat, they had limits—only tanks had an infinite future.

Sorokin's body was weaker than the average of those around the same Energy Rank as him, but destroying his physical body would not kill him. With [Immortal Soul], [Spiritual Energy Foundation], and other talents, Sorokin's soul was the foundation of his life. His soul could live without a physical body.

Furthermore, Sorokin had the [Fleshly Body Reconstruction] ability. He did not have to infest or take over another's body like Psychics; he could build a new shell for himself with his soul energy any time. To him, physical bodies were just replaceable vessels for his soul; his soul was his original body.

Through the introduction of [Immortal Soul] on the interface, Han Xiao knew that Sorokin was immune to physical attacks when in the soul state, while also having very high resistances, it was very difficult to deal with. Destroying his physical body would only lead to Sorokin entering his 'second phase'.

For that, the trump card he had prepared was the Mark of The Underworld. The Underworld at its peak had a special restraining effect on all souls; it was the arch enemy of souls.

Han Xiao' goal was to find an opportunity to destroy Sorokin's physical body in the blink of an eye, force his soul to be isolated, drag his soul right into the Underworld, and have the experts inside send him up happily.

Meanwhile, Sorokin was also making plans in his mind.

Black Star's strength is about the same as what I predicted. He's indeed strong but not as exaggerated as the rumors say. With this level of strength he has, the success rate of this ambush is higher than planned.

Sorokin felt confident.

Remaining in the passive situation was very disadvantageous for him. Although he had found the Holy Accord's weak spot, his safety was still in their hands. This leverage would only be much more useful once he escaped the Holy Accord's control, or it would only keep him alive and nothing else… The Holy Accord organization indeed did not want to be exposed, but even if they were exposed, they would only get in trouble while he would almost certainly be dead. The scale was unbalanced, so there was not much room for negotiation.

He felt an opportunity to escape might appear the moment the ambush succeeded. However, as a soul Esper, his mobility was awful, and his odds of escaping were too low.

I shall follow the plan and find a chance to capture Black Star first, then improvise from there.

Sorokin focused his thoughts, pressed between his eyes, and sent another few hundred soul energy attacks right toward Han Xiao.

The five of them were all waiting for a chance.

The battle went back and forth for quite some time when, suddenly, Han Xiao's movements became stiff as if he had endured too many soul energy attacks.

"Now!"

Before Sorokin spoke, Beiger suddenly yelled in the group chat and took over the heavy responsibility of setting the tempo.

Intense magic energy erupted from all over his body. Control type spells he had been preparing all this time flew out rapidly and all landed on Han Xiao.

The other Beyond Grade As followed instantly and threw out all their control type abilities together.

Ohm!

Energy of all colors and forms tangled around him, seemingly fixing him in midair, unable to move.

Seeing the opportunity, Sorokin followed up right away. With his eyes wide open, energy shockwaves that almost materialized were launched rapidly one after another, penetrating Han Xiao's body, instantly applying all kinds of debuffs on him.

The next moment, Beiger raised his hand. A teleportation circle appeared on the battlefield, and dozens of Beyond Grade As swarmed out instantly, all holding onto charged attacks prepared long ago, ready to launch them at Han Xiao.

However, at this time, Han Xiao's body shook. He seemingly used some kind of ability to escape from all the control abilities.

He actually did not do anything; Beiger and the other two secretly deactivated their abilities.

As for Sorokin's abilities, he gained immunity to the tons of debuffs by activating [Kunde Rage] in advance and was not affected at all.

Even the opportunity was sold by Han Xiao; Beiger only cooperated following the script discussed in the actors group chat and made Sorokin mistakenly think the opportunity had come when it was actually Han Xiao's signal.

The sudden change happened in a fraction of a second. Before Sorokin could react, Han Xiao immediately used Void Hyperdrive after he was freed and appeared right before Sorokin. He then pressed Sorokin into his wide arms.

"You…"

Shock appeared on Sorokin's face. It was as if a huge red "DANGER" appeared above his head.

Before he finished his sentence, the dozens of Beyond Grade As attacked the two of them instantly!

The mechanical army also turned to fire at the two of them, this time, at full output!

Han Xiao activated all his explosive abilities directly followed by Virtual Soul to restrain Sorokin. The two of them stood still and watched countless attacks approaching rapidly.

The next second, the two of them were submerged by a blinding light.

Hong!

The attacks turned into a cluster of rapidly expanding energy, sweeping in all directions. The horrifying energy almost robbed the senses of everyone present, and all they could see was white.

Hu!

The cluster of light expanded to the maximum and exploded abruptly. The energy shockwave erupted from the center and blew away everything around.

The light dissipated quickly. Han Xiao was the only one left, covered in wounds that were gushing blood nonstop like a water bag with dozens of holes. He was clearly severely injured.

The attacks of dozens of Beyond Grade As' trump cards and the mechanical army dealt the most terrifying amount of damage to Han Xiao he had ever experienced. The [Perfect Energy Affinity Physique] and [Proof of Leadership] were the reasons he survived. Plus, Han Xiao wore the 'Defense Gear' of the Black King series. Though already completely shattered, it still blocked tons of damage. Otherwise, he might have had to use the revive token.

As for Sorokin, his physical body had been blown to atoms in the explosion.

Someone else would have completely died in this situation, but for Sorokin, this was only him entering his second phase!

Streams of light suddenly illuminated in front of Han Xiao, forming a glowing green energy entity with Sorokin's appearance.

At the same time, a mind message sounded in Han Xiao's mind.

"The attack worked… Looks like your Indestructible Body isn't really eternally indestructible."

Sorokin was secretly glad.

Luckily, the foundation of his survival was not his physical body. When his soul separated from his body, there was a moment his soul was in the phased invincible state, or that round of attacks would also have heavily damaged him. As for now, his soul was at the peak state.

One more round and Black Star will definitely be dead!

Without hesitation, Sorokin launched a chain of soul shockwaves onto Han Xiao, attempting to stop Han Xiao from escaping with the King.

Then, he backed away immediately through Han Xiao's arms, planning to increase the distance between the two of them. At the same time, he yelled in the mission channel for others to use this opportunity to launch another round of attacks.

However, as Sorokin was about to back off, Han Xiao raised and shoved his hand into Sorokin's soul. The Mark of The Underworld on the back of his palm instantly lit up, and an astonishingly strong absorption force erupted from it.

"What is this‽"

Sorokin was stunned. This mark felt like a vortex. His soul suddenly went out of his control. Before he could do anything, an irresistible force dragged him inside.

"I got him!" Han Xiao spit out a mouth of boiling blood and grinned.

These changes seemed like they had taken a very long time to occur, when actually it all happened in an extremely short amount of time. If not because all of the Holy Accord cooperated and held back, he would not have been able to defeat Sorokin so easily.

However, only half of the plan succeeded. The problem was not yet completely solved.

"Follow me!"

Han Xiao put on the King while at the same time throwing out a few extras at Oathkeeper and a few other Beyond Grade As who were experts in the soul territory.

The mechanical suit latched onto them automatically. The next moment, Han Xiao shot out a few streams of Mechanical Force and activated the Kings on all of them.

With a flash of light, they disappeared.

…

Plop!

Sorokin felt the world was spinning. He fell onto a black stone ground.

At this time, the unknown energy that pulled his soul only finally faded. Sorokin flew up immediately and observed his surroundings cautiously. He had no idea where Black Star had sent him.

His eyes scanned through the boisterous land. An odd sense of familiarity surfaced in his mind.

Suddenly, Sorokin suddenly remembered something. His soul trembled, and his expression changed drastically.

"Is this the… Underworld‽"

As a Primordial One from the exploration era, he had also heard of the two sisters and was no stranger to the existence of the Underworld.

The only thing left in Sorokin's heart was disbelief.

Aren't the two sisters dead? How does the Underworld still exist‽

Why did Black Star send me here‽

While he was being appalled, Onicelu appeared before him out of thin air and gave him an odd smile that made him feel threatened.

"Sh*t!"

Sorokin had no time to think carefully. He hastily rushed up the sky hoping to flee from the Underworld.

If this was another secondary dimension, he would not have been so afraid. However, all Primordial Ones knew that all independent souls were severely countered by the Underworld.

The Underworld was the nemesis of all souls! A forbidden ground feared by all soul life forms!

Onicelu remained in the same place and did not chase after Sorokin, all she did was extend her arm, aimed at Sorokin who was getting further away and tightened her fist.

Buzz!

The Underworld moved according to her will. A mysterious force suddenly appeared, pressing all Hero Spirits in the Underworld onto the ground.

Underworld—Soul Restrain!

The Underworld had recovered to its peak. Onicelu was a professional at dealing with souls!

Even though Sorokin's soul was extremely unique and had Beyond Grade A combat capability, his flight speed still decreased by ninety percent, and his altitude continued to decrease.

With the same smile on her face, Onicelu performed a 'pull' gesture.

Underworld—Soul Arrest!

Thick Underworld energy flowed out from the black ground, turning into countless tentacles that shot up the sky and ensnared Sorokin, trying to pull him down.

Although souls could penetrate all kinds of physical objects, they could not penetrate the energy of the Underworld and would instead be stuck. Sorokin used all his strength to try to escape from the tentacles but could only just keep himself from being dragged down further.

Hu!

At this time, a red tornado rose on the horizon, and Hila appeared. She had been waiting there since long ago.

"It's you!"

Sorokin was astonished. His soul was not immune to soul attacks; Hila happened to counter him.

"Go down!"

Hila waved her hand. Death energy gushed out like a raging river and brushed Sorokin's soul down.

Sorokin fell onto the black ground. Onicelu moved her index finger, and chains formed by Underworld energy extended from the underground. They penetrated Sorokin's soul and locked him down in multiple layers.

While Sorokin was clenching his teeth and trying to escape, a group of people suddenly appeared before him. It was Han Xiao, Oathkeeper, and the others who arrived by the Kings' teleportation. They all took off the mechanical suits.

Seeing this, Han Xiao smiled. "Looks like you had a fun time with my friends."

Seeing Oathkeeper and Han Xiao appearing together, Sorokin was completely dumbfounded.

At this moment, he understood everything.

"You guys are on the same side‽"

Sorokin was filled with rage and shock. Without hesitation, he immediately tried to contact his manifestation and expose all their secrets.

However, he was dumbfounded once again the next second.

His connections with his manifestations were all cut off!

"Why do you think I spent so much effort to get you in here? In here, unless approved by the Underworld's consciousness, no one can send soul signals to the outside world. Oathkeeper could not block your ability with absolute certainty, but the Underworld can."

Han Xiao lightly stepped on the black stone ground under his feet.

"After all… the initial function of the Underworld was a prison!"

Chapter 1245: Welcome to the Underworld

Oathkeeper looked around and said with a surprised tone, "I didn't expect the trump card you mentioned to be the Underworld. I thought they perished along with the two sisters."

When the actor chat group was discussing the plan, Han Xiao had said he had a trump card that could disable Sorokin's ability, and he just needed an opportunity. He did not say what the trump card exactly was. Since the others had the same goal as him, and Black Star was usually quite reliable, Oathkeeper trusted him.

Only now did the Holy Accord members present discover that the trump card Han Xiao spoke of was the Underworld, which they were familiar with.

"Did the two sisters revive too?" Beiger asked with shock.

"Nope, the Underworld has a new master now."

Han Xiao shook his head, told Hila to land beside him, and patted her shoulder. He did not share the detailed information about the two sisters' inheritance.

At this time, the seven Hero Spirit Kings suddenly appeared around Sorokin and sized up the Holy Accord members present with shock and disbelief.

"You guys are still alive‽"

"What, you guys too‽"

The few Holy Accord members and the seven Hero Spirit Kings looked at each other with dismay.

Both sides were Primordial Ones who chose different paths of reviving. Both achieved that goal at this point. Meeting each other in the modern age after countless years, they felt complicated and surprised.

However, comparatively, the seven Hero Spirit Kings felt somewhat regretful.

They thought the Holy Accord was nonsense and the path they chose was the only right one. They never expected the Holy Accord to really succeed…

I should've joined the Holy Accord back then!

Looking at this, Sorokin was already completely dumbfounded.

The existence of the Holy Accord was already unbelievable enough. He never would have thought the Underworld still existed too. So many Primordial Ones lived till now, and he was not the only one at all.

Sorokin suddenly felt that his sense of superiority all these years was nothing but a joke.

This time, Han Xiao squatted, leveled with Sorokin's eyes, and said slowly, "I'm someone who always prefers to give others a chance to make a choice. There are two paths in front of you now. One, get wiped out by us, and you will then become fertilizer for Hila. Two, become an Underworld Hero Spirit and be controlled by the Underworld. Which do you choose?"

Sorokin was a top-level combatant. The external enemies of the explored universe had yet to be dealt with, so Han Xiao preferred not to eliminate him.

In fact, if not because Sorokin accidentally found out the Holy Accord's secret, Han Xiao would not even have targeted him. He was only displeased about how many times Sorokin plotted against him in the past and felt this guy was too much of an *sshole, but he did not see him as someone he had to kill.

Now that Sorokin was completely in his hands, Han Xiao almost wanted to say some classic villain lines… Go on and scream, no one will come!

Sorokin looked around at everyone and said with indignation, "What… are you guys planning‽"

It was horrifying to find out that Black Star was both related to the Holy Accord and the Underworld. In fact, it was unfathomable. He felt Han Xiao was certainly planning something big secretly, and he could almost smell the stink of conspiracy.

Are these people trying to overthrow the universe‽

Also, since Black Star is together with these guys, is he also one of the Primordial Ones who lived till now‽

Having discovered these secrets and linking them with Black Star's history, Sorokin could not help but to fantasize in this direction.

"You think I'd tell you now?"

Han Xiao chuckled.

Telling the enemy all my plans when the mission is about to succeed is a huge no-no for villains. I'm not going to fall for it.

This time, the seven Hero Spirit Kings had heard about Sorokin's real identity from Oathkeeper. The head of the Hero Spirit Kings, Rega, walked over, patted Sorokin's shoulder, and comforted him. "Stop hesitating. When you join the Underworld, you'll realize that it's nice to be a Hero Spirit."

"Rega, you got domesticated too?" Sorokin said sarcastically. They were all from the same generation, so of course, he knew the seven Hero Spirit Kings.

Rega was not offended. He smiled and said, "Don't make it sound so bad. As long as the Underworld still exists, Hero Spirits will never die. You've borderline survived in the main universe for so long, I'm sure you're not willing to die. What's so bad about being happy with us? You'll never have to worry about being killed, think about it."

The other Hero Spirit Kings also started to enthusiastically promote the advantages of becoming a Hero Spirit King. It was like a company's interviewer promoting the company's benefits during an interview.

It was not that they actually cared about Soul Emperor's life, but living in the Underworld while not being able to go out was quite dull. The seven Hero Spirit Kings already knew everything there was to know about each other, the freshness was long gone. Now that a possible new member was finally here, they did not want to let him get away.

Even the Holy Accord members on the side nodded in agreement.

The history of the exploration era already proved that as long as the Underworld was fine, the Hero Spirits could do whatever dangerous things they wanted to. Honestly, they were quite jealous too.

Since Oathkeeper had hidden some of the Sanctums' information due to certain reasons, the current Holy Accord members all thought that they could only be revived once. Seeing the Underworld, they also started to have some ideas.

They originally thought they could only revive once, but with the Underworld, would that not mean they could keep living?

Although they would have to become someone else's subordinate… as long as they could live, what was so bad about becoming dogs!

"Black Star is closely related to the Underworld. I have to maintain a good relationship with him…" Beiger mumbled softly, saying what everyone was thinking.

Han Xiao heard his whisper and laughed in his mind.

This was part of the reason he had brought them to the Underworld. Using the fact that the Holy Accord members did not know the truth about the Sanctums, he increased the importance of the Underworld in the ears of the revived Primordial Ones so that his plan in the future would be easier to execute.

Even those Holy Accord members with other goals could not ignore his existence for the sake of having a backup plan, which meant he could influence these people and prevent them from doing things too out of the line to a certain extent.

Seeing Sorokin was shaken, Han Xiao said, "You already love to cower. Now you're just cowering somewhere else. Plus, you won't have to worry about your safety. What's there to hesitate about?"

Sorokin stayed silent for a while. He sighed with frustration and resignation. "… I admit I'm done for. I'm willing to join the Underworld."

He always believed in living as a coward was better than dying a hero, so he had no choice but to say goodbye to freedom and choose to live with regrets.

Han Xiao looked like he expected and gave Onicelu a look.

Onicelu raised her hand. Clusters of Underworld energy flowed out from the ground and hovered beside Sorokin. She then smiled and said, "Lower your guard and accept the transformation. It might hurt a little, but don't resist no matter what, alright?"

Swoosh!

Before Sorokin responded, the Underworld energy rushed into his soul the next moment.

The color of Sorokin's soul was gradually painted with the Underworld energy's color as he transformed into a Hero Spirit.

Sorokin felt like burning iron bars penetrated his soul. His soul was scorching from inside out as if it was going to be burnt to ashes any second.

Seeing this, the seven Hero Spirit Kings were so overjoyed they wanted to beat the drums on the side to welcome another unlucky fellow joining them.

The Hero Spirit transformation lasted for quite some time before finishing.

The chains formed by Underworld energy disappeared. Without them, Sorokin slowly stood up, looked down at his soul that had now turned into an Underworld Hero Spirit, and felt his connection with the Underworld. He was filled with complicated emotions.

After so many years of cowering, to think he became an Underworld Hero Spirit he once despised; fate was really full of surprises…

The seven Hero Spirit Kings surrounded him and smiled passionately.

"From now on, you're the eighth Hero Spirit King. Welcome to the Underworld!"

"Hehe…"

Sorokin could not laugh at all. His lips were twitching.

Onicelu suddenly turned to look at Han Xiao and said, "He's not like the other Hero Spirit Kings. Although he's transformed, he still kept his original strength."

Han Xiao expected this. He asked, "He's special, can you restrain him?"

"That's not a problem. After being transformed into a Hero Spirit, he's already connected to the Underworld and is under my control." Onicelu nodded.

"That's good." Han Xiao nodded.

Normal Hero Spirits had no combat capability. They could only regain their strength with the help of life energy. However, Sorokin had [Immortal Soul] and [Spiritual Energy Foundation], so he maintained the strength of a Beyond Grade A even as a Hero Spirit. This was his uniqueness.

However, after the developments made by the two sisters, the Underworld was already a treasure close to the Space Wonder level. Its operating mechanisms were impeccable, so restraining Sorokin when it was at its peak state was not a problem.

Seeing that Sorokin's face was filled with regret, Han Xiao smiled and said, "Stop being so down. One day in the future, you might be glad you joined the Underworld."

"I don't think that day will ever come." Sorokin was filled with sadness.

"Hehe, we'll see."

Han Xiao smiled and shook his head.

With the increase of his strength, position, and connections, the enemies he once felt were tough to deal with were no longer so tough. Having gotten rid of another hidden threat, he was quite satisfied.

Sorokin's value was not just his strength; the resources and information this guy had was also very valuable.

Having thought of that, Han Xiao turned to Hila and said, "Go talk to Sorokin and have him share the information he knows."

Hila nodded and pulled Sorokin aside to question him. As the current master of the Underworld, she was perfect for this task.

Seeing that Sorokin had been dealt with, the Holy Accord members present were all relieved. They went to chat with the seven Hero Spirit Kings about the old times.

On the other hand, Han Xiao and Oathkeeper walked to the side on their own and talked about something else.

"How's the collection of the Third Sanctum keys?"

"Still working hard on it. With the experience from the last time and the channels you provided, it should be much quicker this time," Oathkeeper replied.

"Do it fast. I have a feeling that the peaceful times won't last too long," Han Xiao whispered.

He still had missions related to the Sanctums that were not yet complete. Even not for the missions, since the Sanctums were the future of the Beyond Grade As, he had to go in and take a look.

Oathkeeper nodded. He suddenly changed the topic and asked, "Although I'm not in the Beyond Grade A Association, won't Sorokin suddenly going missing cause problems?"

Han Xiao glanced at him and said with a deep voice, "Yes, Gaud went missing a few years ago and now Sorokin too. It's easy for people to link these two events… However, the difference is, no one will step up for Sorokin, so the problem won't be too big, and the impact won't be too strong. It'll mainly cause doubts among the association itself and investigations."

"It won't affect you, will it?"

"Not much if it's dealt with properly. The dynasty has been secretly investigating Sorokin recently. I can find a way to make Sorokin look responsible for what happened to Gaud, then fake the reason he went missing, saying he fled due to fear of having what he did discover. Thus, creating a motive for him and closing the case… As for the future, there's no need to worry if others discover Sorokin is here. His Esper Ability allows him to change his soul frequency, which will solve most problems."

Han Xiao was prepared for this.

Sorokin was now tied up to the fate of the Underworld. Although he had no freedom, it was not all bad. Han Xiao was someone who knew Sorokin's personality well. This guy's biggest trait was that he knew his situation well. He would basically never do something that would damage both parties, so there was no need to worry about him not cooperating.

Oathkeeper agreed. "As long as you have a plan. You're an expert at these shady things."

"Sarcasm, huh? Don't copy my words." Han Xiao glanced at him.

The two of them did not chat for long. The other Holy Accord members were still waiting in the main universe. Han Xiao used another King suit to send Oathkeeper back to explain what had happened to prevent them from worrying.

After sending the outsiders away, Han Xiao went to where Hila and Sorokin were. The two of them sat opposite each other. One asked, and the other answered; the atmosphere was peaceful.

Although Sorokin had regrets, what was done was done. He had no choice but to let go of his pride. He was quite cooperative.

Han Xiao walked beside Hila and asked, "How's it going?"

Hila looked up at him and had a playful expression.

"You came at the right time. He seems to have just said something huge…"

Chapter 1246: Confession and Doubts

"You played a part in making the Tragedy Of The Pinnacles happen?"

After hearing the interrogation results, Han Xiao could not help but size Sorokin up with surprise.

"I've changed many identities and have always been trying to reduce the number of Beyond Grade As in the universe. But as you can see, the Holy Accord and the Underworld found ways to revive them, so that's a dead end."

Sorokin was hopeless.

After entering the Underworld, there were no secrets that he could keep anymore. Plus, Hila could control him anytime.

Reducing the number of Beyond Grade As was his old goal. However, as he found out about the Holy Accord and the Underworld, he immediately knew that there was no way this plan would ever work. He was forced to change his mindset.

Sorokin shared all the other identities he had once used and confessed the fact he secretly assisted in making the Tragedy of the Pinnacles happen. He knew his situation very well; no matter how unwilling he was inside, he knew that this past of his had the potential to become a ticking time bomb in the future, so he actively brought it up.

If he kept it hidden, although he might have a chance to mess with Han Xiao, if the Underworld was damaged because of it, he would be affected too. As the saying went, if he could not resist, he might as well enjoy it. At least the Underworld Hero Spirits had almost infinite life. Although it was not what he really wanted, it was not too bad either. He had no choice but to protect this only remaining privilege he had.

After hearing the various identities Sorokin shared, Han Xiao tutted and said, "So, they were all you. You really love causing chaos."

Initially, he had been thinking about how to frame Sorokin for what happened to Gaud, but now it seemed easy. Sorokin had so many identities in the past and a history of guiding the Tragedy of the Pinnacles. There was his motive!

As for clues and evidence, with Sorokin right there, he was not worried about not finding them.

Han Xiao put this thought behind him for the time being and said, "Let's put this aside first. Tell me the resources you have, such as secret warehouses, internal intelligence of the Limitless Financial Group, business secrets… Be honest. If you cooperate, I might consider leaving you some."

Sorokin knew that Han Xiao had his eyes on his assets and wanted to get all the benefits he could get from him. He was unwilling in his heart, but Hila was right beside them, and he had no choice but to truthfully share everything.

Han Xiao noted them down and could not help but be impressed.

"Not bad, not bad. You've accumulated quite a lot of good things. Other than technology, blueprints, and knowledge, you even secretly collected eight Universal Treasures…"

If not because I have Jayz's treasure trove, my inventory would also be about this much.

Being rich is really nice!

As for the Limitless Financial Group, it was a huge cake. Although Han Xiao wanted to eat it all, he had to control his appetite, or it would cause suspicion.

After Sorokin 'escaped due to fear of having what he did to Gaud discovered', the Limitless Financial Group would definitely be severely impacted and dissected by tons of organizations. Han Xiao did not plan to enter the scene in advance. He planned to have the Germinal Financial Group act together with the other organizations after Sorokin was discovered to have gone missing. Making sure he could get a piece of the cake was enough; being too greedy was not a wise idea.

However, as for the 'backup plans' Sorokin secretly prepared by using the Limitless Financial Group's funds, he could take all of them.

After Sorokin was done, Han Xiao put away the notebook with satisfaction and grinned.

"Alright, what needs to be said has been said. Spend some time getting used to staying here… Hila, take care of this guy. I'll be going back."

Hila nodded with a poker face. "Don't worry, I'll take care of him."

She emphasized the words 'take care'. Han Xiao instantly remembered how much of a battle maniac Hila was and could not help but secretly pity Sorokin.

He did not have the time to spar with Hila, while as the only Hero Spirit who had Beyond Grade A strength in the Underworld, Sorokin was clearly the perfect opponent. Since he could not be killed, she could kill him again and again!

Han Xiao gave Sorokin a weird glance, shook his head, and disappeared in his King suit.

Seeing this, Sorokin sighed. He felt that life was so magical. All he could do now was adapt to the new life.

This time, the seven Hero Spirit Kings approached him, smiling.

"Eighth, let's chat. How about you start by telling us what big things happened in the universe in these years? We're so curious."

Sorokin's face turned black.

"Who's Eighth? Don't disturb me. Scram!"

…

Days passed one after another. Not long after Sorokin went missing, the galactic society finally noticed that the head of the Limitless Financial Group had not appeared in quite some time.

Although very few people could see Sorokin to begin with, he was the head of a top consortium in the universe and was quite famous. Sooner or later, people were bound to notice.

Without the orders from their leader, the Limitless Financial Group was becoming quite chaotic.

While the entire galactic society was wondering, the Crimson Dynasty suddenly announced a wanted order. The target was indeed Sorokin!

The dynasty claimed that they had made a breakthrough in their investigation. They disclosed Sorokin's real identity and his many identities, listed the many crimes he had committed—including guiding the Tragedy of the Pinnacles—and even claimed that Sorokin was deeply connected with Gaud going missing. They stated that Sorokin was missing because he had fled, so they announced a wanted order to find him.

Ever since Han Xiao hinted Sorokin's identity to the dynasty upper echelons, the dynasty had been secretly investigating Sorokin in every way possible. Using this opportunity, Han Xiao left some related evidence provided by Sorokin. He did not do anything personally but instead secretly guided the dynasty to discover the evidence in the process of the investigation, exposing what Sorokin had done.

As soon as the news was announced, the entire galactic society was in an uproar. Countless galactic residents and organizations were shocked by this news!

All along, Sorokin's image in everyone's eyes was a wildly successful businessman, the owner of a universal consortium, and a Beyond Grade A who did not like violence. His business talent overshadowed his Beyond Grade A identity in the eyes of the galactic society. No one had ever thought Sorokin had such a big secret, that a universally renowned businessman was the secret mastermind of so many incidents!

For some time, the popularity of topics surrounding Sorokin shot through the sky. His history was too legendary. Almost everyone uncontrollably made wild assumptions and speculations; conspiracies became popular.

As this went on, the galactic society gradually began to look at it as a form of entertainment. More and more people started to make fun of Sorokin.

In the words of the galactic residents, Sorokin seemed to have become the biggest conspiracist ever in history, and everything became related to him. Even the pig next door giving birth to seven babies was part of his secret big plan.

A new meme was born on the internet—no matter what matter they were talking about, it would all end with 'this is all part of Sorokin's conspiracy!'

While the public was having fun, the Limitless Financial Group was filled with tragedy and worry.

As the consortium's head had run away with the money, the dynasty's strategies came right after. The negative impact of the news caused the consortium to not be trusted. Tons of creditors came to collect their debts, the stock market price plummeted, all their business partners and galactic banks stopped granting loans, and the capital flow gradually started to show signs of breaking apart. It was doomed.

Sensing the difficult situation the Limitless Financial Group was in, the hunters everywhere sharpened their knives and started moving, biting off the Limitless Financial Group's enormous business empire bit by bit.

Tons of organizations came to enjoy this festival, countless talents of the Limitless Financial Group left one after another, and numerous businesses were taken over; its size shrank rapidly. The product of Sorokin's blood and sweat over many years fell like dominos.

Approved by Han Xiao, the Germinal Financial Group also took part and shared the cake as a shareholder. Old Manison, Kasuyi, and the other shareholders also feasted on the remains of the Limitless Financial Group.

Sorokin was a member of the Beyond Grade A Association, after all, so the association had to host a meeting for this matter and discuss how to deal with it.

…

A meeting was going on in the round table conference room on Planet Finn.

"It's hard to imagine that Sorokin, who always pretended to be weak, was hiding such a big secret… He's a Primordial Ones who lived all the way till now. Who knows how strong he really is? We never saw it coming," Kasuyi said with disbelief.

"He's indeed very well hidden. I always thought he's really weak, even laughed at him. He probably thinks I'm just a joke." Sun Hunter scratched his head.

"Actually, I'm a little doubtful. Would Sorokin really do this? Could someone have framed him? After all, some people have a history of that…" A neutral Beyond Grade A peaked at the dynasty's direct members. It was easy to read between the lines of what he said.

"We have solid evidence," Clotti replied calmly and was not angry about it.

They discussed the matter for quite a while when Han Xiao suddenly coughed, expressing that he had something to say. Everyone immediately became quiet.

Seeing this, Han Xiao slowly said, "Sorokin's conspiracy is already proven to be true. He once guided the Tragedy of the Pinnacles, so attacking Gaud might be his attempt to do the same again. No matter what, despite being an upper echelon of the association, he's not only not on our side but even wants to split the Beyond Grade As. He broke the principles of the association, causing extremely negative influences… I suggest canceling his membership as punishment. Let's vote on it."

Hearing this, the others exchanged looks. After quite some time, someone finally raised their hand.

"Seconded!"

"Agreed!"

Beyond Grade As voted one after another. The people who agreed with it quickly became the majority. Manison was the only one who had yet to make a stand.

"Old man, what do you say?" Han Xiao raised his brow.

Manison glanced at him and said with a poker face, "I concur. From today onward, Sorokin's membership will be cancelled. He's no longer a member of the Beyond Grade A Development Union."

…

On the Crimson Dynasty mother planet…

"I see, the Beyond Grade A Association cancelled Sorokin's membership… They're wise."

Marbruce finished reading the report and nodded slightly. He did not react to it much, as if he had expected this.

Opposite him was Bekorodi. They were the only two people in the room.

Bekorodi said softly, "Do you really believe that Gaud was attacked by Sorokin?"

"No," Marbruce replied without hesitation.

"Then, why did you…"

Marbruce knocked on the table and slowly said, "The evidence came too easily. Think about this. If you were Sorokin, would you have left so much information behind? This evidence is very odd. Although it's not fake, someone secretly guided us to find it. It might be an attempt to use a real lie to hide the real culprit."

"But Sorokin is indeed missing. If it is really as you say, maybe the person who made Sorokin disappear is the same culprit who attacked Gaud?"

"Hmm, it's very possible." Marbruce pondered. "Don't you think all of this is too coincidental? It's like an invisible hand is controlling everything. Do you… really think Black Star did it?

"I can't say easily." Bekorodi hesitated. "Logically, Gaud only tried to copy the Evolution Energy, and there's no need for Black Star to make such a big deal out of it. He has no reason to…"

"Maybe there are some things we still don't know about." Marbruce's eyes flickered. "I have a feeling that there might be a powerful force hidden in the universe we have yet to discover…"

"What do you mean?"

"Hehe, that's confidential."

Marbruce smiled and shook his head. He recalled a certain piece of information he only found after becoming the ruler that had the highest confidentiality level.

As a Primordial One, the Soul Emperor somehow lived till now. Is he really the only one?

Chapter 1247: Consumed

Sorokin going missing and the Limitless Financial Group's collapse caused a certain impact on the economy of the galactic society. However, one company falling meant many others would take over. Many organizations absorbed the nutrition of the Limitless Financial Group and completed the handover, making up for the shortage caused by the Limitless Financial Group's collapse, continuing to provide the services to the galactic society.

In this battle of sharing the cake, relying on Black Star's identity as a shareholder and the army's military power advantage, the Germinal Financial Group inherited many ace businesses and tons of talents of the Limitless Financial Group. Its scale expanded instantly, and its stock price skyrocketed.

After this incident, although the Limitless Financial Group secured the last bit of their business and survived, it was severely damaged. Only a part of Sorokin's elite offspring remained to protect their family business.

However, even though the Limitless Financial Group was already severely damaged, it only fell from the position of top consortium and was still a big consortium in the Star Field, clearly proving how many assets Sorokin had worked hard to accumulate. In terms of making money legally, there was probably really no one among Beyond Grade As who could match him.

If not because it was not convenient to let Sorokin appear in front of the public, Han Xiao almost wanted to make him in charge of the commercial area of the army. Han Xiao had already confirmed that making money was really one of the few hobbies of Sorokin.

In Sorokin's own words, the increase of the money he had was visible and much easier than the increase of strength. He loved this kind of snowballing mechanism; the increase of his assets made him happy.

However, Han Xiao also did not plan to let Sorokin do nothing. He decided to have Sorokin take care of some business affairs behind the curtains.

This guy loved to make money, so letting him enjoy his hobby was also a form of entertainment for him. He could also give him some dividends… He had no place to spend it anyway.

The way Han Xiao looked at it, the Limitless Financial Group's players were the unluckiest. When they returned in the next version, their reaction would probably all be the same…

Where's my faction? It's such a big faction. What happened‽

Just thinking about it, Han Xiao felt pitiful.

Looks like I'll have to take these homeless leeks into my warm arms and show them that love really exists in the world.

After the Crimson Dynasty announced the wanted order of Sorokin, Gaud's case seemed to have finally settled. The dynasty did not do anything after that, and everything went back to normal.

The focus of the galactic society shifted with it and back to the developments of the Flickering World. The fourth exploration phase had already finished, ending with the exit of the Super Star Cluster Alliance. There would still be the fifth phase, the sixth phase, and so on. All would be focused on developing peacefully. The developments afterward did not have much to do with the Beyond Grade A allies.

A few months later, the Germinal Financial Group finally digested the 'inheritance' of the Limitless Financial Group and submitted a detailed report to Han Xiao.

…

In his office, Han Xiao carefully read through the report on the screen. After a while, he finally nodded with satisfaction and looked at the remote projections of Sylvia and Iapetus in front of him.

"You guys have done a good job consuming these businesses of the Limitless Financial Group. The army has taken a huge step in the progress of expanding its subdivisions in the various Star Fields, at least saving twenty years' time."

"It's all thanks to your guidance. You're the lighthouse of the army, showing us the path." Sylvia smiled lustfully.

Han Xiao caressed the back of his palm and said, "I also saw on the report that we recruited some of Sorokin's offspring. Some even actively chose to join us…"

"That's because no one can resist your charm." Sylvia did it again.

Han Xiao looked at her oddly.

What's going on with this woman today? Did her personality change?

Han Xiao ignored her, turned to look at Iapetus, and said, "What do you plan to do with Sorokin's offspring?"

Iapetus rubbed his moustache and slowly said, "Although Sorokin escaped for his crimes, his offspring are innocent. Some of them were raised as elites and had high management positions in the Limitless Financial Group. They're very capable, so taking these people in is great for the Germinal Financial Group. Of course, I'll test them before giving them positions, limit the power they have, and split them up into different management positions."

"Hmm, do as you said."

Although Han Xiao felt like it might be immoral for them to join the person who caused Sorokin to go missing, he felt like given Sorokin's personality, giving birth to offspring was probably just to raise trustworthy assistants; he would not be too emotionally attached to him.

Beyond Grade As breeding offspring as assistants was very common. Most people would carry out group activities at most to increase efficiency. Beast Ancestor was the only one in this era who was so extreme about it.

"Offspring are indeed good. They can be raised systematically from a young age. Maybe I should start to breed some babies," Han Xiao mumbled.

Sylvia's eyes lit up instantly. "I'll do it! Maternity leave is still leave. I don't mind it!"

Han Xiao almost fell down from his chair from shock.

What, are you already this desperate for the sake of taking leave now?

Not only do you want to take leave, but you even want to sleep with your boss! How do you think something that incredible will happen?

Iapetus coughed on the side and whispered, "If you want to take maternity leave, I can help too…"

Sylvia glared at him. "Keep dreaming!"

Iapetus's expression froze. Facing Han Xiao's meaningful stare, he wisely went offline.

Only two of them were left in the room. Sylvia suddenly smiled lustfully, shook her waist left and right, and walked to Han Xiao. She pressed her arms on the table, leaned forward, pressed her lips near Han Xiao's ears, and whispered, "I wasn't kidding. What do you think of me?"

"Is today your estrus cycle? Looks like I have to remember this date and calculate your cycle so I can dodge you in the future."

Sylvia's face twitched, and her smile became stiff. She did her best to not lash out and said with a suggestive tone, "Do you really not know just how charming you are? My admiration for you has flooded since long ago. Are you really going to treat me like this?"

"Stop it. It's not useful to me. Say what you want to say."

Han Xiao was unaffected. He pressed on Sylvia's forehead and pushed her head away.

Excuse me, I'm a righteous man. I have never practiced the "if there's something to do, let the secretary do it; if there's nothing to do, do the secretary" system.

Usually, you were always dismissive of me, but today you suddenly turned into an emotionless praising machine. There's definitely something you want from me today.

Sylvia's expression collapsed. She kicked Han Xiao's leg heavily, then rubbed her feet while grinding her teeth with annoyance. "I've been the Chief Administrative Official for decades. You've always used me like a tool! I've had enough. I want to change my position!"

Han Xiao thought it made sense. Although Sylvia was very loyal, she would not be happy about being a tool for so long, especially when the lifespan of Calamity Grades was far shorter than Beyond Grade As. She had basically given her youth to the army.

He always said that the hairline was the durability of the officers, but Han Xiao considered himself to be quite flexible. As long as the request was logical, he would not really treat his officers like tools.

"What do you want to do then?"

"I want you to teach me to become a Beyond Grade A!"

"Huh?" Han Xiao almost thought he had heard wrong.

"I've given my heart and soul to the army, putting in my entire youth, but you're not even willing to teach me!" Sylvia was angry.

"No, no, that's not true. It's just that becoming a Beyond Grade A depends on talent. Even if I teach you, you don't have too high a chance…" Han Xiao sighed.

"I don't care. I just want you to teach me!"

Sylvia pulled Han Xiao's arm and shook it like she was begging him. In front of others, she was a decisive, capable, and smart Chief Administrative Official. But in front of Han Xiao, she was still occasionally that little girl in the past.

"Alright, alright, after you've finished the handover for your job, come back as my student." Han Xiao agreed.

Hearing this, Sylvia finally smiled brightly. She kissed Han Xiao's cheek and ran away like a thief.

At the door, Sylvia stopped, turned, and smiled like a fairy with a slightly blushed face. She said with a playful tone, "I really wasn't kidding about what I said earlier."

Then, before Han Xiao could respond, she ran away.

"Tsk, as if I'd believe you, you little minx." Han Xiao shook his head and wiped away the lipstick on his face.

In his previous life, after Sylvia's father was sent into a prison, Sylvia could only wander in the universe without a goal. Now, the army had given her a home and a goal she could work for.

Without him knowing, many people's fates had changed because of him.

"Sylvia's potential shouldn't be enough to reach Beyond Grade A, but nothing is absolute. Even garbage like Kohler and Beyoni can become Beyond Grade As, after all. With my teachings, Sylvia might not be completely hopeless… I shall teach her some knowledge from Jayz's treasure trove."

Han Xiao nodded in his head.

Beep beep beep!

At this time, his communicator suddenly rang. He took it out and to his surprise. It was a call from Ames.

Sylvia just left seconds ago and Ames already called?

So coincidental, is this the sixth sense of woman?

Han Xiao shivered slightly.

He focused his mind and picked up.

Ames appeared on the screen holding her cheek with her hand and smiling elegantly.

"We've not met for quite some time. Do you want to come and have a chat? Aesop brewed a batch of new wine."

"That's it? No, no!"

"Also… I might slightly, a little tiny bit, miss you." Ames blinked.

"Let's go."

Without hesitation, Han Xiao put on the King suit immediately.

For the past few years, other than the plenary, he did not meet with Ames much. He had been busy with plotting and studying machinery. He felt a bit sorry for it. Furthermore, he had just dealt with a huge matter, so he also needed some soothing and stress relief.

Chapter 1248: Galaxy Calendar Year 780

In Ames' palace at the center of Floating Dragon Island, Han Xiao arrived through teleportation and saw a round table in front of him right away. Neatly arranged snacks and fruits were placed on top. Ames sat on a chair beside it.

Ames was smiling at the communicator when he arrived, only hanging up when she saw him. She kept the communicator and shifted her eyes onto him, maintaining a faint smile.

"I knew you'd come. Sit, the wine is ready."

Han Xiao walked up and sat beside Ames. He sighed and said, "I've been busy lately and didn't come for quite some time. I've neglected you."

"When are you ever not busy?" Ames replied.

Han Xiao shook his head, picked up a glass, and drank the wine. He tutted and said, "Why does it taste different from the last time?"

"Aesop improved the recipe the last time he returned."

Ames controlled her force field and filled Han Xiao's glass up.

Han Xiao smiled and said, "Speaking of which, after Aesop was kidnapped, I was surprised you didn't reject Aesop's request to travel. I thought you'd ground him for a very long time."

"I wouldn't have agreed if not for the Soul Swapper." Ames snorted softly.

After Feidin acquired the Soul Swapper, Han Xiao had come up with a plan for Aesop. After long consideration, Aesop had taken his suggestion and asked Feidin to temporarily swap his soul into someone else so that he could go out. It was secretive and safe. In the end, Ames agreed with his request.

"The Soul Swapper is indeed nice. Sadly, Feidin is only at the Calamity Grade for now. The functions he can use are limited." Han Xiao shook his head. He suddenly thought of something and said, "I have a gift for you."

"A gift?" Ames raised her brows.

Han Xiao took out a pure white small sphere from his pocket. He passed to Ames, smiled, and said, "This is a Universal Treasure I happened to obtain. It can help Espers develop their ability. It's for you."

Ames accepted the small sphere, toyed with it using her force field, and said curiously, "What's this thing's name? How do I use it?"

"Just call it Esper Ability Enhancement Orb. It's easy to use. Just apply energy to it every day. Basically, play with it."

Han Xiao briefly explained its effects.

This was one of the Universal Treasures that Sorokin secretly collected and was seized by him. According to the item details on the interface, this thing could randomly enhance the various ability parameters of Espers. The effects would only be triggered if it was worn for a long time. The chance was unknown, and the magnitude of the enhancement each time was not high.

At its maximum, it could at most increase the Esper Ability's potential by one grade. After that, it would lose effects on the same user.

However, the enhancement effects would not certainly occur. It might be completely useless too. According to the introduction, the chance of triggering the enhancement relied on Luck to a certain extent… Basically, it despised unlucky people.

Han Xiao recalled that Ames' Luck was quite high, so she should be able to trigger this treasure. After she was done using it, given her relationship with Hila and Aurora, why would she not lend it to them? It was perfect.

"I'll take it then, thanks." Ames toyed with it for a while and put it away.

In the past years, Han Xiao had given her gifts frequently. A few years ago, he had even secretly given her the entire set of Esper class knowledge. She almost thought Han Xiao hacked into the dynasty's database.

The two of them chatted while eating snacks.

Most of the time, Han Xiao was speaking, and Ames was listening with a smile, staring at Han Xiao and holding her chin with her hands.

After chatting for some time, Ames suddenly interrupted Han Xiao and said, "I've realized you've had a lot on your mind in the past few years."

Han Xiao was stunned for a moment. "How did you notice?"

"I know you too well." Ames smiled. "Do you want to talk to me about it?"

Han Xiao sighed.

Indeed, after he found out about the Sanctums, he had been feeling more stressed mentally. He had been spending all his time studying machines and becoming stronger in the past few years, keeping himself busy and not slacking off.

Han Xiao thought about it and said with a deep voice, "In the past few years, I've been thinking about one question. What if our world is just an illusion that exists only in the past and the things we see are only mirages in a cell?"

"Why did you suddenly have this thought?" Ames was curious.

"… I just happened to discover some information and made some connections."

Han Xiao's answer was ambiguous. Of course, he was not going to easily share the information about the Celestial Star Alliance, the iterations of the universe, and the Sanctums.

Actually, he had been suspicious of this since long ago. He had only buried it because he knew it was very difficult to find the answer for it. He only had more speculations after finding out about the Sanctums.

Although Ames did not understand what Han Xiao was talking about, he could sense the pressure from Han Xiao's tone. It sounded somewhat distant, and she felt something she rarely ever felt from Han Xiao. He sounded a tiny bit lost.

Most of the time, Han Xiao was very confident. She rarely ever saw Han Xiao like this. Although she did not know what caused Han Xiao to be so stressed, to her, it did not matter. What mattered was that she knew this man needed her comforting.

Having thought of that, Ames smiled.

"It doesn't matter. I know that our breath is real, the warmth I feel is real, and your touch is real…"

While saying, Ames held Han Xiao's hand in her hands and whispered, "And I'm real too."

The two of them looked into each other's eyes for almost twenty seconds.

"… Ahem, we're not in the secondary dimensions."

Han Xiao suddenly coughed and pulled his hand away.

"Hehe." Ames laughed softly with unknown meaning.

The two of them both skipped this topic without saying anything and chatted for a few more hours before Han Xiao bade farewell and teleported away.

Looking at the empty seat, Ames suddenly sighed.

After spending so much time with Black Star, she had long found out that although Black Star looked like he had many friends, for some reason, he always kept his heart locked up and would not let anyone walk into it.

…

In the place where Gaud was 'raised', a spaceship stopped at the port, and the hatch opened. Two rows of people appeared, one boarding it and another alighting. Most of the people in the former were dejected, while the people in the latter looked full of confidence.

This was a transport ship that carried a new batch of students in. It was also in charge of taking away the students who were disqualified from the training base.

Karlot was in the row of people boarding the ship. He could not help but glance back at the training base.

For all the time, Karlot had been on the edge of the disqualified list every term. If not because of what Gaud said back then, he would have been kicked out by the manager of the base long ago. Now, however, Gaud was nowhere to be found, so what he said, of course, became meaningless. The manager of the base no longer gave Karlot special treatment and placed him on the disqualified list in this term, no longer giving him advanced training.

"I've studied for almost a decade here. It's a shame I couldn't remain here…"

Karlot sighed softly.

He was not really down, just felt it was a pity.

He had worked hard for so long and only just discovered the right training method of the Super system, but before he could change the way he trained, he was kicked out…

"Never mind. At least the studies I did in these ten years had not gone to waste. As long as I've learned something, it's good enough."

Karlot shook his head, turned back to look at his front, and walked up the spaceship in big steps. The vibe he gave off was completely different from the dejected crowd around him.

…

After the dust settled on Gaud and Sorokin's cases, the galactic society finally entered a period of stable development.

The Super Star Cluster civilizations defeated in the Flickering War quietly licked their wounds, while the other organizations who took part in the war continued to rest and digest the profits of the exploration. A time of stability was needed after the leader of the Crimson Dynasty and the Federation of Light changed. On the other hand, the Beyond Grade A Association was continuing to build the profit network.

While all sides peacefully developed in this calm atmosphere, the fifth, sixth, and the rest of the exploration phases of the Flickering World were smoothly completed. The Flickering World was finally added to the map of the explored universe, making the galactic society even more prosperous than before, bringing in countless business opportunities.

Even a pig could fly with a strong enough wind. The development of the Flickering World bred many new organizations. New consortiums appeared in the Flickering World every once a while.

After the Black Star Army consumed part of the Limitless Financial Group's businesses, it grew even quicker and expanded rapidly in the various Star Fields. Its force became larger and larger, and Han Xiao's position increased along with it.

The two hidden threats, Gaud and Sorokin, had been dealt with, and Manison was accumulating strength with a low profile, so no one in the universe dared to mess with Han Xiao in this period. He finally entered the longest peaceful development period he had ever experienced.

Other than the daily activities, Han Xiao spent the rest of his time studying Jayz's technology while occasionally trying to break down the life energy. Every day was spent meaningfully.

As someone who had always been at the center of the attention and always slapped himself in the face in the end every time he said he wanted to keep a low profile for some time, Han Xiao finally faded out of the sights of the outside world.

Although the universe still remembered him, the stage was cleared for newbies to shine.

This situation lasted all the way to Galaxy Calendar Year 780. On this day, the Beyond Grade A Association welcomed its fiftieth anniversary.

This meant that the president position that lasted for fifty years every term was going to change. It was finally time for the election.

Chapter 1249: Forty Years

After growing steadily for forty years, the Black Star Army's territory was already very prosperous, and the number of undeveloped areas was rapidly decreasing. The Sigma Star System in the Garu Star Cluster was the Black Star Army's Flickering World logistics headquarters. It was not open to outsiders.

A cluster of gentle pale-golden energy floated in an area surrounded by many satellite bases like a glowing golden asteroid. It was expanding and shrinking as if it was breathing, sending out rings of light gold energy rhythmically like ripples.

Two figures, one black and one red, hovered near this 'asteroid'. Around them were countless mechanical soldiers that formed a line of defense guarding the area.

"This day has finally come. Aurora has stepped into our territory…" the red figure said softly with a tint of satisfaction and pride. A gentle smile appeared on her usually-cold face.

The two of them were Han Xiao and Hila. The glowing golden 'asteroid' nearby was indeed Aurora, who was going through the last step of transforming into a Beyond Grade A.

The last forty years had left no traces on Hila. Other than her vibe being colder and more distinguished, her appearance did not change at all. To normal Beyond Grade As, this amount of time was equivalent to about six to seven years, and to a special Beyond Grade A like Hila who controlled death, it was but the blink of an eye.

Han Xiao smiled. "If Aurora was accumulating energy on her own, it'd probably take more than a hundred years for her to become a Beyond Grade A. This is even quicker than I expected."

His appearance did not change much too, but his vibe became more unfathomable.

The army had steadily expanded over the last forty years, and the bonuses of [Proof of Leadership] increased along with it. Through studying Jayz's treasure trove, Han Xiao already increased his God's Trait Transformation to a very high level. He was remarkably stronger than forty years prior.

The leek harvesting technique using the Holy Light Particle reduced Aurora's process of accumulating energy. With her special trait of having no energy limit on top, becoming a Beyond Grade A was just a matter of time for Aurora. The time it took was close to what Han Xiao speculated.

After quite some time, the golden 'asteroid' in front of the two of them finally started to shrink. From an enormous cluster of light, it turned into a silhouette, glowing with light gold light all over, giving off a divine vibe like the combination of mothership and holiness.

Aurora's appearance changed drastically. She became taller, and her face became gorgeously beautiful; she had the face of an angel and the body of a devil. Her entire style turned from adorable to alluring. It was almost like a completely different person.

Seeing this, Han Xiao and Hila flew over to Aurora and sized her up, looking astonished.

"Why do you look different?" Hila compared her height with Aurora and realized Aurora was surprisingly even about fifteen centimeters taller than her.

Han Xiao stared and studied Aurora's body for a while and made a decisive conclusion. "This must be the second puberty!"

"This is my new ability. I can control the shape of my body now." Aurora giggled. Her body glowed, and she instantly returned to her normal tiny body shape. "How was that? Was I prettier than you, sis? I can change back anytime."

Hila tutted, changed the topic, and asked, "What other abilities do you have?"

Aurora performed them right away. All her abilities were enhanced. She did not have to develop her abilities on her own and directly inherited the progress from her predecessor. She instantly acquired many abilities and talents, fully displaying the advantages of being a cheater.

After entering the Beyond Grade A realm, the life energy Aurora could produce every day multiplied by countless times. She basically did not have to worry about not having enough of it at all. Furthermore, she even got an aura. The allies on her side would have a drastically higher regeneration speed if they were within a certain range of her. The range of this aura would even grow as she became stronger.

"Also, I should be able to perfectly produce revival energy now."

While speaking, Aurora flicked her finger and sent out a cluster of life energy. Hila saw it and released a cluster of death energy too. The two fused together and turned into a cluster of golden-orange revival energy. The strengths of the two types of energy achieved a stable balance.

"Now that you're a Beyond Grade A, you only have to briefly familiarize with your abilities, and we will be able to use the reviving function of the Underworld," Hila said.

The seven… oh no, eight Hero Spirit Kings had been doing nothing in the Underworld. Now that Aurora had become a Beyond Grade A, the last piece of the puzzle was found. These Hero Spirits would be able to have combat capabilities.

With the help of the eight Hero Spirit Kings of the Underworld, the two sisters leaped right to the front of the list of the strongest people in the universe. This was the biggest inheritance left by their predecessors. With enough strength to protect herself, the summoning style would become Aurora's best combat mode.

Han Xiao smiled and said, "You're a Beyond Grade A now. Do you want to become a deputy army commander like your sister, or do you have other plans?"

Aurora's eyes spun, and she said with excitement, "I can protect myself now. Does that mean I can act freely?"

"… Technically, yes." Han Xiao could only nod.

"Then I want to travel alone. Don't stop me." Aurora's tone was filled with anticipation. She had been extremely bored for years. She basically could not go anywhere at all. All she wanted to do now was travel the universe.

Han Xiao and Hila exchanged a look and saw the resignation in each other's eyes.

Now that Aurora had become a Beyond Grade A, they could no longer arrange everything for her like before. They had to respect her personal will.

However, at least there was no need to worry about her safety. Aurora could solve most accidents with her current capability.

"I'll approve it, but you have to take a Throne with you," Hila said with a serious tone.

Aurora was exhilarated. She turned to look at Han Xiao and said, "By the way, I can join the Beyond Grade A Association now, right?"

She had been longing for the Beyond Grade A Association for a very long time. She had heard that all of its members were talented and sweet. She had been wanting to see for herself.

"Okay, I'll arrange to put you in… Hmm, the presidential election is in two months. Letting you in will increase my chances too."

Han Xiao did not reject her.

Now that Aurora had grown, she had more than enough power to protect herself. There was no need to continue hiding her. Plus, she did not want to hide either. She was going to join the association sooner or later.

Although this would make the various organizations once again be reminded of the two Primordial sisters, Han Xiao could deal with it now.

Aurora's ability might even assist in uniting the Beyond Grade As… Who did not want to last longer?

Aurora blinked and said, "Are you sure you'll become the president this time?"

Han Xiao smiled. "At least ninety percent sure."

Over the last fifty years, the Beyond Grade A Association had already completed some of its initial goals. It successfully became a huge profit network. Although it met obstructions from the three Universal Civilizations along the way, there were no too intense conflicts.

Therefore, in the past few years, he did not hold back on causing problems for Manison. He had already obtained the highest reputation in the association; Manison could only be a mascot most of the time.

Other than the support of the internal members, the exterior organizations also supported him. If things remained this way, he would certainly take over the position of the president during the plenary in two months and bring the Beyond Grade A Association into an age led by Black Star.

However, he did not know what Manison had been doing over the last few decades since he had been keeping a low profile all this time. Han Xiao did not know if he would be watching him become the president or do something… However, no matter what, Han Xiao had already made the necessary preparations.

After chatting for a while, Hila brought Aurora to the Underworld to familiarize herself with her abilities, leaving Han Xiao alone.

Han Xiao watched the two of them leave. "The army has now raised a second Beyond Grade A. It's the only example. It'll be even better if Lothaire makes a breakthrough too."

Lothaire had been training hard and improving rapidly in the past forty years. He was already on the path of transformation. However, unlike Aurora, he had to break through some obstacles and was still some distance away from Beyond Grade A. As for the other officers of the army, no one showed any signs of becoming a Beyond Grade A any time soon.

Han Xiao caressed his chin and thought about the presidential election in two months' time.

Becoming the president was not even the most important thing; the chain reactions it would cause were. For example, the elderlies of the Holy Accord organization had remained quiet for decades, and they agreed with Han Xiao to only appear after he became the Beyond Grade A Association president.

Han Xiao could imagine the reactions of the entire galactic society—even though many details were changed, it would most certainly go back to the path of the Calamity of the Supers incident.

"Quite a number of rookies have been born in the last forty years and have been active in the universe, while I've been keeping a low profile for so long. Looks like I'll be returning to the center of the public attention once again."

…

The Beyond Grade A Association was already a giant in the galactic society. The election of the president received the attention of countless organizations.

On the Federation of Light's mother planet, the current federation president, Louis Rocky, tapped the table and said to the chief elder in front of him with a deep voice, "The Beyond Grade A Association is about to have an election. Manison will definitely be beaten by Black Star. What ideas do you guys have?"

The chief elder shook his head and said, "This is unavoidable. Although Black Star is the dynasty's ally, their honeymoon period has ended. Letting him become the president won't be a bad thing for us."

Louis frowned. "I'm not talking about Black Star alone… Not even a single rookie born in the past forty years joined the three Universal Civilizations. All of them went to the Beyond Grade A Association. The existence of the association is already influencing our interests."

As the Beyond Grade A Association grew, the three Universal Civilizations had been having a harder time controlling it. For example, the spread of knowledge privately happening between Beyond Grade As became more and more frequent, causing the three Universal Civilizations' system of attracting new Beyond Grade As by monopolizing the Ultimate Knowledges of all the classes to be severely impacted. They could not recruit any new allies.

Of course, the three Universal Civilizations never agreed to let the association pass around knowledge, so this kind of act could be considered a violation of the laws the three Universal Civilizations set. However, the association did not openly share the knowledge, so it would be extremely difficult for the three Universal Civilizations to find who was responsible for what. Hence, they could not prevent the association's members from spreading the knowledge in private. With the association backing them, the Beyond Grade As cared less and less about the three Universal Civilizations causing trouble for them.

"This is indeed a problem, but to solve it, we'll have to face the Beyond Grade A Association directly, which will have enormous consequences. I suggest you do not do anything before coming up with a fully developed plan," another elder said.

Louis tapped the table and narrowed his eyes.

The former president Bader did not want to flip the table on the Beyond Grade As during his term, so this mission fell to him. Louis had no choice but to take responsibility.

Through the past decades, he had become more and more certain that the Beyond Grade A Association was the top problem he had to solve during his term.

From the way Louis looked at it, the Crimson Dynasty and the Arcane Church probably had the same thought.

…

In a certain base of the Holy Accord…

"The Beyond Grade A Association's presidential election is finally here…"

"After Black Star gets elected, we'll be able to go out as promised."

The many Primordial Ones looked at the news on the virtual screen. Some were excited; some were looking forward. They chatted softly.

Oathkeeper stood beside the door with his arms crossed, mumbling.

"This day still came… Black Star, I hope your predictions are right."

Chapter 1250: Headstrong

As only a limited number of people knew about it and the army did not promote it, the news of Aurora becoming a Beyond Grade A did not spread to the outside world. Less than half a month later, Han Xiao hosted a welcome plenary just for her.

The welcome meeting was being hosted at the association headquarters on Planet Finn.

The remote projections of the Beyond Great As sat in the venue. Compared to forty years ago, there were more seats now. Beside Hila, an empty seat was added for Aurora.

At this time, the Beyond Grade As present were all chatting and curiously guessing the identity of this new Beyond Grade A.

As the information had not been leaked, the people present only knew that another new Beyond Grade A had been born in the universe. They did not know who this rookie was.

"I wonder if the rookie is a neutral or a member of a big organization."

"There's no information anywhere at all, and Black Star's already recruited this guy. I have a feeling this rookie is closely related to Black Star."

"I'm only curious about what Super class this rookie is."

"I hope it's not a Pugilist. There's already enough people with clogged brains…"

The people chatted within their factions.

After forty years, many more factions were formed in the Beyond Grade A Association.

Some were classified by the huge organization they were in—for example, the three Universal Civilizations direct members, their allies, and the neutral ones. Some were classified by their partnerships, like those Beyond Grade As whose organization worked very well with each other. Others were classified by different classes. These factions were formed because of the private spread of the Ultimate Knowledges, which caused the Beyond Grade As in various classes to gather around the stronger ones with the same class as them.

Because of that, many members hoped the rookie had the same class as them so that they could expand their faction.

Han Xiao let them chat freely for a while. He then clapped and smiled.

"Alright, let's keep it down and welcome the rookie."

Hearing that the vice president had spoken, the members all shut their mouths, ignoring Manison, who was resting with his eyes closed.

Not long after, the side gate of the venue opened. The mature version of Aurora walked in and sized up everyone curiously.

The Beyond Grade As present also looked at her with curiosity and mumbled softly.

"So, she's the new Beyond Grade A. Doesn't look like a Pugilist, great."

"Hmm, I don't know her. I know all the renowned Beyond Grade A seeds in the universe. She's definitely not one of them."

"That's weird. She looks familiar to me… Don't you guys think she looks a little similar to Hila?"

At this time, Han Xiao spoke. "This rookie's name is Aurora. She only stepped into the Beyond Grade A territory not long ago. She's Hila's sister and also is a member of the Black Star Army. Her ability is the complete opposite of Hila's. She controls life energy. This can help others to quickly regenerate their wounds and recover their life force… Aurora, on behalf of the Beyond Grade A Association, I welcome you."

As soon as he said that, shock appeared on almost everyone's face.

This rookie is a Black Star Army officer again‽

She's even the relative of another Beyond Grade A. What are the chances of that‽

"One controls death; one controls life. And they're sisters! Why does this sound familiar?" someone murmured.

Hearing this, many people recalled that there was a similar pair of sisters among the Primordial Ones.

Same Esper Abilities, same two sisters… this is too coincidental!

If someone were to say the two sisters were completely unrelated to the Primordial sisters from history, the vast majority of people there would never believe it.

Recalling the stories of the Primordial sisters, the way they looked at Hila and Aurora changed subtly. On top of disbelief, a tint of desire appeared.

Hila's ability could reduce people's life span. If her sister's ability was the opposite, did that mean she could increase people's life span? Or could she even imitate the Primordial Ones and create the legendary 'Underworld'?

Most people present had ideas of befriending Aurora and immediately welcomed her. They were very enthusiastic.

They avoided Hila as much as possible but acted the complete opposite with Aurora.

Seeing this, Hila coldly warned, "Don't have any ideas about my younger sister. I won't hold back."

"We're greeting Aurora. What does it have to do with you?"

Many snorted.

Although they feared Hila's ability, they could not act that way.

However, words were one thing. Indeed, not many dared have any vicious thoughts. After operating for fifty years, the association had already established a reputation. Not many were willing to violate the rules and do anything to its members. Furthermore, most people feared the giant organization, the Black Star Army. Even if they were not afraid of Hila, they had to consider Black Star too.

As they thought of Black Star, they could not help but feel bitter and jealous.

He had acquired another Beyond Grade A officer… Where in the world did Black Star find so many top talents from?

"Er, I'm Aurora. I'm glad to join the association…"

Aurora came to her seat and briefly introduced herself. She then read the script she had memorized and said the standard things like 'it's an honor to be a part of the association'.

The others responded kindly.

Hila watched on the side and secretly curled her lips.

Tsk, you dogs. I've never seen you this enthusiastic toward me before…

Aurora was the focus of today's welcome meeting. She had finally entered the Beyond Grade A circle and was filled with curiosity. In the face of the others trying to befriend her, she kept on talking excitedly, creating a clear contrast with Hila's cold image.

From her own words, the others confirmed that Aurora could extend their life span. They were overjoyed.

However, as soon as they mentioned anything about requesting her to do it, Aurora kicked the ball to Han Xiao and stated that she would only listen to Black Star. This was discussed beforehand to increase Han Xiao's reputation and position further, increasing his chances of being reelected as much as possible.

Hearing this, the people looked at Han Xiao. When they saw that he was smiling, they immediately knew that they had to pay a price for Han Xiao to approve their requests. After knowing him for so many years, they knew that Black Star was not easy to deal with or deceive. The presidential election was very soon; it was easy to figure out what Black Star was trying to convey.

After chatting for some time, someone could not hold back his curiosity and asked, "Why do you work for the Black Star Army?"

"Well, Black Star saved me…" Aurora briefly shared her experience in the Germinal Organization, saying that Black Star had saved her life.

Hearing this, even those who knew about Black Star's early history were astonished.

A puny surface civilizations organization that made three Beyond Grade As, just how blessed is this Germinal Organization‽

After some time, seeing that they chatted about enough, Han Xiao spoke and changed the topic.

"Alright, you've all met. Let me use this opportunity to say something. The next plenary will be the presidential election. Manison will step down then, and all members can run. The election will be in the form of voting, and everyone has one vote. Don't forget."

The people nodded.

At the same time, Manison's eyes opened slightly. He glanced at Han Xiao and closed them again.

…

On a certain planet in the Flickering World…

"The next presidential election, huh? If I can take that seat…"

Inside a palace, Royce's eyes gleamed.

He was a relatively new Beyond Grade A. With the assistance of this platform, he quickly formed his own organization. Therefore, he knew what power the association had very well and had been eyeing it all along. Occasionally, he would fantasize about himself being on top of it.

The next president would be elected in two months' time, and Royce felt his chance was here.

As a rookie, he knew that he could not compete with seniors like Black Star. However, the ambition in his chest made him want to give it a try no matter what.

What if he made it?

He was a doer. As soon as he had that thought, he immediately started to act on it.

"I'm definitely no match for Black Star in terms of strength, but the election is vote based. Although my chance is thin, it's not completely hopeless…"

Royce's eyes spun rapidly.

The rookies who had just stepped into the Beyond Grade A circle for a short amount of time had no way of finding out about Han Xiao's personal relationship with the other members, so he did not have a strong sense of Black Star's connections.

Therefore, in Royce's eyes, he did not have completely no chance.

One of the reasons he dared do this was that as a member of the association, his life would not be in danger.

In terms of combat, although Royce admitted he was no match for Han Xiao, he felt the difference would not be too big.

When Royce came to fame, Han Xiao had kept a low profile for quite some time. Everything he knew about Black Star's strength came from hearing it from others; he had never experienced it personally, nor could he really see the details by looking at the videos on the internet.

Overconfidence was a common problem for most new Beyond Grade As. They were ambitious and headstrong, always dreaming of taking over those at the peak.

Usually, only a beating from society could cure this illness, but ever since Royce became a Beyond Grade A, he had yet to receive any 'treatment'.

"Although Black Star wants to become the president, who said I can't take it from him?"

Royce started planning in his head and was looking forward to it.

…

Two months passed very quickly, and the election of the Beyond Grade A Association came as expected. The various organizations in the universe all focused their attention and waited for the results.

Inside the closed venue, all members came online earlier than usual. The atmosphere was solemn. The people's eyes kept moving back and forth between Manison and Han Xiao.

"Ahem, since everyone is here, let's start," Han Xiao said. He then looked at Manison with a smile. "Let's have the president host the meeting."

Manison glanced at him, slowly stood up, and looked around the entire venue.

After a short silence, Manison then spoke. "The association rules state that the president will be elected every fifty years. Now that fifty years have passed, I'll be stepping down from the president position and will not be running today."

As soon as he said that, the people were stunned.

Although most people knew that Manison would not be re-elected, no one felt he would easily give up. To their surprise, Manison gave up running for president completely.

Han Xiao was a little surprised too. He was already prepared to debate with Manison, but Manison directly gave up.

Odd, this doesn't suit old Manison's personality!

"Are you really not running? Is it because you're worried about being embarrassed when you lose to me?" Han Xiao asked to confirm.

"Humph." Manison did not reply.

Seeing this, Han Xiao shook his head.

No matter what Manison was thinking, as long as he did not run, his biggest competitor would be gone. Becoming the president was almost certain for Han Xiao.

"If that's the case, I'll be the first to run." Han Xiao looked around at the expression on everyone's faces and asked, "Who else?"

Many people looked away and did not meet his eyes.

Judging from the current situation, it was basically already decided that Black Star would become the president. Plus, he was indeed the most suitable for it.

None of the peak Beyond Grade As who were the most qualified to run even spoke, so most people read the room and shut their mouths. They were thinking they might as well let Black Star be the only one running so that the voting round could be skipped, and he would become the president on the spot.

However, when everyone thought that was how it was going to be, a voice filled with confidence sounded.

"I'll run!"

Who? Who's so headstrong‽

The people were shocked. As they turned around, their expressions became odd.

Royce raised his hand and remained in the posture. He had an excited smile on his face as if he was enjoying the moment of being the center of attention.

"Are you sure?" Han Xiao was a little surprised.

"Anyone can run anyway, so why not try it? What if I win‽" Royce was not afraid at all and looked directly at Han Xiao's eyes, giving the vibe of confronting him directly.

This looked quite hot-blooded on the surface, but in the eyes of the people present, it was nothing but ridiculous.

This rookie is so daring. Does he really want to wrestle with Black Star?

At the same time, Aurora quietly whispered into Hila's ear and asked, "This guy should be a Pugilist, right?"

Hila glanced at her.

"You guessed that right."

Chapter 1251: Age of Black Star

A rookie wants to compete for the position of president against me? Who gave you the courage?

Han Xiao looked at Royce's confidence. Thoughts quickly spun in his mind, and many speculations flashed past.

However, when he recalled Royce's class, the surprise in his mind disappeared completely.

Oh, he's a Pugilist, never mind.

Han Xiao shook his head and stopped speculating Royce's motive.

The way the Pugilists' brain worked was, well, refreshing. Most of the time, one thought they were at the second or the first level, when actually they were at the negative one level. There was no need to think too much.

Han Xiao did consider the possibility of some peak Beyond Grade A trying to compete, but he never thought a rookie would step up out of nowhere. This meant that they had to enter the voting round, but it was not a big deal.

Although he had no idea where Royce's confidence came from… he was a Pugilist, so it was understandable.

"Anyone else want to run?" Han Xiao moved his eyes away and scanned through the conference room.

The people exchanged looks, and no one responded.

Seeing this, Han Xiao nodded. "If that's the case, only Royce and I will be running. You guys can vote now."

Everyone there was a Beyond Grade A. No one's opinion could be ignored, so everyone could vote.

Those who always stood on the side of the Black Star faction voted immediately and supported Han Xiao as the president. The direct members of the three Universal Civilizations also voted for him. Some of the peak Beyond Grade As who were upper echelons of the association also expressed their support for Han Xiao.

Other than Heber, Psyker, Manison, and a very few who abstained. Almost all the members voted for Han Xiao.

As for Royce, he stood alone and did not receive a single vote. It was almost lonesome.

Han Xiao could not help but glance at him with an odd look.

Wait, what, that's it?

You didn't even get anyone on your side, yet you still came to compete…

What are you so confident about?

Even Han Xiao felt awkward for Royce just by looking at his bewildered expression.

Come on kid, did you really think anyone would vote for a rookie? Are you the kind of person who likes to be humiliated?

The voting was completely one-sided. Han Xiao regulated his emotions, cleared his throat, and said, "The situation is clear then. Royce, do you accept this result?"

The people simultaneously turned to look at Royce with all kinds of emotions such as mockery, pity, disdain, and other complicated emotions in their eyes.

Royce opened his mouth, sat down, and said sadly, "I accept."

Although he only gambled because he knew there was no risk involved and he would not lose anything even if he did not get elected, seeing how big the difference was, he was still embarrassed.

Royce actually had quite the plan. He knew he most likely would not be elected as the president, but he thought that if he could receive some votes during the election, it would at least show that he had some reputation, so he would not have to be treated like a rookie in the future and be involved in more affairs of the association.

In his eyes, this was the first step for a rookie to obtain a higher position.

In order to achieve this goal, he indeed did contact other association members privately and expressed his thoughts of running for president in the calls, and some people promised to support him even. This was why he had the confidence to run.

However, when the time came, those b*stards all broke their promises!

Actually, what he did not know was, most people thought he was just kidding and promised him as a joke, which mistakenly gave Royce confidence.

As these people were all stronger than him, Royce did not dare vent his anger and could only sulk in the corner while screaming in his mind that verbal promises were not reliable.

Han Xiao was not interested in what Royce was thinking.

He knew Pugilists way too well; it was not that their brains were really made of muscles but that the path of the Pugilist required a 'no backing down' attitude. For those Pugilists who could become Beyond Grade As, this personality would definitely be more apparent. In other words, Pugilists who were not headstrong would have a harder time becoming a Beyond Grade A.

And this was exactly the reason Han Xiao had high hopes for Lothaire. After all, this man was the prime example of someone who was headstrong…

Random thoughts flashed past. Han Xiao focused, looked around, and smiled.

"Thanks for your support, everyone. I shall gladly take on the position of the president."

Aurora clapped first with her face filled with excitement.

Seeing someone lead the applause, the others hesitated for a moment and also clapped symbolically. Most people were rather reserved and not used to doing something like this.

A round of not too loud or too soft applause sounded in the room. Han Xiao smiled in return.

Although he already expected this to happen beforehand, when it actually happened, he still felt content.

He was the leader of the Beyond Grade A Association and could formally lead the Beyond Grade As. His influence evolved to a higher level.

The effects of [Proof of Leadership] also updated right away. He only received part of the bonuses when he was the vice president, but when he became the president, the bonuses were finally complete. Although it was not so tremendous it would increase his strength drastically, it was still a cherry on top.

As the president was elected, the position of the vice president became vacant. An election was then also carried out. This time, the system changed. The number of vice presidents changed from one to two, taken by Kasuyi and Sierron.

Other than that, the association also decided on a few new directors, including Hila.

The voting process was very simple. The procedures were smoothly carried out, and the handover was completed.

Han Xiao finally sat in the main seat. On his left and right were Kasuyi and Sierron.

An inaugural address was needed even in the Beyond Grade A circle. Seeing that everyone was looking at him, Han Xiao pondered for a few seconds before speaking.

"Since I've been elected as the president, let me say a few words… It has already been fifty years since the Beyond Grade A Association was founded. From nothing, we have built a strong foundation. We've done quite a good job till now, and we couldn't have done it without the contributions of the former president Manison and all of you here.

"The initial purpose of founding the association was to unite all Beyond Grade As, form an interest network, and protect the Beyond Grade As. This purpose will be passed on. All decisions made in the future will work in accordance with this principle. All individuals or organizations who attempt to divide the Beyond Grade As will be the association's enemy.

"As for me… I'll also do my very best to make the association grow better, making it into a shelter for all Beyond Grade As. I won't say too much. All of you here know what kind of person I am. I'll certainly do my best to live up to your expectations."

At this point, no matter what their thoughts about Han Xiao were, all the Beyond Grade As were nodding with approval.

Everyone present knew that from this second, the Beyond Grade A Association had entered the age of Black Star!

Looking at the different expressions on their faces, Han Xiao paused before speaking again in an unusual tone.

"We might see a revolution not far in the future. Be mentally prepared."

Hearing this, many people could sense that Han Xiao was subtly conveying a meaningful message, but they could not figure out what it was.

And Han Xiao did not elaborate.

When the Holy Accord members appeared, a drastic change would come.

He could already see that a storm was about to arrive!

…

In a certain secret base of the Mechanic Emperor, as the election meeting ended, Manison deactivated the remote projection, and his sights returned to the dark room.

He picked up another communicator that had been in a call all this time, and the person he was calling was surprisingly Kasuyi.

"Thanks to you not running. The handover was smooth," Kasuyi said with a smile.

"For the record, I did not give up running because you came to ask me do it," Manison said with a poker face and a normal tone.

Others had no idea that the two of them negotiated privately. Kasuyi secretly contacted Manison and asked him to give up thinking of being re-elected. They had made an agreement under the table.

Kasuyi smiled. "No matter what, you've helped me."

"Humph, it was an election, but it looked like Black Star was the only one whose words mattered." Manison snorted with dissatisfaction.

"That's called 'the support of the people led to the right result happening'." Kasuyi laughed.

"I have no idea what benefits Black Star gave you for you to help him this much. If I ran for office, even if I might not be re-elected, I'd at least be a vice president." Manison frowned.

Kasuyi shook his head. "He didn't give me anything. I did this of my own volition."

"Ever since you and him went to the secondary dimensions together a few decades ago, you've always spoken for him. Did Black Star grab your heart with his charm? Humph, anyway, it's none of my concern. Just don't forget you owe me a favor." Manison snorted softly.

"I won't, old friend."

Kasuyi smiled, and his figure disappeared from the screen.

Manison hung up the call, and his eyes narrowed slightly.

Kasuyi's request was only a very small factor in him choosing not to do anything during the election. He was actually already planning to do it.

The first reason was that he knew his place and knew that there was no way he could beat Black Star, so he did not want to humiliate himself. The second reason was that he wanted to keep a low profile and let Black Star take all the pressure so that he could look for opportunities in the dark and turn things around in future elections.

The third reason was the main reason Manison made this choice. After forty years of growth, the Beyond Grade A Association had become more and more independent, which prevented the three Universal Civilizations from gaining any new allies. He saw the brewing danger in this situation and felt that the three Universal Civilizations would very soon take the next step.

He stepped down to let Black Star take all the pressure.

Manison also understood that Black Star was the best person to lead the association in times like this. Black Star's words mattered to the three Universal Civilizations, so he could relieve the pressure from the three Universal Civilizations to a certain extent. Black Star had a higher chance of leading the association to conquer the difficulties ahead and prevent the 'cleansing' from happening.

He had personal beef with Black Star, but protecting the safety of the Beyond Grade As was more important to him. Therefore, he chose to take a step back and not cause problems for Han Xiao's election.

Manison closed his eyes.

"The three Universal Civilizations won't watch us grow infinitely. Having rested for more than forty years, they'll act soon… Black Star, will your method be enough to deal with the next 'Tragedy of the Pinnacles'?

"Your philosophy is wrong; peaceful developments won't lead to compromise. If we don't make rulers like the three Universal Civilizations feel afraid, how can they allow us to grow stronger freely? If you can't hold on, don't blame me for releasing the imitation of the Virtual Mutiny Virus…"

…

"Black Star has taken over as the president of the Beyond Grade A Association."

This news rapidly spread out in the galactic society, which had been paying attention.

Tons of reports appeared on the internet, announcing the arrival of the age of Black Star!

Suddenly, Black Star, who had kept a low profile for forty years, became the center of attention once again. His reputation and fame rocketed, and his legendary deeds of the past got brought up by the media once again for promotion, attracting tons of attention. Even the stock price of the Germinal Financial Group increased quite a bit because of it.

Overall, the galactic society had a positive attitude for this change. Black Star was the hero of the universe who solved the Intelligent Plague, a Stuarts Peace Prize winner, a receiver of the Galaxy Medal, the shared consultant of the three Universal Civilizations… These titles were so much better than the Mechanic Emperor's. Most people trusted that the Beyond Grade A Association would peacefully grow under Han Xiao's lead.

While the outside world expressed all kinds of opinions about the Beyond Grade A Association having a new president, Han Xiao had already teleported to the Ancient Star Desert and met with the Holy Accord organization.

He did not go there just to discuss the Primordial Ones appearing in public but also for another big matter…

The keys to open the Third Sanctum were once again all collected!

Chapter 1252: Enter

The spaceship rode into the port of a certain secret base of the Holy Accord organization. The hatch slid open. Han Xiao walked out and saw Oathkeeper waiting on the dock right away.

"Yo, it's been some time. You're still wearing this? Don't you need to wash your clothes?" Han Xiao laughed and joked.

"… No." Oathkeeper's lips twitched. "I've been waiting for you. Let's talk inside."

Oathkeeper led the way ahead. Han Xiao followed him along the corridor of the base.

The two spoke while walking.

Han Xiao scratched his chin and said curiously, "It's only been a few decades, and you've collected all The Third Sanctum's keys again. Aren't you too efficient?"

"That's nothing. There's only zero times or countless times for entering the Sanctums. With experience, doing it again becomes much easier. Some keys are not single use, and we've kept inventory of them. For example, the Primal Esper Ability Entities. We were stuck on that previously, and we managed to collect them all the last time, so we just have to use them again… As for the other types of keys, with your financial help and channels you provided, collecting them was much easier than before," Oathkeeper explained.

Han Xiao nodded.

Basically, the crucial items could be reused and did not have to be collected again.

It was the same in the previous life too. The Holy Accord organization's scale was much larger than when they appeared, which meant that Oathkeeper had definitely entered the Sanctums multiple times, so being this efficient was not surprising.

This time, Han Xiao would be entering the Sanctum alone to complete the third round for the [A Relay Across Iterations] mission as well as out of curiosity.

The two of them chatted along the way and came to the elderlies activity room. As soon as Han Xiao walked in, dozens of pairs of eyes focused on him.

The many revived Primordial Ones were waiting there. As soon as they saw Han Xiao, they all swarmed over and surrounded him.

"Black Star, congrats on being elected as the association president!"

"The promised time has come. We can go out now, right?"

They spoke noisily.

Han Xiao raised his hand and signaled for them to calm down. He then said slowly, "Hmm, it's about time. But I think it's better to wait one or two more years."

"One or two years?"

The expressions on their faces changed slightly.

You told us to stay here three years after three years. Now it's almost fifty years, pal! We really can't hold it in much longer!

"Ahem, guys, don't be in such a hurry. I have three reasons for that."

Han Xiao pointed his fingers and explained, "Firstly, I've only just been elected as the president, so it's best to wait a little. Secondly, in the past forty years, the three Universal Civilizations have not gotten a single new ally, so they're probably not very happy about it. I have to see what they're going to do first.

"As for the last reason… it's that I have to enter the Sanctum, and I don't know how long it'll take."

According to Oathkeeper, the flow of time in the Sanctums was different from the outside world. Oathkeeper did not feel like he spent a long time inside, but when he came out, he found out that a few years had already passed in the main universe. Therefore, Han Xiao had to prepare for that.

Hearing this, the many Primordial Ones looked like they were in a dilemma.

They wanted to go out right away, but if Han Xiao was in the Sanctum and might disappear for a few years, without the support of President Black Star in this period of time, many things would be difficult.

"Doesn't matter," Pangon coldly said. "I wasn't going to join the association anyway. I've decided, I'll leave shortly!"

Han Xiao glanced at him, nodded, and did not say anything.

This batch of revived Primordial Ones were generally divided into three groups with different goals. One wanted to enjoy the privileges of Beyond Grade As in a peaceful era so wanted to join the association. For example, Lady Lust. They were the ones who were conflicted.

The second group wanted to continue hiding in the Holy Accord and help Oathkeeper operate the organization. They did not plan to go out, so of course, they had no problem with waiting.

The last group were the creditors from the exploration era wanting to take revenge against the advanced civilizations. They were the minority, and their representative was Pangon. He planned to be a lone wolf to begin with, so he did not want to join the association.

Han Xiao did not want these people to join either. After all, acts of revenge would heavily intensify the conflicts between the three Universal Civilizations and the Beyond Grade As. If those people entered the association, should the association help them or not when the time came? Most association members would definitely oppose helping them. Therefore, he felt he might as well let these lone wolves be so that they do not drag the association down with them.

In his previous life, these people's acts of revenge were one of the crucial fuses of the Calamity of the Supers version. Han Xiao did not care about where Pangon and the others were going.

Han Xiao knew what Pangon was thinking too. Pangon did not expect the association to help. He knew the purpose of the Beyond Grade A Association, so he did not want to burden the association and decided to take on the responsibility of taking revenge alone.

In Han Xiao's previous life, Pangon never leaked the existence of the Holy Accord. Therefore, though headstrong, this guy was loyal to his morals.

Han Xiao looked at Beiger and the others. "What about you guys? Are you willing to wait for me?"

Beiger thought about it, nodded, and said, "Although we can't endure it much longer, the big picture is still more important. We might not be from the same generation as the modern Beyond Grade As, but we all represent the same grade and share the same interests. When we appear, the entire Beyond Grade A class will definitely be shaken. Don't worry, we won't damage the big picture for our personal interests."

Hearing this, Han Xiao smiled with satisfaction.

After more than forty years, most Primordial Ones had adapted to the era. Some of them no longer only thought for themselves and were tricked… ahem… convinced by him to be invested in the Beyond Grade A Association's future, letting go of their past in the exploration era. They decided to participate in this new warfare between the Beyond Grade As and the advanced civilizations and were willing to fight for the entire Beyond Grade A class.

From these people's perspective, when the huge change arrived, they could not not have the key person, Black Star. For that, they were willing to continue hiding for some time.

Although Beiger and these guys had yet to appear in public, in their hearts, they already considered themselves members of the Beyond Grade A Association and had the collective interest in their mind.

"Great, I was not wrong about you guys…" Han Xiao laughed, quickly comforting their emotions.

As they received a response, they arranged their emotions and went back to playing cards on the side.

Han Xiao pulled Oathkeeper out of the elderlies activity room and into a side room to speak privately.

Han Xiao closed the door and said, "To deal with the drastic change that's about to come, we need more Beyond Grade As. Are all the revival mediums prepared?"

"Hmm, they're all ready. Thanks to the fact that many Beyond Grade As left offspring and races behind, they weren't difficult to collect." Oathkeeper nodded.

This time, Han Xiao would be entering the Sanctums. He was going in with a mission—to revive more Beyond Grade As.

Reviving Beyond Grade As through the Sanctums required all kinds of mediums. In the past few decades, the Black Star Army and the Holy Accord organization had been secretly carrying out this task of collecting objects related to old Beyond Grade As. They included their inheritance, the remaining people of their race, and others.

Han Xiao took the list and scanned through. His eyes narrowed slightly.

"Looks like there are some strong people in the list of people we're reviving this round."

"No matter how strong they are, are they stronger than you?" Oathkeeper curled his lips.

"You're right about that. I'm f*cking invincible." Han Xiao accepted this compliment.

He then recalled Jayz of the Celestial Star Alliance and wondered if he could revive this guy from a different Iteration.

Shaking his head, Han Xiao temporarily put away this thought. He found an empty room and entered alone. He blocked all the surveillance in the room, took out his communicator, and called a number.

He first called Kasuyi. Very soon, Kasuyi appeared on the screen.

"Black Star… oh no, it's Mr. President now. What is it?" Kasuyi smiled.

Han Xiao scratched his chin and said, "I might have to disappear for an unknown amount of time, maybe a few days, maybe a few years. When I'm not around, help manage the association's affairs."

"Where are you going?" Kasuyi wiped the smile off his face and frowned.

"Remember our experience in the secondary dimensions? I found some clues and need to spend some time investigating them." Han Xiao did not share the details, but Kasuyi knew about the Sanctum-related information too, so he would know what he was saying.

As expected, Kasuyi understood what he meant and looked surprised. He did not question him further, nodded seriously, and said, "Go then, don't worry. I'll take care of the association."

When Kasuyi found out about the Sanctums from Jayz a few decades ago, he knew that Han Xiao's path was the right one and stood on his side. They had become secret allies.

Kasuyi had no interest in power; he stepped up to become the vice president not because he wanted a higher position but because Han Xiao told him to as it would indirectly help Han Xiao solidify his position further. It had no disadvantages anyway, so he did not mind helping Han Xiao.

"I'll leave it to you then."

Han Xiao nodded, said a few more things, and hung up.

He did not stop there. He then called up Hila, Ames, and so on, telling them he would disappear for some time, going to the secondary dimensions to look for opportunities to undergo God's Trait Transformation.

This was not rare for peak Beyond Grade As, so this excuse was very useful. Hila, Ames, and the others did not suspect anything.

Han Xiao told them to take care of the army while he was out.

Then, he called the last few numbers, the three Universal Civilizations' men.

The three Universal Civilizations once wanted him to be elected, thinking he would be a more suitable leader of the association than the Mechanic Emperor. However, after decades, conflicts accumulated quicker than expected, so this slight favor was no longer enough. There was no way the three Universal Civilizations would allow the Beyond Grade A Association to continue becoming stronger just because of him alone.

Han Xiao did not know how long he would spend in the Sanctums, so he planned to restate his identity and stance to keep things stable for a period of time.

The negotiation was considerably smooth. After all, he still had the consultant of the three Universal Civilizations title. Han Xiao found out what the three Universal Civilizations were planning to do.

The three Universal Civilizations were still observing the changes him becoming the president would cause, so they would not make the conflicts explode in a short period of time. This was logical and within his expectations.

After arranging everything, Han Xiao approached Oathkeeper again, looked at his anticipation-filled eyes, and nodded solemnly.

"Start the preparations and open the Sanctum as soon as possible!"

…

Three days later, at an unpopulated area near the Holy Accord organization's base, spaceships hovered in the desolate cosmic space.

Han Xiao was the only one hovering outside the spaceships. He remained in contact with Oathkeeper using the screen inside the mechanical suit.

On the screen, Oathkeeper made an encouraging gesture and said, "Ready? Everything's ready on my side. The Sanctum can be opened anytime."

"Do it." Han Xiao exhaled and calmed his emotions.

Oathkeeper nodded, turned around, and ordered, "All units, begin!"

As soon as he said that, the spaceships immediately moved. They had rehearsed the process countless times, like an impressive machine, not a single mistake was made.

Bang bang bang!

Primal Esper Ability Entities were shot out one after another, contained in special seals. Colorful light beams focused at one point, rapidly expanded, and turned into a hovering white sphere.

Under the effects of special devices, like a piece of rubber, the light sphere shrank into a bright ring only about a hundred meters wide. Its energy was extremely condensed.

Then, the remaining spaceships activated one device after another and released the other 'keys' into this ring through beams.

As the space seemed to have trembled, the ring suddenly shone even brighter and projected six mirage-like light gates.

The next second, five light gates disappeared, leaving only one that seemed to have materialized from an illusion to something real. It was still shaking unsteadily like it could disappear any second.

"That's the entrance of the Third Sanctum. Go!" Oathkeeper hastily said.

Han Xiao focused his mind, activated his thrusters, and dashed into the Sanctum's entrance.

The next moment, the light before his eyes suddenly became much brighter. All he could see was white.

The moment he passed the gate, Han Xiao felt his body suddenly become lighter as if he had broken through some kind of barrier. He felt fuzzy, like he was no longer in this world.

"I'm finally inside…"

Chapter 1253: The Third Sanctum (1)

This moment felt both like an instant and like countless years.

Han Xiao's vision slowly became clear as he gradually saw his surroundings.

This was an endless world of white with no gravity. His body floated in midair. Countless white light spheres floated all around him, some small, some large. Looking from afar, every light sphere seemed to be playing blurry images.

"The Third Sanctum does indeed look no different from what Oathkeeper described…"

Han Xiao looked around curiously. Suddenly, he turned around and saw that the light gate entrance he came from was trembling intensely as if it was going to collapse.

Suddenly, out of intuition, he extended his hand and closed his fist.

Buzz!

At this time, a stream of special energy suddenly appeared in his body. Six warm streams of energy seemed to have appeared out of thin air and gathered on his palm, turning into a glowing unique pattern.

The next moment, the entrance seemed to have received some kind of support and instantly became stable, turning into a slowly spinning light gate like a glowing mirror.

"What's this?"

Han Xiao was surprised. Earlier, he only thought of not wanting the entrance to disappear, and suddenly, he intuitively felt that he could make it happen, which was exactly what happened.

He looked down on his palm and observed this mark that appeared out of nowhere. It looked like it was a combination of six patterns, and it did not seem whole.

"That's weird. When did I have this thing inside my body?"

Han Xiao was just about to open the interface to check his status, when to his absolute shock, he discovered he could no longer open the interface.

This was the first time ever the interface did not respond!

Han Xiao frowned. He clenched his fist and tried to command the energy inside his body, the next moment, streams of golden Mechanical Force shot out.

"Hmm. Although the interface can't be opened, my status did not change. I'm still at my peak."

Han Xiao sensed the state of his body and heaved a sigh of relief. Although he could not open the interface for the time being, it did not affect his abilities.

Since the very start, everything he felt was real. All the abilities he learned became his own techniques that he could use anytime. If it was a player, they would not even be able to use any ability at all without the interface. For example, when building machines, he had to personally finish all the processes, while players only had to wait for the progress bar to finish. The difference was huge.

This was Han Xiao's first time inside a Sanctum. All he could do was slowly figure things out.

He tested several abilities and realized he could use almost all of them. The only ones he could not use were the abilities that were related to the outside world such as quantum network communication functions and the Dimension Factory. Even the King's teleportation function became unusable.

Although he somehow stopped the Sanctum entrance from disappearing, all means of communication he had with the outside world were no longer working. His call with the Holy Accord organization was also cut off.

"Interesting. The Sanctum is very special. Not only is the King suit useless, even the interface can't be opened…"

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes, and his brain quickly spun. Staring at the mark on his palm, he suddenly had a flash of insight.

"Six patterns… six… if I remember correctly, that's about the same number of Third Sanctum fragments I have, isn't it?"

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

Despite not being able to see the interface now, he still remembered things like that.

Initially, he only had two [The Third Sanctum] fragments, one from the [Primal Esper Ability Collector] milestone and another from beating up the elderlies of Holy Accord.

The mission requirement of the third round of [A Relay Across Iterations] was to enter any one of the Sanctums. The reward was three Sanctum fragments of the respective Sanctum. Although he could not see the interface now, Han Xiao had a feeling that the interface might still be operating. He could not see the notifications, but the mission rewards were still given.

If that was the case, he had five Third Sanctum fragments.

As for the one extra fragment, Han Xiao had a few speculations about it. According to Oathkeeper's experience, the biggest possibility was that by entering any Sanctums, he would automatically obtain its respective fragment.

If this theory was true, the number would match, and it would explain this situation. This meant that this mark did not appear out of thin air but had always been sleeping inside his body, and the activation requirement was to enter the corresponding Sanctum.

"I had no idea about the use of Sanctum fragments, but they stabilized the Sanctum entrance just now… Does this mean that the Sanctum fragments are related to the level of authority I have in the Sanctums? The more fragments I have, the more things I can do?

"Oathkeeper said he felt like he was in a dream when he was in the Sanctum and his mind was not clear, but my mind is only a little bit distracted and not as fuzzy as he said. Is this also because of the Sanctum fragments?"

Han Xiao could not help but ponder.

Suddenly, he regained focus and shook his head heavily.

"These things can only be speculated now. I can't waste too much time. I should find out what happened after I go out and can see the interface… The priority now is to observe the Sanctum!"

Han Xiao focused, controlled his body, and flew to the nearest light sphere. He opened his eyes wide, wanting to see the illusions in it clearly, but it was still very blurry.

He hesitated for a moment, reached out the hand that had the Sanctum mark, and carefully touched this light sphere.

Swoosh!

At the moment he came into contact with it, an enormous stream of information gushed into his mind like a tsunami.

Suddenly, illusions appeared before Han Xiao's eyes. It was as if he saw the entire rise and fall of a race, creating a glorious civilization, breeding great people generation after generation, improving its technology rapidly. It was eventually destroyed in a disaster.

Han Xiao remained stunned for quite some time before removing his hand. He realized that he could only remember parts of the illusions he saw. Some knowledge appeared in his head out of nowhere that seemed to be a part of the technology this civilization created in its development.

"This knowledge mainly revolves around biology and gene tech. It's only a part of this civilization's technology…"

Han Xiao digested this surprise and went back to touching more light spheres.

After several tests, he had a rough idea of the mechanics of the Sanctum and concluded a few patterns from speculations.

Firstly, every light sphere was an Information Form collective body that recorded the information of various things, mainly civilizations. Usually, one light sphere represented one civilization. None of them existed historically and should all be from the past Iterations.

Secondly, he could read the information inside the light spheres by touching them, but he could only remember parts. The number of things he could remember should be related to the level of authority he had, meaning the number of Sanctum fragments he possessed.

However, there was a limit to the number of memories he could keep. At a certain point, when he read new light spheres, he would forget a part of the information he read earlier.

According to the nature of the Information Form, the number of memories he could keep every time he entered the Sanctums was very likely limited and would only be reset the next time he entered. This meant that the amount of knowledge he could bring out of the Sanctums each time was limited too, and the limit probably still depended on the number of Sanctum fragments.

Thirdly, after touching multiple light spheres, he noticed that the technology he acquired was mostly related to biology, genetics, and Esper Abilities. This might be the difference between Sanctums, meaning that the knowledge of these civilizations in the past Iterations was stored separately based on its type. Different Sanctums might represent the different types of knowledge. The Third Sanctum most likely contained the biology, genetics, and Esper Ability related technology.

Fourthly, some light spheres contained information about Beyond Grade As from different Iterations. By reading it, he could immerse himself in their life experience and even acquire some of the information they knew.

However, there were only Espers in the Third Sanctum. According to Han Xiao's speculation, if he read the light spheres about Mechanics or Mages, he would very likely acquire the knowledges, technology, spells, blueprints, or other things these Beyond Grade As had.

"Jayz didn't lie…"

Han Xiao was shocked.

Although parts of these patterns were speculation, he felt that it should be very close to the truth!

Other than completing the revival goal, Oathkeeper almost did not gain anything at all the last time he entered the Sanctum. It might be because his level of authority was not high enough.

However, he had six fragments in the Third Sanctum to begin with. His authority level was a full five levels higher than Oathkeeper. He should be able to do much more.

Having thought of Jayz, his request appeared in Han Xiao's mind.

"Let's see how the Sanctum revival system works."

Han Xiao focused and took out the mediums that Oathkeeper had given him.

As soon as he thought about testing how the Sanctum revival system worked, the mark on his palm seemed to have sensed it and flickered.

Swoosh!

The next second, thin lines of light suddenly shot out from some light spheres and met before Han Xiao's eyes. With a bright flash, a glowing mark hovered in midair.

Han Xiao sized it up and was delighted.

"This mark… it's the Sanctum revival mark Oathkeeper drew."

Han Xiao reached out and touched this mark right away. The mark instantly turned into a stream of light and landed on the back of his hand.

At the same time, a stream of data flowed into his brain that recorded the instructions on how to use the Sanctum revival mark and the list of targets this mark could revive.

Sadly, Jayz was not in the list.

"Looks like it failed…"

Having realized that, Han Xiao sighed.

Either this medium of his was not recognized by the Sanctum, or there was some kind of restriction on reviving targets from other Iterations like Jayz said.

Although they did not spend a lot of time together, Jayz left a heavy impression on him. Since the revival had failed and he could not meet Jayz again, Han Xiao felt complicated.

"Never mind, this is just fate."

Han Xiao shook his head and cleared up his emotions. His thoughts jumped from Jayz to the Celestial Star Alliance, and he murmured, "The Information Form collective body of the Celestial Star Alliance Iteration should also be inside the Sanctums, right?"

As soon as he thought of that, the Sanctum mark reacted and glowed, pointing to a direction.

Seeing this, unprepared, Han Xiao was surprised.

Then, he flew in the direction the mark pointed and stopped beside a bunch of light spheres.

"Are these the Information Form light spheres of the Celestial Star Alliance Iteration?"

As he thought that, he read the content of one of the light spheres and immediately verified his speculation. It indeed contained the information of a certain civilization from the Celestial Star Alliance Iteration.

Regaining focus, Han Xiao looked at the mark on his hand with surprise.

"Looks like I guessed correctly. The Sanctum fragments represent authority, but it's surprising it can even lead the way… Well, I guess it makes sense. There's so much Information Form information inside the Sanctum; finding a specific piece of information is like finding a needle in a haystack."

As soon as he said that, Han Xiao's body shook, and a daring thought appeared in Han Xiao's head. He mumbled, "If it can lead the way like an index, if I search for the Iteration information of the Galaxy and find it, does that mean that we're already…"

Buzz!

Before he even finished, the Sanctum mark pointed in another direction.

"There really is‽"

Han Xiao's breath stopped for a second, and his heart sank.

He bit his lips, followed the direction silently, and came to a light sphere.

He stood in place for quite some time before he finally prepared himself mentally, took a deep breath, and slowly touched this light sphere.

However, the next moment, Han Xiao was dumbfounded.

There was no content in this light sphere. It was empty!

"Why isn't there anything‽"

Han Xiao had touched many light spheres. This was the first time he had come across this.

He then tried to search for the three Universal Civilizations of the Galaxy and the other advanced civilizations.

Every search worked, but none of the target light spheres had any information in them at all. They were all empty shells.

Han Xiao was shocked yet could not help but feel relieved.

He was worried about seeing the information of the explored universe inside the Sanctum. It would mean that just like the Celestial Star Alliance, Galaxy was only an illusion of the past. However, this was beyond his expectations. Although he could search for the target civilizations, they were all empty. Han Xiao did not know what it meant, but at least it was not the worst scenario.

"Interesting, what is going on?"

Han Xiao frowned and pondered, beginning to speculate.

"The reason they're empty shells… does it mean that Galaxy is the ongoing Iteration, meaning it's the present, and its related information will only be recorded by the Sanctum after we experience the Great Reboot? If that's really the case, it should be good news…"

This time, Han Xiao suddenly thought of something, and his expression changed slightly.

"Therefore, these empty shells… are the gravestones the Sanctum prepared for this Iteration?

"Is the Sanctum trying to say that nothing can escape death?"

Han Xiao became silent.

He silently looked at the empty light sphere before him. At this moment, his heart was filled with a strong sense of grief.

Chapter 1254: The Third Sanctum (2)

Be it the three Universal Civilizations or the World Tree Civilization, they were all empty shells.

Han Xiao took a deep breath, cleared his emotions, and buried them, not looking at the empty light sphere in front of him any longer.

"This isn't a bad thing. At least it's not an illusion of the past like the Celestial Star Alliance. Plus, judging from the Celestial Star Alliance's time period, the Galaxy is far from the Great Reboot. I don't even know if I'll live till that day…

"Speaking of which, if I search for Planet Earth, will it have any results?"

This thought suddenly appeared in Han Xiao's mind.

He looked down at the mark but realized it did not respond this time. He raised his brows.

"Hmm, no reaction, huh? My old home is still in another world then. It has nothing to do with our Iterations…"

Han Xiao shook his head.

He focused his mind and went back to business, putting the information he read into the storage device.

Although his devices lost internet connection, they still functioned. He wanted to see if he could go around the memory capacity limit of the Sanctums by storing information in his hardware.

Han Xiao quickly stored the technology he acquired into the storage device, then started to touch another light sphere to read its information. The new technology he acquired once again replaced some information in his mind.

Then, Han Xiao opened the storage device and saw that the same information disappeared in it too.

"Looks like this doesn't work either… Be it the human brain, mechanical hardware, or anything else, as long as it's an information transmission medium, the part of information will be wiped no matter what. It's similar to how Destiny's Child works, just in a more advanced way. It's one of the principles of the High Dimensional Information Form…"

Han Xiao then tried a few more times using different methods, but nothing worked, so he had no choice but to let go of this thought.

He put the storage device away, stopped making meaningless tries, and looked around the Sanctum. He nodded.

The Sanctum revival was successful, what Jayz said was verified, he found out about part of the mechanisms of the Sanctums, and his memory capacity reached the limit. From how Han Xiao looked at it, his goal of entering the Sanctum was basically achieved. It was about time to leave through the gate he came from.

Just as he was about to move, he suddenly had a flash of insight and realized a problem.

"Wait a minute. I knew about the Sanctums' origin, the contributions of the Savior Civilization and the Sanctum Civilization, and how they passed on the knowledge from Jayz… but how did Oathkeeper find out?

"If the information he has only came from reading the light spheres, with so many light spheres here and the memory capacity limit, it should most likely be incomplete…"

Han Xiao frowned.

The Sanctum did not just record the final civilization of an Iteration but all civilizations of every Iteration. As long as they once existed, they would be recorded whether they were weak or strong, unlike the information of individuals.

This meant that only an extremely few light spheres contained the information about the origin of the Sanctums and The Great Reboot.

According to Han Xiao's experience of reading so many light spheres, if not because he found out about the full picture from Jayz, he would most likely not have been able to combine them into this much information just by reading the light spheres. The memory capacity limit was the main reason.

However, Oathkeeper's authority level in the Third Sanctum was far lower than his; unless he got extremely lucky and touched one of the 'final civilizations', there was no way he would know so much. Therefore, Han Xiao started to have doubts about Oathkeeper's source of information—he did not believe that b*stard would be so lucky, or he would not have taken so many years to collect all the Sanctum keys.

Han Xiao pondered. The moment he doubted why the Sanctums existed, a change suddenly occurred!

Buzz!

The Sanctum mark on his hand suddenly flickered and shot out streams of light like silk that formed a translucent light curtain hovering before him.

"Hmm? What's this?"

Han Xiao looked at it closely.

Chains of symbols that he could not understand appeared on the curtain. The language seemed to have changed every few paragraphs. Han Xiao could read none of them.

However, the next second, all these symbols turned into the common Galaxy language.

"It can automatically change into a language the reader understands, another Information Form mechanism, I see…"

Han Xiao focused and read from top to bottom. He realized that the contents of the Sanctums and the Iterations were right at the top, clearly explaining the full story. It was basically completely the same with what Jayz said, only more detailed.

Reading further, gaps started to appear every now and then. The further down he read, the more gaps there were.

After reading it for a while, Han Xiao roughly understood what was going on.

"I see, what this light curtain records are the last words of the final civilization of every Iteration. This thing is probably a special message board that passes down the important experiences of final civilizations to the next generations.

"These messages should be arranged according to time. The earliest messages are at the top, basic and the most crucial information about the origins of the Sanctums and the Iteration. This is basically the source of the information Oathkeeper knows… The lower it gets, the closer the messages are to the current Iteration, and the more random gaps there are. This is probably also related to the level of authority. The gaps will only decrease with a high level of authority."

Han Xiao suddenly understood the purpose of the message board—to record the order of the Iterations and let those that came after quickly understand the origins of the Sanctums and the Great Reboot. That way, they did not have to randomly touch light spheres and piece the puzzle together themselves. Those that came after could learn from their experiences and make fewer mistakes.

This message board should be the main platform for the relay between the final civilizations of the various Iterations!

Han Xiao rubbed his chin and said with surprise, "This message board doesn't feel like it came from the Sanctum itself but a change created by the later Iterations…"

Jayz had once said that because the Sanctums were eternal, many final civilizations saw the Sanctums as a breakthrough point and carried out all kinds of plans around it. That caused the Sanctums to 'mutate' and gain new functions. The Sanctum's revival function might be one of them, since the class of the revival targets was not restricted by the different types of Sanctums.

This message board was very likely one of the mutated functions too. Through reading, he realized many civilizations did indeed carry out plans concerning the Sanctums. The first civilization to leave a message clearly conveyed in the message that it was the first to discover the message board function, and there were light spheres of civilizations in earlier Iterations than them.

The first civilization also briefly described the basic mechanisms and functions of the Sanctums, such as the required keys of the other Sanctums. As Han Xiao expected, the Sanctum fragments represented the level of authority.

Even Beyond Grade As occasionally receiving a feeling that Sanctums existed was a mutated function so that the following Iterations could come in contact with the Sanctums earlier and have more time to prepare.

At the same time, the final civilizations in the later Iterations also continued the work of introducing the functions of the Sanctums, adding new mutated functions on the message board. However, most of them were incomplete, and Han Xiao could not see them.

"All the rulers of the Iterations were leading the path for those who came after them…"

Han Xiao's eyes flickered and looked at the light curtain again with different emotions.

[Today is the day to carry out the ███ Plan. Hope everything goes smoothly.]

[Will the ███ really work? We're not actually confident…]

[The Rebirth Plan is based on ███. According to our calculations, our success rate is only at about 1.44%. Maybe we've not studied it enough and won't make it through the Great Reboot, but the technology of the Rebirth Plan will be recorded by the Sanctums. We hope those who come after us can continue to study it. The name of our civilization is ███.]

[We're the ███ Civilization. The Great Reboot has begun; all of this is not a lie. We are using the remainder of our time to leave this message. Our plan will fail. It proves that the ███ technology won't work. Don't take our path, it's a dead end!]

On the light curtain, there were messages full of hope, messages that sounded unconfident, and messages that analyzed the path they took…

Looking at these messages, Han Xiao could almost feel the emotions these civilizations were going through when leaving them. They suppressed their anxiety, despair, and fear, forcing themselves to calm down and leave the knowledge they had to those who came after…

"This must be the true meaning of 'A Relay Across Iterations'… What an incredible history."

At this time, Han Xiao finally had a deeper understanding of the name of this mission. He felt complicated and could not help but respect these civilizations.

"Maybe one day in the future, the three Universal Civilizations will leave a message here too… hmm, or the World Tree Civilization?"

Han Xiao sighed, calmed his emotions, and started searching for messages related to the Celestial Star Alliance.

As the messages were arranged by time, he wanted to see where the Celestial Star Alliance came in and how many Iterations they were away.

He read one message after another, and when he came to the fifth last message, he saw the related information.

As this was relatively recent, the messages below were mostly empty. But he saw the familiar phrase 'World Reset Plan', which was the Celestial Star Alliance's plan to get through the Great Reboot.

"Fifth last, huh. This means that the Celestial Star Alliance is at most four Iterations before us, or the last Iteration before us at minimum…"

Han Xiao nodded.

As one Iteration could leave multiple messages, he did not know who wrote the last few messages. It might be other Iterations or the Celestial Star Alliance. Originally, he could judge from their language as the same language would mean they were from the same Iteration, but the message board had already translated all of them into the Galaxy's general language. Han Xiao tried to but could not turn them back to their original language; he did not know if there was no such function or his level of authority was not high enough. Either way, there was nothing he could do.

The last few messages were filled with blanks. The only valuable piece of information was a phrase in the middle of the last paragraph.

[██████ Information Form becoming real. This is the right path ██████]

Han Xiao scratched his head and did not know what to say.

"Information Form conversion… Both the Intelligent Plague and the Sanctum revival function should share this trait. However, this message actually said this path is the right one… If it really is, how did you guys perish?"

Han Xiao sighed.

He pondered for a while. He then tried to leave a message on the light curtain, but it did not respond.

"Hmm, speaking of which, all the messages on this light curtain are from civilizations, no individuals. I wonder if my authority level is not enough to leave a message, or are the messages left by individuals not recorded by the message board?"

Since there was no way of figuring that now, Han Xiao could only put this question aside and close the message board.

The goal of this trip was mostly achieved. To him, the biggest thing he acquired this time was that he recorded the full methods to open the other Sanctums with his authority level, which was much higher than Oathkeeper's.

Due to the limit of memory capacity, he would probably have to wait till the next time he entered if he wanted to acquire more things.

"I hope I can see other Sanctums next time. The First Sanctum would be best; my authority level there is quite high too."

Han Xiao mumbled to himself and returned to the stabilized Sanctum gate.

He glanced at the Sanctum, then turned around and flew into the gate.

When the bright light filled Han Xiao's sights once again, in the short moment his consciousness was blurry, he only had one thought.

"I've stayed in the Sanctum for five hours at most. I wonder how much time has passed in the universe…"

Chapter 1255: Fourth Round Mission and Second Revival

Out in space, a light gate suddenly appeared and spat Han Xiao out before disappearing.

Han Xiao only regained focus as if his consciousness got dragged back to his body after being stunned for about ten seconds.

"Hmm? I'm already out?"

Han Xiao felt the complete opposite from when he entered the Sanctum. It was as if he passed through a thin membrane and his body became heavier, like stepping out from a pool.

Recalling what he had experienced in the Sanctum, his memories became blurry like he was seeing through a clouded window. However, it felt much better than what Oathkeeper described. It should be because his authority was higher.

The technology and knowledge he had memorized were totally clear.

Han Xiao looked down at his palm. The mark that represented his authority level in the Sanctum was already gone, leaving only the Sanctum revival mark.

"Let's see if I can open the interface now…"

Han Xiao tried to bring up the interface, and the next moment, notifications popped up rapidly one after another.

You have successfully entered The Third Sanctum.

You have received 1 [The Third Sanctum] Fragment.

[A Relay Across Iterations] third round completed.

You have received 200 Billion EXP, 2 Random Rewards, 3 [The Third Sanctum] Fragments.

You have entered a Sanctum. [The Third Sanctum] fragments are now assembling…

Assembly completed. You have received ability [The Third Sanctum Authority Lv6]!

"I knew it, the fragments represent authority. I can't open the interface in the Sanctums, but it still works."

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

He opened the ability introduction of [The Third Sanctum Authority Lv6] and read it. It was basically about the same as what the Sanctum's message board described, only more detailed. It also stated that the speed of time in the Sanctums also relied on the level of authority.

Han Xiao took out his communicator to look at the date and was relieved.

"Phew, less than four months have passed. This is much shorter than I expected, unlike that unlucky Oathkeeper, who spent years there. This means that the higher the level of authority, the closer the speed of time in the Sanctum compared to the main universe."

He was in a much more delighted mood. After all, he had expected this to take years and already made preparations for it. Since it had taken less than four months, it was a pleasant surprise.

He took out the communicator and looked at it. Since he had already made the arrangements before entering the Sanctum, the affairs of the army and the association were all taken care of. The past few months had been peaceful, and nothing big had happened. Those seeking revenge, including Pangon, had yet to appear.

"This is the best scenario possible. I still have a hold of things."

Han Xiao nodded, put the communicator away, and looked at the interface. The fourth-round mission of [A Relay Across Iterations] had also popped up.

Fourth round started!

Mission Requirements (Optional)

Share the information related to the Sanctums, The Great Reboot, the Universe Iterations, and so on with the current advanced civilizations (Super Star Cluster minimum).

Prove the existence of the Sanctums to the advanced civilizations and help them to open the Sanctums.

Make use of the level of authority advantage you have and lead the advanced civilizations into the Sanctums.

Remarks: Select one or more mission requirements stated above. The more requirements completed, the higher the Mission Rating for this round will be.

Basic Reward: 25 Billion EXP, 1 All Sanctum Fragment.

Bonus reward will be given depending on the Mission Rating.

"Hmm, so this is what the fourth round is like… It requires the person who entered the Sanctum to share this precious information with the advanced civilizations… Well, it makes sense. This is the meaning of a 'relay', after all. The perspective of this mission is bigger; civilizations are the key to the universe's growth. The sooner they know about the Sanctums, the more time they'll have to prepare. The final goal of this mission, judging from its name, is to help the civilizations get through the Great Reboot…"

However, although Han Xiao understood the purpose of this mission, he did not plan to do it.

From the perspective of the mission, helping the civilizations get control of the Sanctums was the top priority. However, this would cause unpredictable impacts on his plan.

It was no longer personal. Han Xiao had to think for all the Beyond Grade As.

In the future, to deal with the Great Reboot, they might have to work with the three Universal Civilizations. However, for now, there was no way he was going to be in a hurry to share such precious information with the advanced civilizations—it would be betraying the Beyond Grade As.

He only planned to work with the three Universal Civilizations after the association got a firm hold of the Sanctum revival function. Otherwise, the Celestial Star Alliance's complete rule over the Beyond Grade As would be a prime example of their future.

Han Xiao sighed and decided not to complete the mission for the time being.

At this time, a few spaceships suddenly deactivated their stealth mode, appeared, and asked cautiously in the public channel, "Is this His Excellency Black Star?"

"Yes, it's be."

Han Xiao looked up and was not surprised.

He had noticed these few Holy Accord organization spaceships earlier and knew that they were the guards Oathkeeper had stationed there.

Han Xiao paused, took out the communicator, and called Oathkeeper. It was picked up very quickly.

Oathkeeper appeared on the screen with a face full of surprise.

"Black Star? Doesn't it take a few years? How did you return so fast?'

"Maybe because I'm lucky?" Han Xiao shrugged.

"Really? I don't believe you."

Oathkeeper expressed strong doubts and was bitter.

Why did it take a few years for me and only a few months for you? It's unfair!

"By the way, why didn't you tell me about the message board? Naughty you, did you hide it from me on purpose?" Han Xiao narrowed his eyes.

If not because he felt something was not right, he might have left without seeing the message board. Furthermore, Oathkeeper did not say anything about the Sanctum's authority level, which made him unavoidably suspect Oathkeeper's motives.

"What message board? What's that?" Oathkeeper said with a confused tone.

"You don't know?"

Han Xiao raised his brows and observed Oathkeeper's expression but could not see anything.

It might be because Oathkeeper's authority level was too low and he could not remember, or he was hiding it deliberately. Anyway, no matter what motives Oathkeeper had, such a trivial matter was in the past. Han Xiao did not want to bother dwelling on it.

"… Never mind. I've already acquired the Sanctum revival mark. Quickly bring the fleet over."

"Okay, on it," Oathkeeper immediately replied.

Han Xiao nodded, thought about it, and added, "By the way, it might be best to bring those Primordial Ones. We're not reviving only the people we know this time. We have to make sure they're under control."

"Understood." Oathkeeper nodded.

The targets of the first revival were the old members of the Holy Accord organization, all people who knew about the Sanctums, so they got a grip of the situation very quickly. However, the targets of this batch were outsiders who had no idea the Holy Accord even existed. Once they were revived, it would be difficult for them to accept the reality.

The targets of this revival were filtered, mostly Beyond Grade As who died in accidents. None of them were a direct member of any advanced civilizations, an ally at most. Also, many of them died during the Tragedy of the Pinnacles.

As the Tragedy of the Pinnacles incident had the highest number of Beyond Grade A deaths ever since the exploration era, they occupied quite a high percentage of all Beyond Grade A deaths in history, so it was tough to avoid those who were sacrificed in the Tragedy of the Pinnacles in the process of finding suitable targets to revive. Even Han Xiao could not guarantee there was no one difficult to deal with among them.

In his previous life, the Holy Accord revived many batches of Beyond Grade As, including many outsiders. Yet, they still only appeared during the World Tree war version and did not leak any information beforehand. This proved that the Holy Accord had a certain way to restrain them.

The Holy Accord organization was not a charitable organization. Never mind those Primordial Ones who joined long ago, but if any outsider who revived later wanted to cause trouble, the Holy Accord probably would not mind sending them back into their coffins while adding more nails.

"Thinking about it, Oathkeeper lying to the members of the organization saying that they could only revive once was a good thing. This way, those who revive after will treasure this one revival chance and won't mess around."

Han Xiao nodded. He hung up the call, opened the secondary dimensional army box, took out a small portable base from it, and rested inside, reading about events from the past four months while waiting for Oathkeeper.

Two days later, the Holy Accord organization's fleet finally arrived along with many Primordial Ones.

The fleet docked at Han Xiao's portable base, and they met there.

"It's surprising you came out after only four months. Looks like we won't have to wait years." Beiger and the others were pleasantly surprised.

Han Xiao scanned around but did not see Pangon and his clique. He asked, "Where's Pangon and his group?"

"They left the Holy Accord three months ago. We have no contact with them now." Oathkeeper shook his head.

Han Xiao nodded and did not say anything. This was within his expectations. The good news was that before Pangon caused any big problems, he had already returned.

"Alright, let's cut to the chase and revive these people. You guys just stay on the side. They'll only calm down and speak with us properly in the face of overwhelming power." Han Xiao displayed the Sanctum revival mark on the back of his hand.

The others nodded and had no objections.

The group of them came to the venue prepared beforehand and stood in position. Han Xiao took over the activation device from Oathkeeper, took a deep breath, and pressed on the activate button.

Buzz!

The Sanctum revival mark suddenly gave off an extremely bright light, flew out from the back of his hand, and turned into an expanding, blinding sphere of light.

The next moment, the light sphere split up and turned into illuminated figures of various shapes that slowly materialized, turning into several Beyond Grade As who all looked lost.

At the front was a male elf with long ears and an elegant posture who was wearing an exquisite robe. He looked around. His eyes stopped at Han Xiao, and he mumbled, "So, this is the underworld… You're dressed like a ghost. You must be the legendary King of Hell."

"Huh?" Han Xiao frowned. Since you're so clever, speak more while you can, or I'm afraid you won't have the chance in the future.

Chapter 1256: Provocation

Before Han Xiao could respond to this male elf, the other revivors started a commotion. They backed away from each other and stared at the Holy Accord members with caution and shock.

"Didn't I die? Why am I alive again? What have you people done to me!"

"Where is this? Who are you guys‽"

"What in the world is going on? Is this an enemy trap‽"

Shock and panic rapidly spread in the crowd. All kinds of yelling and roaring sounded one after another. It was chaos.

Facing the reality that they came alive after death, even though they were Beyond Grade As, their hearts were still heavily impacted.

Seeing the commotion become worse and worse, Han Xiao took a deep breath. His face tensed up, and his presence exploded!

"Silence!"

Boom!

Like a deafening thunder, the presence of Han Xiao's Energy Rank swept across everyone, and golden lightning bolts flickered in midair.

An enormous pressure suddenly landed on every revivor. It was as if someone had pressed the stop button. All noises disappeared instantly, and everyone shut up. Looks of shock and fear focused on Han Xiao.

It felt like they were at the center of a Primordial Psionic Energy explosion. They intuitively felt an incomparable sense of danger, as if they were prey targeted by a hunter. Their bodies tensed up uncontrollably.

There were peak Beyond Grade As among these revivors who were watching the situation calmly, but even their expressions changed drastically, and they looked at Han Xiao with shock.

This overwhelming energy seemed to be stronger than anyone they had ever seen before!

This man in black in front of them was probably capable of ending their lives!

This time, before these revivors could react, the other Holy Accord members stared at them with their arms crossed and released their presence too!

Boom!

The energy presences of dozens of Beyond Grade As clashed intensely, creating one shockwave after another. The entire room started to tremble!

"These are all Beyond Grade As‽"

The expressions of the revivors changed dramatically. They were petrified.

The pressure only lasted three seconds before Han Xiao told everyone to retract it.

This intimidation act was clearly very effective. None of them dared cause a mess anymore. Seeing that everyone had finally quietened down, Han Xiao smiled and said, "Looks like everyone has calmed down. Good, now we can talk."

Hearing this, the revivors looked around at the dozens of Holy Accord Beyond Grade As and instantly decided to follow their hearts and obediently wait for Han Xiao to continue.

Seeing this, Han Xiao cleared his throat and slowly said in as friendly a tone as possible, "I know everyone needs an explanation. It is now Galaxy Calendar Year 780. You're all Beyond Grade As who died in different eras. The reason you guys have appeared here is that we discovered a unique way that revived you!"

Although the revivors already made some guesses, when hearing the confirmation, they still could not help but be astounded.

How is this possible? We're really alive again‽

Their emotions were complicated and contradicted. They felt both glad and worried.

Although reviving was a surprise, most people still felt weird about it.

You didn't ask for our permission to dig us out!

This is definitely not a free service. These people definitely have motives!

"So, this is not the world after death…" This time, that male elf with a sweet mouth seemed to have realized what was going on. He then looked at Han Xiao with a strange expression, frowned, and said, "Then, what's with that outfit? You think you're very stylish?"

Han Xiao's head was filled with question marks. He could not help but look at his clothes. Sure, it is quite black, but its design is rather exquisite, isn't it?

Is this a matter of personal aesthetic? My officers all think it looks great!

Plus, is this really a good time to look down on my outfit?

Han Xiao sized him up, searched through his mind palace, and found the information about this elf male very soon.

'Elf King' Dylan, a peak Beyond Grade A Mage, was active from the final stage of the exploration era to the early stage of the Galaxy Calendar. His position back then was about the same level as Dark Lord, Void Overlord, and the Mechanic Emperor now, one of the representatives of the Beyond Grade As of the generation.

The elves were a huge race in the universe with many branches like the Galaxy Human Race. Back then, using his power, Dylan united the sub races in the universe one after another, founding an enormous organization belonging to the elf race that was similar to old Milizaus' 'Dragonblood Nation'. It was a time of glory in the history of the elf race.

Back then, the three Universal Civilizations tried to recruit Dylan, but they were rejected. He then allied with multiple Super Star Cluster civilizations.

The reason he did this seemed to be that he felt that he could only choose one of the three Universal Civilizations while if he stood on the Super Star Cluster civilizations' side, he could acquire resources from many of them while enjoying more freedom.

In the end, Dylan died during the Tragedy of the Pinnacles.

It's this guy. Now it makes sense… Han Xiao understood.

According to the records, Dylan's personality was very strange. He never cared about the timing and situation of saying things, nor did he care about others' feelings. Because of that, he had a very bad relationship with the Beyond Grade As back then and many enemies.

In his final battle, he faced a whooping twelve Beyond Grade As who wanted him dead.

This is almost my level of treatment…

As for what this guy would decide to do, it was tough for Han Xiao to judge. After all, the era and environment had changed.

During Dylan's era, as there were no prior examples, the Super Star Cluster civilizations were still openly competing for Beyond Grade A allies with the three Universal Civilizations and trying to attract them using better terms. At that time, joining the Super Star Cluster civilizations was the norm. No one thought the Tragedy of the Pinnacles would happen.

Han Xiao curled his lips, ignored him, looked away, and said to everyone, "I know everyone still has a lot of questions, such as who we are, how and why we revived you guys, and so on. For these questions, my friend here will answer them one by one."

Hearing this, Oathkeeper stepped up and said with a deep voice, "Everyone, we're a secret organization named the Holy Accord. We were founded by some of the Primordial Ones during the exploration era. Our core goal was to revive in the future. As for how we revived you guys, it's through a phenomenon called a Sanctum…"

Oathkeeper had prepared the script long ago and explained Holy Accord's origin and purpose in detail, answering everyone's doubts.

The Primordial Ones were famous. The revivors sized up the Holy Accord members present and realized that they were indeed the Primordial Ones recorded in history. They started to gradually believe what Oathkeeper was saying.

This time, someone looked at Han Xiao and said, "Who is he then? He's not one of the Primordial Ones,"

The rest looked over too.

Hearing this, Han Xiao straightened his shirt.

"You guys can call me Black Star. I'm the leader of the Beyond Grade As of this era."

As soon as he said that, everyone's expression changed.

Leader of Beyond Grade As?

How arrogant!

In our eras, even the strongest Beyond Grade As did not dare to call themselves the leaders of the Beyond Grade As. Who are you again? How dare you give yourself such a title!

Oathkeeper coughed and said, "Let me introduce you. His Excellency Black Star isn't a member of the Holy Accord but our crucial partner in this era. We have the same goals. In this era, the Beyond Grade As have already founded an association and united, and Black Star is the president of that Beyond Grade A Association. Plus, his strength is also at the top tier in the universe. At the same time, he's also the only shared consultant of the three Universal Civilizations. He has an extraordinary position…"

After hearing the explanation, everyone looked shocked and could not help but keep sizing Han Xiao up.

Beyond Grade A Association president, consultant of the three Universal Civilizations… Those titles had never existed before. Although they did not know the details yet, just from these titles, they could feel Han Xiao's influence.

Thinking back of the Energy Rank Han Xiao had just displayed earlier, the majority of people started to take him seriously and remembered the name Black Star.

To think that such an incredible youngster appeared in the 'future', this Black Star guy might have had the best time out of all the Beyond Grade As in history…

This time, a revived peak Beyond Grade A coldly said, "How strong you are is your business. All I want to know is, you didn't revive us to accompany you to play Wayne Card, did you? Or are you planning to use us to help you achieve some kind of ambitious goal, like the classic 'rule the universe'?"

Han Xiao shook his head and chuckled. "That's funny. The Holy Accord organization and I disturbed all of your rest not out of personal ambition. The entire Beyond Grade A class is in urgent danger, and we need our seniors, your strength!"

As soon as this was said, many people felt honored and interested right away.

"Tell us more. What danger are the Beyond Grade As in?" someone else asked curiously.

"It's still related to the three Universal Civilizations…"

Han Xiao spoke fluently and explained the crucial problems such as the unity of the Beyond Grade A Association, the stand of the three Universal Civilizations, what the Sanctum Revival meant for both sides, and so on. He did his best to explain the intense situation the Beyond Grade As were in now as simply as possible.

Seeing that they were thinking about his words, Han Xiao added, "If this problem isn't dealt with properly, a second Tragedy of the Pinnacles will certainly happen to the Beyond Grade As!"

As soon as he said that, many people shook.

A lot of them were victims of the Tragedy of the Pinnacles. This term touched their soft spot.

Seeing this, Han Xiao quickly made use of the opportunity and said with a meaningful tone, "This is closely related to every one of you, not just a matter of this era. Even if you guys aren't willing to join us, you have to think about your own interests.

"You guys have already died once and been revived. You definitely want to continue enjoying your lives. However, if this problem isn't dealt with, you won't be able to ensure your own safety. There's only one chance for Sanctum Revival, so if we don't unite and the second Tragedy of the Pinnacles breaks out, you guys will be in danger too. If killed again, your lives will really end this time."

Han Xiao deliberately hid the secret that the Sanctums could revive them an unlimited number of times and claimed that they only had one chance. By doing that, he became tremendously more convincing.

Hearing this, everyone understood the situation and looked serious.

Dylan rubbed his chin and said, "If that's the case, there are only two paths in front of us. Join the Beyond Grade A Association or stay in the Holy Accord, one or the other. There's no other choice."

Someone on the side frowned and asked, "Can't we leave on our own?"

Dylan glanced at him with disdain and said, "Use the few brain cells you have and think about it. Given how important the information about the Sanctum Revival is, do you think they'd let someone who knows about it move around freely? Idiot, no wonder you got killed."

This person's expression froze, and he angrily said, "Didn't you die too?"

"You don't understand. I died strategically!" Dylan snorted.

The others were bewildered.

What a f*cking creative way to describe it.

However, being weird was one thing, but they had to admit what Dylan said made sense.

There were only two choices. If they wanted freedom as soon as possible, they had to join the Beyond Grade A Association and let the galactic society, especially the three Universal Civilizations, know about their existence. This way, they would be tied with the Beyond Grade A Association.

If they chose to stay in the Holy Accord, no one would know about their existence. Even if the 'cleansing' happened, they would not be at risk.

Safety or freedom, there was no third choice… If they thought about secretly sneaking away, they would most likely end up back in their coffins.

They were in a dilemma.

Most people preferred to hide in the Holy Accord; they would lose freedom for some time, but it was better than losing their only second life. If the Beyond Grade A Association's hard work paid off, they could enjoy the fruits of victory. If the association failed, they would still be safe.

Han Xiao saw their hesitation. Knowing that what he said was effective, he was secretly glad.

However, this time, an untimely voice suddenly sounded in the crowd.

"Why do we have to accept such restrictive terms? Everyone, there are many of them, but we aren't few in number either. Why don't we work together for the time being, get out of this place? They can't stop all of us. Everyone will be free that way!"

As soon as this provocative idea was brought up, the expressions of many revivors changed.

Han Xiao's expression sank. He looked toward the source of the voice.

"Well, I really thought the problem would be solved smoothly, but it seems some people's mindsets need to be adjusted physically."

Chapter 1257: Intimidation

The people looked in the direction the voice came from and saw that it was a large male who spoke. He had dark skin and wild gray hair like the mane of a lion, standing with his arms crossed and staring right at Han Xiao with a cold expression.

"Oh? Is that what you think?"

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes and looked at him. This person's information surfaced in his mind.

'Fist of Polar Channel' Bagnita. He was an extremely strong Pugilist with an explosive, aggressive, and destructive style. The founder of multiple Pugilist styles, he was an expert in the Polar Channel Flow. Although he was not the founder of the Polar Channel Flow, he was publicly recognized as the best in the Polar Channel Flow style.

This guy was not from the Tragedy of the Pinnacles but was a neutral Beyond Grade A from even earlier. His cause of death was unknown, and he left his race behind.

Bagnita wore a sleeveless army combat shirt. The muscles on his arm jumped as he said coldly, "I hate it the most when people give me a multiple-choice question. Whether I help you or not depends on my mood. If you're going to force me, there's absolutely nothing to talk about!"

"People with a unique personality usually don't live long." Dylan sneered.

Hearing this, the others looked at him and nodded in agreement.

Bagnita ignored him, looked around, and said with a deep voice, "We're all Beyond Grade As. What's there to be afraid of? Those with a backbone, stand with me!"

Han Xiao shook his head and realized that he was surprisingly calm, as if he was used to it. In fact, it might feel weird if a Pugilist who was not headstrong appeared.

He turned and looked at the revivors. With a shrug, he said, "Who else agrees with him? You can step forward."

The people exchanged looks and hesitated; no one responded. Instead, they backed away and isolated Bagnita.

Seeing this, Bagnita frowned, snorted, and said, "Humph, the Beyond Grade As are getting more cowardly with each generation!"

Dylan tutted and mocked him. "Hehe, you're trying to provoke us to risk our life to play with you. If a fight really breaks out, you can probably walk out alive. You won't be the one to die anyway. Just say it out loud if you want others to block bullets for you. We're all Beyond Grade As here. Who are you putting up a performance for?"

Bagnita glanced at Dylan and said with disdain, "Idiot."

Seeing this, Han Xiao looked back at Bagnita, raised his brow, and said, "Looks like you're the only one. Do you still want to continue?"

"No one dares work with me. What else can I say?"

Bagnita snorted and put down his crossed arms.

Han Xiao could not help but laugh and said, "Aren't you smart, but don't you think you're too naive? You tried to incite the other revivors, but when you saw it can't be done, you gave up and wanted to act as if nothing happened. Do you really think it's going to be that easy?"

Bagnita frowned, tightened his arm muscles again, and said, "What do you want?"

Han Xiao slowly walked forward into the revivors toward Bagnita while saying, "I revived you guys because it's beneficial for the entire class, not for charity. I have already explained the situation very clearly earlier. We're on the same boat here… Still, I never thought about sacrificing you guys. I didn't even force you guys to take any risks and gave you all a choice to stay in the Holy Accord and watch us fight hard for our future. If we win, you guys can enjoy the victory together. If we lose, you guys can still stay hidden and save yourselves.

"You cannot appreciate us giving you a second life, but you were willing to destroy our whole plan just for your own desire… Of course, you're free to do that. But since you've done it, don't blame others for dealing with you."

As soon as he said that, a sudden change occurred!

Raging energy erupted, covered with blinding Pugilist flames. Bagnita's fist landed heavily on Han Xiao's chest like an asteroid!

Boom!

"You knew I'm a Pugilist, yet you still dared approach me. You're asking for a beating!"

This thought flashed past Bagnita's mind. There was no way he was going to wait and do nothing. Seeing Han Xiao's words were heading toward a dangerous direction, he immediately decided to strike first.

The next moment, the power of the punch exploded. Dense Pugilist flames gushed out from Han Xiao's back, turning into a cylinder-shaped energy shockwave that created an enormous hole in the room.

Boom!

A blinding beam of light shot out from this galactic base as if an explosion occurred inside.

In the room, the people were surprised to see how decisive Bagnita was in attacking. Some wanted to help while others wanted to back away and watch.

However, before they acted, they saw that Han Xiao, who had just been punched heavily, did not even shake. It was as if nothing happened to him. In the blink of an eye, Han Xiao's hands grabbed onto Bagnita's head and he raised his leg!

Bang!

Bagnita shockingly could not resist such an enormous force at the time. His head was dragged down and intimately hit Han Xiao's knee. Blood gushed out from his nose, and his brain trembled.

Before he recovered from the short moment he was stunned, Han Xiao wrapped his one hand around Bagnita's head and locked him in place, while the elbow of his other hand slashed down on Bagnita's arched back.

Kacha!

The sound of bone breaking appeared in everyone's ears, and a visible dent appeared on Bagnita's spine.

Hiss!

Many people inhaled with shock. The looks in their eyes changed again.

Taking one powerful attack head-on just to heavily injure the opponent in exchange… we won't believe it even if you tell us he's not a Pugilist!

At this time, Bagnita finally recovered from the short moment he was stunned. He roared, and the flames on his body erupted again. His muscles bulked up. A dense energy spread instantly, and his attributes shot up in a flash.

Then, Bagnita grabbed Han Xiao by his waist, kicked back with his legs at full power, and pushed Han Xiao through metal walls one after another. They shot out into space like an asteroid.

"That's Polar Channel Flow!"

The people instantly figured out what happened.

Relying on the explosive power of the Polar Channel Flow, the combat capability of Pugilists could usually shoot up a small Grade. As the publicly known master in the Polar Channel Flow, its effect on Bagnita was even more incredible. Plus, with his personal improvements on it, its side effects were very limited.

Bagnita was not a peak Beyond Grade A on his own, but with his explosive power, he was more than capable of fighting a peak Beyond Grade A and earning himself the name of 'Fist of Polar Channel'. In the revivors' eyes, he was very strong.

Although they had just felt how strong Han Xiao's Energy Rank was not long ago, they had never seen Black Star in combat and did not have a clear idea of it.

Since there was an opportunity now, the revivors did not help anyone, nor did they stop them—they all wanted to observe Black Star's strength in combat.

Most Beyond Grade As were proud, all of them wanted to see how strong this so-called 'leader of Beyond Grade As' was and what gave him the confidence to call himself that.

The revivors were initially expecting a marvelous fist fight, but the change that happened in the next second took them by complete surprise.

Han Xiao locked his hands around Bagnita too. Right after that, Mechanical Force erupted from all over his body. At the same time, countless mechanical soldiers swarmed out from the galactic base, shrouding the sky, and instantly fired at the two of them!

Boom!

Like a newborn Fixed Star, the expanding energy light sphere lighted up the cosmic space!

As the aftershock of the explosion spread, the protective shield of the galactic shield was activated automatically, barely blocking it out. The entire base was pushed out while heavily shaking.

The sudden blinding light made everyone narrow their eyes subconsciously. They all looked surprised.

"Did the two of them both die?"

"What a violent style of fighting."

"By the way, Black Star is a Mechanic? From his body strength, he's a total Pugilist!"

The people unavoidably started to worry and looked around. However, they realized that the Holy Accord members all looked very calmed and did not seem to be worried at all.

"Are you guys not worried for the safety of your partner?" someone asked.

Beiger turned, glanced at these people, and smiled. "Hehe, something that can kill Black Star probably doesn't exist!"

At this time, the light gradually started dissipating. Two closely attached people flew out from the center of the explosion, quickly headed to the base, and returned to the room through the hole.

Plop!

The sound of someone collapsing sounded. Bagnita lay on the ground like a dead dog; almost not a single spot on his body was whole. He was heavily injured and extremely close to death.

Shocked, the people looked up and saw that although Han Xiao was also wounded, his wounds were regenerating at an unbelievable speed, and Han Xiao returned to normal almost instantly. Han Xiao was the one who had brought Bagnita back.

With a calm face, Han Xiao gestured at Oathkeeper with his mouth.

"Take care of his injuries. Don't let him die."

The Holy Accord members were not surprised at all. A few of them walked forward and flipped Bagnita's body over a few times while spraying regenerative potion on him. It somehow looked like brushing sauce on barbequed meat.

Seeing this, the revivors could hardly believe their own eyes.

That's it?

Did the fight even take three minutes‽

They were expecting an intense huge battle. None of them ever thought Black Star would thrash Bagnita so quickly.

Bagnita was no trash Beyond Grade A but a famous Beyond Grade A!

They already knew that Black Star might be very strong, but they had never thought he would be this strong. It completely surpassed their experience-based expectations!

No wonder he dares call himself the 'leader of the Beyond Grade As'. He's indeed qualified for that…

This thought flashed through the minds of many of them.

Han Xiao stretched his neck and the muscles that felt a little sore from the bombardment massage earlier. He turned and saw the stronger fear in everyone's eyes and nodded internally. He was quite satisfied with the impact of this battle.

He was not actually angry. He scolded Bagnita only to intimidate the others.

This was because he knew that there were definitely more people who had the same thoughts as Bagnita who only did not dare respond because of the situation they were in. In order to get rid of such thoughts, making them afraid of doing anything by just outnumbering them was not enough. He had to make them feel the huge difference in individual strength. To that end, showing them then and there was the most effective method.

The best way to intimidate them was to crush Bagnita in a short time.

Therefore, Han Xiao deliberately displayed his intention of wanting to attack Bagnita while going closer to him at the same time. He did all that so Bagnita would fight him at close-range, which would make using 'die together' easier. After all, this combo was the most efficient way of defeating an opponent in a short time!

The biggest advantage he had was the amount of information he had. Anyone who knew about him well would never get close to him, but these revivors did not know about that yet. Therefore, based on his outdated experience, Bagnita did not give up on this 'opportunity' and fought him at close range right away, completely falling into Han Xiao's trap.

The moment Bagnita chose to fight him at close-range, the ending of this battle was already decided.

The effects of crushing Bagnita reached Han Xiao's expectations, shocking the fragile hearts of these people. There was only one more step to take.

Seeing that Bagnita's body was gradually recovering, Han Xiao took out the Spacetime Amber and wrapped Bagnita up. He then said coldly, "I won't kill him, but in order to avoid uncertainties, I shall ground him so that he calms down."

The next moment, the Spacetime Amber formed around Bagnita. His body was fixed inside the amber.

"What's this?"

The people were confused. The Holy Accord members on the side explained.

Very soon, everyone present understood the function of the Spacetime Amber. They all looked shocked and scared—this thing was almost the nemesis of Beyond Grade As.

This time, Han Xiao turned to them and smiled brightly.

"The person who brought up the question has already been dealt with. So, everyone, have you made your choice?"

Their looks differed. Some were smiling bitterly, while some were swallowing their saliva nervously.

There was no suspense to what choice they were going to make.

"… I'm willing to stay in the Holy Accord."

"Me too."

With someone taking the lead, the rest all responded one after another.

Between the two choices, almost everyone chose to stay in the Holy Accord organization. They did not want to appear in the outside world, at least not before they understood the whole picture clearly, so they did not have to take risks.

Very soon, Dylan was the only one who had yet to express his choice.

Han Xiao looked over. "What about you? Are you staying in the Holy Accord or joining the association?"

Dylan caressed his smooth and white chin, snorted, and said, "I won't want to miss something this fun… I'll join the association! If we start fighting the three Universal Civilizations, count me in!"

Then, as if he felt he did not say enough, Dylan scanned at the other revivors present and snickered. "The books are right, cowardly and ordinary people are always the majority."

Hearing this, Han Xiao could not help but to look at Dylan again.

You really deserved to be slain. Even I want to…

Chapter 1258: Test and Welcome

He asked around. There were only a few people in the second batch of the revivors who were willing to join the association. Han Xiao memorized their names, looked at the Holy Accord members, and nodded.

"I'll leave the rest to you then. You guys usually don't have anything to do anyway. You should be fine helping the newcomers get used to this era, right?"

Beiger smiled and agreed on behalf of the others. "Don't worry, we're adept at this. We were just in need of new card-mates too."

Oathkeeper nodded subconsciously but then suddenly realized, Wait a minute, isn't this my organization? Why are you the one giving the orders?

"Er…" Oathkeeper was just about to speak.

However, before he could, Han Xiao clapped, interrupted him, and smiled.

"I'm glad we've come to an agreement. Let's get to familiarizing them with this era then."

The atmosphere in the place became calmer as he said that. The Holy Accord members led the others and left the room while chatting. Their voices gradually grew more distant.

Oathkeeper's lips twitched slightly.

I, the organization's leader, have been ignored? Don't I deserve some face‽

This time, Han Xiao walked over, patted Oathkeeper's shoulders, and said, "I'm afraid you're going to be busy for some time. These revivors are intimidated by me for the time being, but I can't keep an eye on them all the time. There'll definitely be someone who wants to sneak away. You have to monitor them closely but not too obviously, in case they get unhappy about it."

"Understood…" Oathkeeper coughed. "Ahem, I know what to do. You don't have to teach me."

Han Xiao smiled. He summoned a virtual screen and quickly made a list.

"This is a partial list of keys for the other Sanctums. You guys are the expert in this. It's best to keep collecting them. The more keys we have, the better."

"You found this in the Third Sanctum?" Oathkeeper looked surprised. "Why didn't I see it when I went in?"

"It might be because your authority level is too low…" Han Xiao shook his head and briefly explained authority levels. As for whether Oathkeeper kept it a secret deliberately or not, now was not the time to be concerned over such trivial matters.

"Alright, this way, opening the Sanctums in the future will be easier." Oathkeeper was glad.

Although the information recorded in the various Sanctums differed, the Sanctum revival function worked in all of them. Having the methods to open the other Sanctums meant that the Sanctum revival function could be carried out many times more.

Accepting the list, Oathkeeper paused and asked, "Have you decided on the timing for the first batch of revivors to appear in public?"

"Probably in the next few months." Han Xiao responded.

"After they appear, the attitudes of the three Universal Civilizations will change drastically. Are you ready?" Oathkeeper sounded worried.

No matter how mentally prepared he was beforehand, as the one who would start this storm, it was impossible for him not to worry. That was especially so when this was most certainly going to be a fuse to cause the structure of the universe to change dramatically, as well as the turning point for all Beyond Grade As. Its influence would be colossal; it might lead the future of the galactic society to a completely unknown direction. He was naturally nervous.

"I know what I'm doing. This is a step we must take. There's no need to worry so much."

Han Xiao smiled and patted his shoulder.

Oathkeeper frowned slightly and slowly said, "Also… we hid the truth about the Sanctums, making the others think that they can only revive once. This means that although the three Universal Civilizations will still be concerned, they most probably won't give up on the idea of the 'cleansing"… Are we really not going to share the truth about reviving?"

Han Xiao shook his head.

"It's okay. We have to hide this trump card for a while. Although letting this information out will make the three Universal Civilizations cautious, they might change their strategy because of it too. It's better to give them the wrong idea. After all, being able to revive an infinite number of times… will only be convincing when it actually happens. If the cleansing is really carried out, it won't be too late to reveal it then anyway. That way, not only will the three Universal Civilizations' strategy be disrupted, it would also be a surprise to those who died.

"Plus, fear is the lock of desire. If we tell the truth to the revivors now, it won't be easy to manage them anymore."

Oathkeeper sighed and said, "But you'll face too much pressure this way… You're the one who will bring the revivors into the association, so anyone would think you know the truth. The three Universal Civilizations will definitely target you. Will you be able to deal with it?"

"It's not a big problem. As soon as the association sees that the Sanctums can revive people, the Beyond Grade As will be united around me like never before. In addition, with my capability, forces, and the Underworld, it won't be a problem to stand against the three Universal Civilizations for the time being. That way, there'll be room for negotiation."

Han Xiao smiled and made Oathkeeper not so worried.

Oathkeeper nodded and said with a solemn tone, "As long as you got a plan. Anyway, whether we can walk under the sun in the future all depends on you."

…

The next day, Han Xiao went back to hosting the association and Kasuyi stepped down. Kasuyi contacted Han Xiao multiple times privately, trying to find out what Han Xiao acquired in this trip, but Han Xiao smoothly avoided the topic every time.

Reappearing again after going missing for four months did not attract too much attention. It was common for Beyond Grade As to travel, so the various organizations did not overthink about what Han Xiao had done while he was missing.

After waiting patiently for more than half a month, the three Universal Civilizations finally acted and sent Han Xiao a private meeting invitation.

"After observing for so long, they're finally on the move, huh…"

In his room, seeing the invitation notification on the communicator, Han Xiao focused and sat up straight.

He opened the network link in the invitation letter, and his remote projection entered the online conference room.

The next moment, he came to a secret conference room. The remote projections of the leaders of the federation, the dynasty, and the church were all already there.

"Black Star, you're here." The dynasty's ruler, Marbruce, smiled with his squarish face.

Han Xiao looked around, put on the signature smile of the eighth king of the Underworld, and said, "Your Excellencies, what can I do for you?"

"We haven't officially congratulated you for being elected as the Beyond Grade A Association president, congratulations." Marbruce nodded.

"Thanks." Han Xiao smiled. "It's all thanks to the support of the members."

"We have high hopes for you. You're more suited to lead the Beyond Grade A Association than Manison. We all agree that under your leadership, the Beyond Grade A Association will walk further on the right path…"

The few of them superficially praised each other as usual before getting to the main topic.

The federation president, Louis, stroked his moustache and said, "We've called you here today mainly because we need your help on a matter… The issue of the Beyond Grade A Association members privately spreading Ultimate Knowledges of the various classes has gone on too long. Manison deliberately allowed it when he was in office and ignored it. Now that you've become the president, we hope you can help settle this issue."

Han Xiao raised his brow. "I'll try, but I can't promise it'll work. After all, I can't possibly interfere with the private life of every member."

Knowing this was a perfunctory response, the church leader coughed and slowly said with a more serious tone, "Black Star, this issue is very important to us. This has lasted decades. We can't possibly allow it to continue. There's a limit to everything. We hope we can see the situation improve very soon."

"I'll do my best." Han Xiao maintained a smile and did not reject it. He was not surprised.

The three Universal Civilizations never opened up the restrictions on the spread of Ultimate Knowledges legally, so the association members could only spread it privately. This was an important factor to attracting new blood, so of course, Han Xiao was not going to agree. The three Universal Civilizations clearly knew that too. Part of the reason they still deliberately brought this matter up was to test his position as the new president, and the other part was most likely to set the path for the 'cleansing'.

If he rejected it, the three Universal Civilizations would have a justifiable reason to target the association. If the association compromised, the members would definitely be shaken. Arguments and split opinions would certainly happen too.

The three of them gave Han Xiao a meaningful look.

"We'll wait for your results then. You won't disappoint us, will you?"

"Of course. I've always believed in taking the win-win path; you guys know that." Han Xiao smiled. "If there's nothing else, I'll take my leave."

"Hmm, go do your stuff then."

Han Xiao made a simple gesture to bid farewell and hung up the communication.

When his remote projection in the room disappeared, the three leaders remaining in the room looked at each other, nodded, and came to an agreement.

"Looks like it's time to take action."

Black Star replacing the Mechanic Emperor and taking office was the opportunity to act. This was because, to them, the biggest difference between Black Star and Mechanic Emperor was that Black Star knew all too well about avoiding conflicts, unlike the Mechanic Emperor, who was very headstrong. The chance of Black Star flipping the table was very low. This was one of the reasons they waited to act till Han Xiao took office—the personality of the leader was very important.

The three of them did not plan to target Black Star. Their plan was to kill some and poach some. Peak Beyond Grade As were not the three Universal Civilizations' targets. Instead, they were even going to compensate and woo them during the operation so that they could divide the Beyond Grade As.

According to the personality analysis based on their large databases, Black Star's predisposition to seek profit and avoid conflict was extremely strong. In order to protect his own interests, there was only a very small chance he would stand on the complete opposite side of the three Universal Civilizations for the other Beyond Grade As. As long as the operation was firm and cruel enough, Black Star would very likely step back to protect himself, which would give them an opportunity to divide the association.

The most ideal result would be the Beyond Grade A Association disbanding, fundamental and medium level members all dying, and most uncertainties eliminated, leaving only their direct members and the peak Beyond Grade As. This way, the three Universal Civilizations would once again gain control of the individuals with great strength, and everything would go back to how it was.

When the three of them were discussing the plan, inside Han Xiao's office in the Black Star Army, he put down the communicator and mumbled, "The situation is about to reach the tipping point, looks like it's time to bring the revivors out… there just happened to be a new member requesting to join the association recently, I can use the opportunity to announce their existence to the entire universe."

…

Half a month later, at Beyond Grade A Association headquarters on Planet Finn, a small fleet slowly docked.

In front of the porthole at the bridge of the main ship, a skinny man looked out the porthole at Planet Finn.

"The Beyond Grade A Association finally accepted my request…"

Mahel was relieved, like heavy weights were lifted off his shoulders.

He was a new Beyond Grade A who stepped into this territory a few years ago, raised by a certain Star System civilization. Although the chances of this happening were extremely low, it was not completely impossible. Some civilizations would get unbelievably lucky once in a while.

As the one and only Beyond Grade A of the civilization, Mahel carried heavy responsibilities. After he stepped into the Beyond Grade A territory, he became the guardian of his civilization, earning benefits for his civilization and stabilizing its forces in the local area. He did not join the Beyond Grade A Association as soon as he became a Beyond Grade A, but he also rejected the offers of the other civilizations.

He had only just requested to join the association, and he had come with a mission. He hoped to gain a hold inside the Beyond Grade A Association and bring more benefits to his civilization using the resources of other members.

Today was the welcome meeting the association hosted just for him. Mahel had made a lot of preparations for today. He even hired professionals to draft a script for his speech. He had memorized it and planned to earn the favorability of other members using this nice speech so that he could quickly blend in.

"Hope everything goes smoothly…"

The spaceship stopped at the dock. Mahel walked out and followed the receptionist into the temporary lounge of the venue. On the way, he kept rehearsing the speech he would give later on.

Very soon, Mahel came to the door of the lounge, pushed the door open, and walked in. He subconsciously looked around and was suddenly stunned.

In the room, dozens of people stood and sat around while casually chatting. Hearing someone had pushed the door open, they all stopped chatting and looked at him.

"Isn't the temporary lounge for one? Did I enter the wrong room?"

Mahel was stunned for a moment. He took a step back, looked at the room number, and was confused.

I'm not wrong. This is the lounge for the rookie to wait to enter the venue. Isn't this supposed to be my room? Where did these people come from?

At this time, the people inside the room suddenly started laughing. The people near the gate stood up, pulled Mahel in, and pressed him down on the sofa.

"Yo, finally, a real rookie is here."

"Sit, sit, get something to eat."

"This is the first time I've seen a rookie of the new era."

The others all crowded around and sized him up curiously while chatting.

Mahel was stuck in the middle with no idea of what to do. He could not take it anymore and yelled, "Who are you? This should be my room. Please get out!"

Hearing this, the others exchanged looks and smiled. Suddenly, everyone's body shook.

Boom!

The presence of Beyond Grade As erupted in an instant and disappeared the next second.

Mahel was startled. He froze in place and was totally dumbfounded.

All these strangers are Beyond Grade As‽

"W-who are you peop…"

Mahel's eyes opened wide. His brain was short-circuiting, and he could not even speak properly.

Beiger joked, "Don't be so nervous. We're just like you, all rookies joining the association."

"Impossible! How can dozens of new Beyond Grade As appear in the universe silently‽ Who are you guys‽"

Mahel stood up and lost it.

Isn't today's welcome meeting to welcome just me‽

Beiger smiled and waved. "We're not strangers. Take a closer look, do you recognize us?"

Hearing this, Mahel hastily observed the people present. Suddenly, his expression changed drastically.

"I've seen your information… you're Primordial Ones‽"

"Haha, I knew you would recognize us… Come on, don't look at us like that. We just simply revived. It's no big deal."

Beiger patted Mahel's shoulder with a smile.

As if his bones were shattered, Mahel lay flat on the sofa with no color in his eyes like he had lost his soul.

At this moment, his brain was completely blank. There was only one thought left in his mind…

When did I fall asleep?

Chapter 1259: Youngsters, Times Have Changed!

While Mahel was doubting the meaning of his life, in the venue a few corridors away, the remote projections of Beyond Grade A members appeared on their seats and chitchatted.

"Another welcome meeting today? The last rookie was Aurora, and that was only about half a year ago."

"I don't know if you guys noticed, but the frequency of new Beyond Grade As in the past few decades seems to have increased quite a bit compared to before."

"Indeed. I remember that very long ago, just three of four Beyond Grade As appearing in a few decades was already quite a lot, yet there have already been eight new Beyond Grade As in the past few decades. Although this kind of thing is very random, it does prove that the times are evolving."

"That's right. The population in the galactic society is increasing, the study of the Super system has been improving, and the Beyond Grade A seeds have been reaching their tipping points. There's going to be a period with many new Beyond Grade As."

The time before the meeting started was always for the members to chat and bond. They chatted casually, and it was boisterous.

Han Xiao's projection sat in the main seat and looked at this peaceful scene with a smile.

Looking at how clueless everyone was, Han Xiao smirked slightly… These people had no idea that something huge was about to happen that would change the structure of the entire universe.

At this time, someone suddenly brought up a topic related to Han Xiao.

"I received the Federation of Light's warning a few days ago, strictly prohibiting me from privately spreading Ultimate Knowledges. Your Excellency Black Star, did you know about this?"

Hearing this, many people added their input and expressed that they had received the same warning from the three Universal Civilizations. They all looked at Han Xiao.

Han Xiao glanced at the three Universal Civilizations' direct members, nodded, and said, "I spoke with the leaders of the three Universal Civilizations not long ago. They hope I can solve the issue of privately spreading Ultimate Knowledges."

"And what did you say?' Manison asked.

"The three Universal Civilizations maintain the laws of the galactic civilization. I'll do my best to cooperate with their work without affecting the operations of the association." Han Xiao gave a meaningless answer with a smile.

Manison snorted softly. He knew that given how smooth Han Xiao was, he would not directly reject the three Universal Civilizations and would most likely agree verbally.

This time, a direct member said, "How do you plan to solve this problem?"

"I haven't decided. Do you have any advice?" Han Xiao turned and looked at him.

"I think that one of the reasons the private spread of Ultimate Knowledges is happening is that the statute of the association is too lenient and did not clearly forbid it. I suggest improving the statute and heavily punishing those who disobey…"

While this direct member spoke, the other association members all shut up and exchanged looks.

The interests of the direct members of the three Universal Civilizations were different from normal Beyond Grade As. The two sides were the two most clear-cut factions. As the three Universal Civilizations became more and more dissatisfied with the acts of the Beyond Grade A Association, the conflict between the two factions grew stronger. People had already secretly proposed to Han Xiao to kick the direct members of the three Universal Civilizations out of the association more than once.

Han Xiao listened to the direct member for a while. He suddenly interrupted him and said with a smile,

"These suggestions are all not bad. I'll consider them carefully. Let's leave this topic to the next plenary. Today is the welcome meeting, after all. We shouldn't overstep our bounds."

He skipped this topic casually with a meaningful tone.

This direct member Beyond Grade A's heart sank. He understood Han Xiao's subtle warning and had no choice but to sit down reluctantly.

The other Beyond Grade As, however, were excited… 'Shouldn't overstep our bounds' was a warning to the direct members of the three Universal Civilizations, telling them not to forget who the master of the association was and not to think the three Universal Civilizations could give them orders.

With Han Xiao's subtle response, many people felt more at ease. As Black Star was quite closely related to the three Universal Civilizations, some people never stopped worrying about Black Star changing from taking the firm path like the Mechanic Emperor to compromising with the three Universal Civilizations.

Seeing this, Kasuyi helped to calm the atmosphere and said, "The president is right. We're gathered here today to welcome the rookie. Let's not talk business."

Hearing Kasuyi, the atmosphere became joyful again. The people skipped over this topic and started guessing the identity of this new rookie. Some even set up bets.

After discussing it for a while, someone looked to Han Xiao again and joked, "President, the rookie of this time should be Mahel, right? It's not going to be another new Beyond Grade A officer from the Black Star Army, is it?"

Han Xiao raised his brow, with a smile that was unlike a smile on his face.

"All I can say is… everyone is definitely familiar with them."

The people chatted while waiting. After some time, everyone was finally present.

Seeing this, Han Xiao raised his hand, signaling everyone to quiet down. "It's about time. The welcome meeting can start now. Let's remain quiet and get ready to welcome the rookie."

Hearing this, everyone became silent, turned around, and looked at the side gate of the room. According to the routine, the rookie always walked out from here.

Not long after, the side gate was finally pushed open. Mahel walked out and appeared in front of everyone.

The people started softly discussing right away.

"I knew it. It is indeed Mahel."

"Haha, I guessed right. Give me my money."

"Hmm? Why does he look weird?"

They sized up Mahel and realized that something was off right away. Mahel's eyes were out of focus as if his spirit was not here, and he was frozen.

"What's he doing standing there and not coming here?"

"Why isn't he saying anything? He's not mute, is he?"

They were confused.

At this time, another person walked out from behind the gate, then another, and another… Very soon, dozens of people swarmed out and pushed Mahel aside.

"W-what's going on? Isn't today the welcome meeting?"

The people present were stunned and lost.

This time, Han Xiao smiled and slowly said, "Don't have to be surprised, these people are all rookies who will be joining the association today. Guys, let's welcome them."

As soon as he said that, everyone was bewildered.

You're not f*cking pulling my leg, are you?

Even the three Universal Civilizations' direct members on the side had their eyes wide open with shock.

There were no signs before today. They all thought today was an ordinary welcome meeting. None of them thought such a surprise would happen.

Every welcome meeting was hosted for just one person. When had the association ever accepted so many rookies at once?

Plus, when did so many new Beyond Grade As appear in the universe? There were as many of them as a third of the association! It was completely impossible!

What festival is it today? Is the president joking with us?

He must be.

While these thoughts flashed past their minds, they subconsciously sized up these dozens of 'rookies'. Suddenly, their bodies shook.

"Wait a minute, these people look so familiar!"

"Are they… Primordial Ones‽"

"How is that possible? The Primordial Ones died centuries ago. They must have purposely dressed up this way!"

"Aiyo, they really look the same. Their disguise is amazing!"

The people hastily searched for the information of the Primordial Ones online and matched with the revivors present. They were all surprised.

Manison looked at Han Xiao with a frown and asked with a deep voice, "What's the meaning of this? Finding a group of people to disguise themselves as Primordial Ones and even letting them join the association. What is this nonsense‽"

"You think it's fake too?"

Han Xiao glanced at him and was not surprised. After all, to those who did not know about it, this was way too unbelievable. Anyone normal would doubt it.

He slowly stood up and looked around. His grin grew bigger as he said firmly, "I know you all have doubts, but these people are none other than the Beyond Grade As who existed in history. They have awakened from the river of time, revived, and decided to join the association to shine for the Beyond Grade A class!"

As he said that, the venue became dead silent.

Everyone present was completely dumbfounded.

That was, everyone except Kasuyi, who was shivering with excitement. He was the only other person who knew about the Sanctums, and he immediately linked them.

Is this what Black Star did when he went missing for four months‽

"…Tell me, is this true?" Kasuyi turned and stared at Han Xiao. He could not wait to hear the answer, afraid that this was just a joke.

Han Xiao gave him a firm look and said slowly, "On my honor, I hereby promise that this is not a joke!"

At this instant, joy, shock, admiration, and other emotions exploded in Kasuyi's heart!

He only had one thought in his mind…

Black Star… did it!

At this time, Beiger, who stood at the front, chuckled. He stepped up, facing everyone's shocked looks, and said calmly, "Youngsters, times… have changed!"

As soon as he said that, the energy of dozens of Beyond Grade As shot up the sky without holding back!

Boom!

With a loud noise, the rooftop of the entire venue was blown away. The floor and walls cracked!

The enormous pressure swept the entire planet. At this instant, all lives on Planet Finn were pressed onto the floor almost simultaneously. Deafening alarms echoed across the planet!

The Beyond Grade As present were all remote projections and could not feel the impact, but all of their organizations had an agency on Planet Finn.

Almost instantly, everyone received an emergency report from their agency. All of their radars were showing dozens of Beyond Grade A energy sources, coming from the dozens of people right in front of them! No evidence could be more solid!

At this instant, the expression of all the members present changed drastically. Their faces were filled with disbelief and aghast.

This is true? The Primordial Ones are alive‽

Impossible!

Everyone was dumbfounded!

An irresistible shock instantly shattered their view of the world, leaving only endless confusion.

At this point, almost no word could describe the shock they were feeling.

Even Manison was stunned for a few seconds. He turned around hastily and stared at Han Xiao.

"What in the world did you do? How did they revive‽"

Like waking up from a dream, eyes filled with disbelief focused on Han Xiao.

These revivors were all brought into the association by Black Star. He definitely knew all about how this happened!

"Black Star, how the hell did this happen‽"

"Answer us!"

"Speak!"

The people were in an uproar, wanting to know the answers.

Seeing how worked up everyone was, Han Xiao smiled and said calmly, "In this world, there's a special information form phenomenon named the Sanctum Revival. Once you step into the Beyond Grade A territory, you will leave a set of backup data. Even if you die and leave absolutely nothing behind, not even ashes, you can still be revived through the Sanctum Revival.

"This will only happen once for everyone, meaning all Beyond Grade As have a second life… and using this phenomenon is how I revived them from their graves in history!"

Having received a clear answer, everyone was astonished.

The shock and jubilation exploded in everyone's mind!

There's such a mysterious phenomenon that only works on Beyond Grade As in the universe? Is this another Space Wonder‽

Everyone realized that this was a gift to all Beyond Grade As!

If they had heard about this from someone else, they would most likely have laughed at it and not believed it. Now, however, an example of it happening appeared right in front of them, proving what Han Xiao said was true.

The next second, the way everyone looked at Han Xiao changed.

Black Star had revived so many Primordial Ones, which meant that he already controlled the method of using it. He explained that it existed, but he never said anything about how to use the Sanctum Revival. Therefore, for now, Black Star was probably the only way they could enjoy the benefits of 'Sanctum Revival'‽

Thinking from another perspective, it had only been about half a year since Black Star became the president. Logically, he might have discovered the method of Sanctum Revival long ago and kept it hidden all this time if he did not become the president…

This moment, everyone felt that electing Black Star as the president was the wisest decision they could have made!

Han Xiao looked around at everyone's expression.

"Since everyone no longer has doubts, don't forget the subject of today's welcome meeting…"

Han Xiao raised his hand. The seats around the round table started moving, and rows of new seats extended from under the ground. These were for the revivors. Then, Han Xiao clapped his hands.

"Everyone, let's welcome the return of the old era."

Chapter 1260: Times Have Changed

Pa pa pa!

With Han Xiao in the lead, everyone could only suppress their inner shock and temporarily applaud. A feeling of witnessing history being made spontaneously rose in them.

However, the scene happening in their minds was probably akin to being robbed by a bunch of thugs while they were happily camping and feasting on hotpot in the wilds. This was too damned 'surprising'!

Seeing this, the dozens of Revivors smiled and took their seats one after another. Seeing Mahel standing stupidly on the same spot, some of the Primordial Ones kindly pulled this little brother to his seat as well.

The applause slowly stopped, and Han Xiao sat down once more before looking at Beiger and the others. "Everyone, would you like to introduce yourselves?"

"I feel that there's no need." Beiger waved his hand as he surveyed the scene. "If they want to know who we are, they just have to check up on our history."

Everyone subconsciously nodded. The Primordial Ones were all famous, so every Beyond Grade A would have heard their names before.

At this moment, Dylan raised his smooth chin slightly. "Although I'm not a Primordial One, I believe everyone here should also know of me, right?"

Everyone turned to face him. Among the Revivors, there were a few that were not Primordial Ones, so they were not as popular and well known as the rest.

"Who are you?" Sun Hunter was curious.

"Tsk, there's really someone who doesn't recognize me?" Dylan glanced at him. "Little thing, listen up. I'm the Elf King Dylan. Go home and brush up on your historical knowledge. Don't ask such ignorant questions next time."

Sun Hunter was stunned for a moment before turning furious.

Do you even know how to talk, to dare call me a little thing!

If it was not my remote projection here, I'd conjure dozens of gun barrels into your mouth and blow you to death!

On the other hand, many of the Mages felt a jolt in their spirits.

"So, it turns out to be the famous 'Elf King' from the history of magic. It's said that you took a different approach, pioneering a special elven spell system. Now it has become the mainstream magic system of the elves, but unfortunately, due to your sudden death, some of the mysteries and secrets have been lost forever. I hope I will have the opportunity to ask you for advice in the future."

Austin could not help but speak, showing his goodwill. A Mage's desire for spells was akin to the Mechanic's curiosity about technology.

Hearing this, Dylan instead lowered his head to pick at his nails before casually saying, "It'll depend on my mood. I normally do not like to converse with untalented Mages, but if my mood is good, I could share some information."

Austin's expression froze, and he shut up. Seeing this, the other Mages that wished to talk also closed their mouths, not wanting to flatter a non-responsive person.

Seeing this, many of them gave Dylan side-eyes.

It turns out that this person spoke with such a strange tone. No wonder he died so badly in history—he deserved it!

Seeing that the atmosphere had become a little delicate, Beiger moved away from the subject and smiled. "I have to say, this association is run well. During our time, there wasn't such a good environment. The people who established the association are really long-sight and talented!"

"I feel that way as well." Han Xiao smiled.

Hearing this, everyone glanced at Han Xiao and at Beiger, whose expressions remained unchanged.

These two were really shameless, one flattered so obviously, while the other was bold enough to accept it.

Beiger turned back to look at the rest as he spoke in a friendly manner. "We have many days ahead of us. I hope that we will have the chance to get to know each other better."

Everyone nodded and responded without putting on an arrogant expression. The Primordial Ones were the pioneers of this path, so respect was definitely needed.

The newcomer orientation finally returned to its original role. Both groups of people communicated with each other for a while, allowing the dozens of Revivors to integrate into the association. Even if the other members of the association felt this matter to be hard to believe, they had to accept the fact that these 'elderly' had risen from their coffins.

While the Revivors were accepted on the surface, everyone was still filled with doubts. They were very curious about how Black Star had discovered the phenomenon of Sanctum Revival, how he convinced the Revivors to join the association, and where they had stayed until now.

But Han Xiao behaved splendidly, lightly skimming past all these questions without properly explaining anything.

Everyone felt as though they had an itch in their hearts, their impression of Han Xiao turning more mysterious. They all began to feel awed by him. No one knew how much strength he had hidden, only feeling that he was unfathomable.

But precisely because of this, the rest of the Association felt relaxed. In the past, everyone obeyed the rules of the association for protection and resources, but another important reason had been added.

The Sanctum Revival gave everyone assurance. Originally, there were still some people worried about the three Universal Civilizations, counting gains and losses, but their mentality had now stabilized, their fear of the three Universal Civilizations diminishing significantly.

Just as everyone was busy chatting, Manison sat by the side silently observing, his heart full of shock.

Black Star, turns out this is the trump card you prepared. Beautiful! The Sanctum Revival is of extraordinary significance for us. Not only will this enhance the confidence of members in facing risks, but it also strengthens the cohesion of the association. The group will be more united than ever before.

Furthermore, the resurrection of the historical Beyond Grade As is a way to quickly replenish our numbers, more efficient than slowly wait for a new Beyond Grade A to be born. The strength of the association will expand greatly in a short time, being reborn and breaking through the safety line of the three Universal Civilizations at once. Even they will have to weigh up the consequences if they wish to make a move… With this, I don't have to risk launching the Intelligent Plague.

Manison sighed in his mind.

He had always been worried that Black Star's route of peace would form the basis of confidence for the three Universal Civilizations and was worried that the influence of Black Star alone would not be able to affect the determination of the three Universal Civilizations. However, it seemed now that Black Star's response was completely out of his expectations, allowing him to even be relieved of his hidden cards.

Manison had no choice but to admit that Black Star's move was far more effective than his plan of sacrificing eight hundred soldiers to wipe out a thousand of the enemy's soldiers.

While the two of them were typically at odds with each other, he acknowledged Han Xiao's ability and was quite relieved this time that he 'did not believe in the wrong person'.

On the other hand, Kasuyi glanced at Han Xiao from time to time, his favorability of him increasing.

Kasuyi was aware of most of the facts behind the Sanctum Revival and was probably the only person there other than Han Xiao who knew of the fact that there were no limits to the Sanctum Revivals. He was naturally more excited than anyone else.

He did not know why Han Xiao was pretending that there was only a single chance for the Sanctum Revivals, but after a little thought, he could guess the general intention and naturally would not expose it on the spot.

At this moment, Kasuyi could not help but feel fortunate.

Thankfully, my relationship with Black Star is not too bad. I've never offended him and even chose him as my companion to explore the Celestial Star Alliance. If it was someone else, even if they know the existence of the Sanctums, they would probably be just like me, having no clue even for the next few decades… I don't know how he even managed to master the Sanctum Revivals.

Kasuyi was unaware of the Holy Accord, so he thought that Han Xiao had gotten inspiration from their trip to the secondary dimensions. He secretly sighed to have found himself a reliable comrade.

While the majority of the association members were pleasantly surprised and excited, the descendants of the three Universal Civilizations had solemn expressions.

From a personal point of view, the Sanctum Revival was indeed a divine revelation for the Beyond Grade As, but from the perspective of the civilization, if the Beyond Grade A Association possessed such a method, it would be earth-shattering news for the direct descendants.

The Beyond Grade As now have an extra life, so unstable factors cannot be removed once and for all. This will be troublesome. Even if they can be cleansed once, the deceased will definitely learn how to be smart after reviving, turning to hide and plot their revenge in secret.

The core of this problem was Black Star. Only he had the means to perform a Sanctum Revival. Unless he was killed first, or the method of Sanctum Revival was obtained from him, it would be almost impossible to split the Beyond Grade A Association.

The direct descendants frowned as similar thoughts appeared in their minds.

They had more or less received the news that the three Universal Civilizations planned to attack the Beyond Grade A Association, but at this juncture, Black Star had revealed his true colors, deliberately exposing this method. In their opinion, this was undoubtedly a warning signal. The three Universal Civilizations would be frightened with this move, such that they would not act rashly.

Moreover, the high-end combat strength of the association had suddenly soared up by a third. Even if the upper echelons of the civilizations wished to carry out their plan, they also had to consider the issue of their costs.

For the entire Beyond A realm, he did not hesitate to take the pressure upon himself… This is not like Black Star's usual style.

Thinking of this, the eyes of the direct descendants looking at Han Xiao turned meaningful.

Han Xiao also noticed the gazes of these direct descendants, but his face was calm, and he secretly smiled.

The Calamity of the Supers was inevitable, and conflicts would eventually erupt. Right now, he had become the detonator of the Calamity of the Supers, but his fundamental goal had not changed. He had to find a way to keep the three Universal Civilizations in check, so as to control the intensity of the conflict during the Calamity of the Supers and save more strength to deal with the World Tree Civilization.

His other objective was for self-consideration. Only when the entire Grade was cohesive could his position be more stable.

I've finally taken this step. There's no retrieving a loosed arrow. I can only guide these torrential times, ceaselessly running forward…

All sorts of thoughts flashed past, and Han Xiao calmed down. He clapped his hands, interrupting the communication as he spoke.

"Now that everyone has gotten to know each other, there will be opportunities in the future to socialize. Let's stop here for today's welcome meeting. We'll discuss the resource allocation at the next regular meeting, helping our seniors rebuild their influence."

Everyone nodded without any objection.

There were a lot of Beyond Grade As, which would inevitably cause them to share a part of the profits. However, the existence of the Sanctums gave everyone the decision in their hearts to get closer to Han Xiao. His authority in the association had already expanded to the extreme.

"Alright, then let's end the meeting today."

Han Xiao smiled and directly cancelled his remote projection.

Seeing this, everyone dissipated on their own.

No matter what emotions they had, everyone was aware that the ecology of the Beyond Grade A realm would be rewritten. When what happened in the venue today was spread, the flow of the entire Galactic Society would be greatly affected. A storm of change was bound to rise from this point, sweeping across the entire universe!

The instigator of this whole thing was actually someone who had not shown himself for a few decades yet came out straight with a bang—Black Star!

Many Beyond Grade As had a feeling that Black Star would likely open the curtains to a new era!

…

The content of this welcome party was not kept secret. With the help of those people with certain intentions, the news spread faster than expected. It had already spread to all the major Star Fields by the next day, having countless media channels scrambling to write various reports.

When the many galactic residents and organizations saw the news, their first reaction was disbelief, thinking it some sort of fake news.

Could a Sanctum really resurrect a dead Beyond Grade A? The Primordial Ones who had been buried in history collectively came back to life?

Stop joking, okay. Even the TV studios would not dare to shoot stuff like this!

However, within a few days, the members of the Beyond Grade A Association personally confirmed the veracity of the news. The entire Galactic Society was confused!

This was really true‽

The historical figures from our textbooks are now alive‽

If I'm not insane, then the world must be insane!

The emotions of countless residents exploded!

Driven by panic, fanaticism, and shock, the news spread faster and faster. The Galactic Society, which had experienced calmness for decades, was once again thrown into a stormy sea.

Be it an ordinary person or Super, civilization or private organization, almost everyone could vaguely see a storm brewing at rapid speed.

The universe seemed to be heralding a change!

Chapter 1261: Response of the Three Universal Civilizations

Benefitting from the emergency report the direct Beyond Grade As had written after the meeting, the three Universal Civilizations had learned about the resurrection of the Primordial Ones even before public opinion broke out.

The moment this report was delivered to their tables, the leaders of the three civilizations were shocked, hurriedly convening a joint meeting.

In the conference room of the highest level, the projections of Marbruce, Louis, and the Pope sat on one end. Sitting around them were the upper echelons of each respective civilization that was eligible to participate in the conference. The core powers of the three Universal Civilizations had gathered together, and the atmosphere was solemn.

"Resurrecting the Beyond Grade As… Black Star unexpectedly had such an incredible method. He hid himself deeply and only came out in high profile at this point. He did this deliberately!"

Marbruce's expression was solemn, and he was frightened in his heart.

He had already tried to evaluate Black Star as highly as possible, but he did not expect to underestimate the other party so much. As part of the hawk faction with a strong desire to control, seeing Black Star pull out such a trump card that could stir the universe, his inner anger could not be quenched. He felt that this ally had already left the control of the dynasty.

Louis spoke in a deep voice. "Yes, Black Star has been planning this for a long time. He probably had an idea and was just waiting for an opportunity. Once he sensed the risk, he resolutely released this ace in the hole in order to disrupt our deployments!"

The Pope frowned. "This situation is unfavorable for us. With the return of the Primordial Ones, the top strength of the Beyond Grade A Association has expanded by at least a third. If we use the original plan to cleanse the Beyond Grade As, we will have to pay a higher price. This will shake the order of the entire interstellar society, not to mention that Black Star could possibly resurrect more of them…"

The mood of the trio was the same. Their plans had already entered the ready state, but this abrupt situation brought about by Black Star frightened them into stopping all their current actions and reconsidering countermeasures.

As Black Star was the source of the trouble, the goodwill of the trio toward him had disappeared, only leaving boundless hostility. Even if Black Star was nominally an ally of the dynasty, the Ruler Marbruce was also hostile toward him.

When the other party was beneficial to their own rule, they would cooperate with a smile even if they had a personal suspicion. However, Black Star's actions had broken the balance of the universe and were leveraging on the foundations of the three Universal Civilizations. His reputation and status could no longer prevent both sides from turning against each other.

From the perspective of the three, they had given Black Star so many benefits, only to see Black Star backstab them!

If it were not for the fear of Black Star's strength, influence, and connections, the trio might have convened their troops to smash the Black Star Army.

Marbruce suppressed his impulses, speaking in a low tone.

"It will be tricky in the short term but even more dangerous in the long run. Don't forget, many of the Beyond Grade As have some hatred with us, such as the civilization guardians that were destroyed by us during the exploration era, or even those who perished in the Tragedy of the Pinnacles… If they make a comeback, they're likely to retaliate against us!"

The upper echelons in the audience knew the seriousness of not removing the weeds from their roots, and they shuddered.

The three Universal Civilizations had many direct Beyond Grade As, but this number could not be compared with the number of enemies they had throughout history. Once their enemies were resurrected on a large scale, their direct Beyond Grade As were likely to be completely wiped out, resulting in the loss of their deterrence in the form of individual combat strength.

The best advantage of a Beyond Grade A was their ability as a strategic level weapon. They had unparalleled flexibility and were able to destroy the entire board with just a few people. If there were no direct Beyond Grade As on their side to restrain the other party, then even if the three Universal Civilizations could still wipe out the Beyond Grade As with their fleets, technology, and various Universal Treasures, they would have to pay a huge price to do so.

The pope thought further and solemnly said, "From the perspective of the overall situation, even if the factors of the enemy were not counted in, the dominance of the three Universal Civilizations is in danger of being flipped. The Sanctum Revival has increased the life expectancy of the Beyond Grade As, which will lead to a qualitative increase in accumulation for the Beyond Grade As in the universe.

"With this trend, the Beyond Grade A numbers will break through the balance between civilization and individual might in the near future, enough to threaten our rule. At that time, it will be hard for us to make a comeback. It will no longer be the Beyond Grade As worrying about us but rather us worrying when the ambitions of the Beyond Grade A Association will expand!"

The Pope sighed at this. He appeared resigned.

"But what's the use of knowing this? Black Star's trump card has completely destroyed all our checks and balances. He holds the remote control that could change this era. We can no longer act rashly!"

Hearing this, the trio fell silent.

This current situation was akin to nuclear deterrence, where the three Universal Civilizations did not dare shed all pretenses.

Even if a civilization was strong, facing such a situation, the trio felt helpless in face of this sudden situation. This naturally fueled their hate toward Han Xiao.

There seemed to only be one way to solve this… to obtain the authority to control the Sanctum Revivals!

"For the current strategy, we'll negotiate as much as possible with Black Star until we figure out his plan!"

The trio nodded, reaching a consensus while secretly regretting their past decisions.

When the stubborn Mechanic Emperor was leading the association, they did not act rashly but rather waited for Black Star to take that position. However, it seemed now that Black Star was even more dangerous than the Mechanic Emperor, being able to hide so deeply.

The route the Mechanic Emperor took was a polar opposite of Black Star. Black Star only wished to deter and co-exist, having little negative impacts and benefiting the Beyond Grade A Association. Compared to Manison's method of mutual destruction, the former's method was more inconsistent with the three Universal Civilizations.

If they had known this would happen, when the Beyond Grade A Association was first established, they would have…

Well, what's the use in regrets when it was not us at that time! What a mess our predecessors left us!

Marbruce could not help but think of the warning he had from Urranrell decades ago.

Beware of Black Star, he's a hundred times more dangerous than the Mechanic Emperor!

At this point, he could only utter a single word. "Indeed."

Without delay, the trio dispersed the meeting, sending an invitation and preparing for a secret conversation with Han Xiao.

The trio did not wait long, as Han Xiao descended quickly as a virtual projection.

"Your Excellencies, what a coincidence. We meet again."

Han Xiao still held the same attitude, bowing slightly with a smile on his face.

While his tone was the same, the three of them felt a faint hint of mockery within.

Marbruce suppressed his urge to strangle Han Xiao, solemnly saying, "Black Star, you must know why we have called you over. Long story short, what's happening with the Sanctum Revivals?"

Han Xiao blinked. "I'm not too sure myself either. I also only discovered this peculiar phenomenon by accident. This might be a Space Wonder."

The corners of the trio's mouths twitched.

Stop mentioning the phrase 'Space Wonder', my head hurts!

"Then what's the process of the Sanctum Revivals, and are there any rules of restrictions…" Louis continued.

"Ah, I'm not too sure of that either. I haven't started my research yet." Han Xiao waved his hands.

The Pope cleared his throat before speaking solemnly. "I don't know if you're intending to share the formula for Sanctum Revival, but you can name your price."

Han Xiao smiled.

Bruh, what are you smoking?

Seeing this, the trio knew that this request was outrageous and were secretly unhappy.

Marbruce gritted his teeth before bellowing, "Black Star! You should know what sort of chaos your Sanctum Revivals have brought to the Galactic Society. What's your intention by resurrecting this group of historical Beyond Grade As? What is your goal?"

Hearing this, Han Xiao only smiled. "Just like you said, I was only testing out if Sanctum Revival was even possible. I didn't expect to actually be able to resurrect this group of people. Should I stuff them back into their graves instead?"

Marbruce almost exploded in anger.

Accidental experiment? Only a fool would believe that!

The Pope took over the conversation. "Whether it was an accident or not, the Beyond Grade A Association now has to deal with a huge number of newcomers. We would like to know how you are going to deal with this problem."

What the trio worried about was that with this new force, Black Star would take initiative to attack.

"There's no need to deal with them. The moment they join the association, they are part of it, and they will not be given special treatment. I will only give them some resources in accordance with their established rules of the association. As for other matters… as long as they do not violate the regulations of the association, I will not care."

Han Xiao's attitude was to draw the line.

"This is not enough. You know our intentions. We hope that you will ensure that the Beyond Grade A Association will always exist in peace."

Han Xiao chuckled. "Even if I guarantee it, will you believe it?"

The trio helplessly shook their heads. In reality, the foundation of trust between both parties had already collapsed. Even if they believed in Black Star, their own duties required them to plan ahead and expect the worst. Any sort of guarantee was useless to them.

The trio did not dare take a sharp attitude when facing Black Star. While Black Star had a huge business, his main clients were the three Universal Civilizations. But things were now different. With the existence of the Sanctum Revival, Black Star had become a 'detonator', sitting on the same level as the heads of the three Universal Civilizations.

Marbruce squinted and suddenly asked, "Black Star, is the dynasty still your ally?"

Han Xiao gazed at him, thinking for a bit before asking, "The covenant has not been torn down. The dynasty had provided me with a lot of help, so of course we're still allies."

It was not in his interests to completely tear off all pretenses, nor did Han Xiao wish to do so.

Marbruce's eyes shone. "Then I wish to cooperate. Since you have the means of Sanctum Revival, I hope you can resurrect Gaud or the other dynasty descendants."

"… I'll think about it." Han Xiao raised his brows. He naturally would not resurrect the direct Beyond Grade As of the three Universal Civilizations.

Seeing this, the trio knew that they would not be able to get anything else from Han Xiao, so they could only hold back their dissatisfaction and end the call.

In the huge room, the trio gazed at each other, staring in silence for a while.

Marbruce was silent for a while before he spoke.

"The original cleansing plan can be abandoned. We need a new response plan, and I have three ideas. One is to start with Black Star, using spies to infiltrate and find a method to get into the Sanctum. Second would be to divide the association, winning over some of the Revivors to inquire about the Sanctum Revival. As for the third…"

As he spoke, he glanced at them, hesitating a little before he continued.

"We should establish our own R&D team to independently study the secrets of the Sanctum Revival. I believe that the federation and church are not completely ignorant of this, with some information on hand."

The other two were taken aback before slowly nodding as well.

The three Universal Civilizations came from the exploration era, naturally having some knowledge of the Sanctums. The direct descendants of the three Universal Civilizations would occasionally also obtain relevant inspiration and leave some vague information. Because of the rumors among the Primordial Ones as well, this was not the first time the three Universal Civilizations had heard of the term 'Sanctums'. However, they had treated this as unverifiable confidential information in the past.

Such information was a high-level secret of the three Universal Civilizations. They cherished such things deeply and just wished to research it on their own. However, due to the incomplete intelligence provided, their research had been progressing slowly without any clues. Most of the projects had long been suspended, and even the authenticity of the intelligence was questioned.

But with this situation now, where the ruling foundations of the three Universal Civilizations were threatened, Marbruce felt that this was not the time to hide and monopolize.

"I suggest that we pool and share our relevant secrets, put together our clues to study this so-called Sanctum Revival together. Only in this manner can we have a small chance of making quick progress!"

After a moment of hesitation, Louis nodded. "Seems like this is the best idea. Let's do it."

The Pope also nodded in agreement. "In the short term, the possibility of us solving this problem is very small, but in the long run, while we cannot prevent the resurrection of Beyond Grade As, it's not impossible to suppress the number.

"We cannot prevent the revivals, but we can also reduce the new Beyond Grade As and prevent them from growing endlessly!"

"You mean…"

The two of them started.

The Pope's eyes flickered with an inexplicable light as he whispered, "The birth of Beyond Grade As comes from the huge base of Supers in the universe. If we obliterate the potential Beyond Grade As, then the Super class will be cut off. If we even cut off the inheritance of Super knowledge at the bottom, nationalizing all of it, this will make the Beyond Grade As lose their fresh blood…"

Hearing this, both Marbruce and Louis felt their hearts jolt. They were unable to help feeling shocked at the Pope's bold declaration.

The Supers had always been an important part of the Galactic Society, but now he wanted to uproot them‽

With their insight, they felt that this idea was too insane.

But… if there were only advanced civilizations left in the universe that could train Supers, how stable would their public order be, and how strong would their ruling foundation also be?

They could not help but fantasize.

…

At the same time, in Black Star Palace, Han Xiao put away his communicator. Recalling the exchange between him and the three Universal Civilizations' leaders, he sighed lightly.

"The checks and balances have been formed. The three Universal Civilizations will give up on their cleansing plans for now, fearing repercussions of their actions. In this manner, the intensity of the Calamity of the Supers will be controlled, but I don't know… How long can this last?"

Han Xiao nodded.

The Revivors were born ahead of time, and the fact of Sanctum Revival was revealed. The butterfly effect he had brought would inevitably change the course of the Calamity of the Supers, not developing like his previous life.

But he could not say for sure to what extent the Calamity of the Supers would change, so he could only adapt to the circumstances.

Chapter 1262: Mechanical Divinity

"Even if we have not torn off all pretenses now, our relationship is basically frozen stiff."

Han Xiao stroked his chin as he pondered.

While the storyline had changed, he had predicted the actions of the three Universal Civilizations. The leaders had approached him for a secret talk, naturally with the intention of negotiating with him.

But Han Xiao did not plan to talk about it at all. The fundamental contradictions were already placed up front, so negotiations would be useless if that was not resolved.

The three Universal Civilizations wished to achieve the result of preventing him from resurrecting the Beyond Grade As in history at will. The Revivors had to first be screened by them, and the number could not exceed a certain value. In short, the Sanctum Revivals would be limited, in a way that best fit with the needs of the three Universal Civilizations.

Even if he were to compromise, as long as the three Universal Civilizations did not control the Sanctum Revival function, their behavior would not change. The foundation of trust had already been broken; nothing said now would be able to dispel their fear. This fundamental conflict of interest had already prevented both parties from reaching a consensus.

Han Xiao naturally did not want to tie up his hands and feet. Now that the checks and balance were established, there was nothing they could do even if Han Xiao did not wish to negotiate. That being said, he did not wish to further provoke the three Universal Civilizations.

Unless the three Universal Civilizations made a move, he did not intend to expose any new Beyond Grade As revived by the Holy Accord.

"The three Universal Civilizations could be said to have turned into our enemies. While they are not yet openly hostile, the business cooperation between us will be gradually lifted. Naturally, their resource support will also not be handed to me.

"Tsk, Marbruce has never been happy with me. It's only because of the deal signed between Urranrell and I that he has no choice but to continue to give me strong support. Now, he can finally terminate the cooperation in a fair way.

"However, I'm not the only one who is receiving this treatment. Except for the direct descendants and the allies who have not made a clear statement, it's difficult for anyone else to be able to continue cooperating with the three Universal Civilizations. It is necessary to enhance the independence of the association."

The nature of this wave caused by the Beyond Grade A Association had changed. The three Universal Civilizations would no longer continue their original intentions of killing their 'enemies' but would carry out non-armed conflict countermeasures such as economic sanctions.

With them taking the lead, a large number of affiliated civilizations would also terminate their cooperation with the Beyond Grade A organizations. If targeted policies were introduced, many of the interstellar consortiums would also choose to terminate their contracts with the Beyond Grade As. No matter how powerful the Beyond Grade As were, there was no way for them to develop their organizations without support, and Han Xiao did not doubt the influence of the three Universal Civilizations in this area. Free trade would turn into a political issue.

Because the three Universal Civilizations were hegemons, they did not care about losing this portion of cooperation, but for the Beyond Grade A organizations, it would be a significant dip in income. Many of their channels would be cut off, which would have a great impact.

This situation would cause the Super Star Cluster Alliance to take advantage of this vacancy and attempt to lure in the Beyond Grade As to replace the position of the three Universal Civilizations. However, the three Universal Civilizations were even more likely to turn toward the Super Star Cluster Alliance than to continue to cooperate with the Beyond Grade A Association.

Of course, even if the three Universal Civilizations were to take this route, they would not do it in a high-profile manner. This struggle would be out of sight of most galactic residents.

Such problems would not happen in the short term, but it was necessary for Han Xiao to establish an interest system for the Beyond Grade A Association that was independent from the three Universal Civilizations. The current interest system could only be regarded as a semi-complete product, needing further tuning.

"There are countless organizations contacting me these days to ask about the Sanctum Revivals. These are all resources that can be used."

Han Xiao scratched his chin thoughtfully.

For the ordinary citizens, while the Sanctum Revival was magical, it had little to do with them. Instead, it was the consortiums with more sensitivity in business that were requesting further cooperation, believing that this would be a huge business opportunity.

In Han Xiao's opinion, these were all 'building blocks' that were delivered to his doorstep.

The various consortiums had always been important partners for the Beyond Grade A organizations, but if the three Universal Civilizations adopted such economic sanctions in the future, these various consortiums would be caught in a dilemma between the two factions, not knowing which to choose.

During these unordinary periods, Han Xiao did not wish to clarify any risks with his investors. He planned to immediately accept any investors that wished to invest, tying the association and the consortiums further together to prevent them from running away.

If there came a day when economic sanctions really took place, the consortiums could either be as stubborn as mules and stay all the way or slice off a big piece of their flesh to withdraw. In short, they would not be allowed to pull out with all their investments.

For some organizations with Beyond Grade As, the significance of the Sanctum Revival was even more important. Among them, Han Xiao's attention was focused on the surviving descendants of those historical Beyond Grade As. A few of them had already reached out to him, expressing their desire to resurrect their 'ancestor'.

"The surviving descendants of the historical Beyond Grade As… they're both a source of propaganda and a pool of high-value talents. With the Sanctum Revival in my hands, we can gain something of value from these groups," Han Xiao muttered.

Resurrecting a Beyond Grade A would only allow him to receive gratitude from said person, but acting on someone's request to resurrect would mean he could obtain many more benefits.

This was basic demand and supply. Since he had a monopoly, he could decide the price, and in Han Xiao's view, this might be the correct method to operate the Sanctum Revival.

Right now, however, in order to maintain a sense of secrecy, it would be better not to turn it into a business.

Han Xiao populated his memo, recording thought after thought. It was the president's duty to guide the development direction of the association, so it was necessary for him to consider all aspects and begin preparing early.

Very quickly, the memo was densely filled up. Han Xiao listed the current affairs that had to be completed, turning it into a complicated mess. Scanning it, he nodded to himself.

"Regarding the work of the association, this is about it. On the side of the organization, I'll withstand the pressure, using my own strength as the foundation to maintain all of these things…"

While he thought to himself, Han Xiao opened up the interface with a smile.

With the Revivors joining the association, his bonus given by [Proof of Leadership] had seen a small rise. In the past few decades, he had digested most of Jayz's technical treasures, building a variety of Gold Grade equipment. He had already come a long way on the road of God's Trait Transformation.

His Machinery God's Trait Transformation had reached the apex at level fifteen with the help of his Mission Completion Cards. As for his Void God's Trait Transformation, it had reached level nine, which was also quite a high level.

The bonuses brought about by both of them had once again increased his Energy by thousands of Ona. At the same time, when his Machinery God's Trait Transformation reached the final level, it brought about additional enhancements to himself, such as obtaining another fragment of the First Sanctum, as well as a fifteen percent increase in his chance to form an exclusive talent.

But unlike the first two times, his unknown talent was finally activated, turning into a new talent—[Mechanical Divinity]!

This was a special reward given when one reached the top of the Mechanic Class. The effect was comprehensive, covering strength of abilities, Machinery Affinity, manufacturing efficiency, and basic attributes, giving bonuses to Endurance and more. This allowed Han Xiao's Energy to rise by more than 900 in one go, making progress in every single possible manner.

In addition, [Mechanical Divinity] provided him with two additional abilities. The first allowed him to obtain a stacking bonus when he activated his machinery with Mechanical Force, allowing him to get stronger as he fought.

The second gave him an ascension for his life level in his next advancement. From Han Xiao's viewpoint, this might be the most critical effect, which would live up to its name of 'transformation'.

As for the Void path, it mainly strengthened his Race Specialties and basic attributes, improving his Racial Talent. At the fifth level, the Black Star race's talent [Mechanical Genius] experienced a forward leap in evolution, giving him a fragment from the First Sanctum.

As for his Unique Talent, Han Xiao was finally not totally clueless about it. During these decades of research, he had finally triggered a notification from his interface.

The Unique Talent was not one that could be obtained from a sudden epiphany. The mechanism worked when relevant activities were carried out, randomly giving him a certain amount of progress each time. Only when the progress bar was filled up could a true Unique Talent be formed. The triggering frequency and amount of progress depended on the probability of the activity being able to form his Unique Talent.

Because of the bonus awarded by his God's Trait Transformation, Han Xiao had finally activated a prototype. It had only triggered about three times in the decades, with an extremely low probability. His progress bar was only at 44.7%. At this rate, it would take more than a hundred years for a normal Beyond Grade A to be able to develop their own Unique Talents.

The Awakening Points were able to speed up this progress, but he had no leeks to harvest for a few decades, so Han Xiao decided to be economical, not upgrading his skills, which led to fewer Awakening Points.

Our Great Mechanic Han gazed at his interface as he silently calculated his strength.

The Energy Rank increase brought to me by the various specialties is really high, opening up a gap between myself and the topmost echelons of the universe. I belong to a position on my own now, and when I reach my advancement for level 360, I might really step into a totally new realm…

The best thing to do now would be to push my Void God's Trait Transformation to the maximum before my advancement, in order to maximize the benefits. The Gold Grade blueprints that Jayz left for me might be insufficient, but as long as I enter The First Sanctum, I should be able to collect a wave of these blueprints, and there will not be a need to worry about not having enough God's Trait Transformation points…

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled in expectation.

Nobody seemed to have been able to set foot in this higher territory, even in the previous iterations. When the time came, what sort of feeling would it be?

…

"Unexpectedly, the Beyond Grade A Association gave us such a huge surprise!"

In the Super Star Cluster Alliance remote conference room, the leaders of the various Super Star Clusters were gathered together, their expressions unable to withhold their grins.

Ever since they lost in the Flickering War, the Super Star Cluster Alliance had been driven out of the Flickering World by the three Universal Civilizations. They could only endure this humiliation and go home to lick their wounds and recuperate, lying dormant whilst waiting for other opportunities.

They did not expect that merely a few decades later, the patterns in the universe would change once again.

"The conflict between the three Universal Civilizations and the Beyond Grade A Association has begun. Black Star is always surprising us, even managing to dig up all those dead people. The three Universal Civilizations will definitely not sit still. This is our opportunity."

The eyes of the Star Arc Civilization's leader flickered as the corners of his mouth rose.

Someone laughed. "That's right. This is a good time to intervene and also a direction to shake the rule of the three Universal Civilizations. We can make some improvements to the basis of our original plan."

Even whilst recuperating, the Super Star Cluster Alliance was not idle. They were already planning to create some trouble for the three Universal Civilizations.

They originally wanted to jointly support a special task force, instigating the anger of the common people that suffered from inequality, reducing the goodwill of these people toward the three Universal Civilizations so as to shake their rule.

But plans could never keep up with the changes. There were now obviously better options.

Everyone had their own ideas, and they discussed vigorously.

"From what angle should we intervene in this storm?"

"It's impossible to appear in person. We have to hide behind the scenes… Since the three Universal Civilizations and the Beyond Grade A Association are restraining themselves, we should intensify their conflict and make them turn openly hostile."

"The best result would be having both sides lose out, but the Beyond Grade A Association only possesses top-level strength. The power difference between the two is too wide. They are not an opponent of the three Universal Civilizations, so we should find a way to help them increase their power."

"Are you talking about cooperating with them? That works, but it will attract the attention of the three Universal Civilizations."

"No, no, not cooperation. We can secretly kill a few of their members, then pin the blame to the three Universal Civilizations, just like what they did to us in the Tragedy of the Pinnacles…"

The people threw out idea after idea, discussing them endlessly.

At this moment, the Star Arc Civilization's leader interjected.

"Maybe… we could play it big this time!"

Hearing this, everyone turned, curious.

"What are your thoughts?"

The leader narrowed his eyes as he solemnly spoke. "Currently, the contradiction is only between the Beyond Grade As and the three Universal Civilizations. This scope is still too narrow. We can attempt to provoke a greater opposition… For example, we can expand the conflict to the entire Super class against the three Universal Civilizations!

"We can spread rumors that the three Universal Civilizations wish to slaughter the Supers in order to prevent new Beyond Grade As from being born, then we find some people to pretend to be part of the three Universal Civilizations. The hunting team will expose themselves, and by then, even if the rumors are too exaggerated, fear will be the best persuasive power, leading to panic.

"The Beyond Grade A is the natural leader of the Supers, which will cause them to step up, confronting the three Universal Civilizations and deepening their conflicts. The Beyond Grade A Association might seize this chance to increase its power since it will not miss out on such an advantage. The three Universal Civilizations will thus lose a lot of Supers, people, and prestige… Isn't this very profitable?"

Hearing this, everyone jumped in shock, staring at each other.

After being silent for a while, someone asked, "Isn't this a bit too exaggerated? If you instigate the rebellion of the entire Super-class, Galactic Society will experience a huge disturbance. Besides, the three Universal Civilizations will not sit still and wait. They will come out with countermeasures, and if they expose us, what should we do?"

"The risk is indeed high, but the benefits are proportional. This is already the best bet. I just put forward a new path we can follow. As for the specific details, we'll still have to consider it further."

The leader of the Star Arc Civilization then added after a pause, "Besides, the three Universal Civilizations are unlikely to be completely clean as well. Judging by their current situation, they might really have the idea of creating a fault in the Supers. Since they cannot prevent the resurrection, they can only prevent the birth of the new people. But even if they have such ideas, they will only act secretly to target potential Calamity Grade seeds. What we're doing is just helping them 'advertise' it."

The Star Arc Civilization's leader sneered.

I dare not say anything else, but I'm the best at sh*t stirring!

…

Somewhere within the Ancient Star Desert, in a bustling galactic transit station, a few people clad in black robes walked among the ceaseless streams of people, their appearances hidden.

Suddenly, a few of them stopped, looking at a tall building not far away. At this moment, the virtual screen on the wall of the building was broadcasting news about the Sanctum Revival and the association.

The lead man slightly lifted his hood, revealing a stern face. It was Pangon, and those with him were the avengers that had left the Holy Accord about two months ago.

"Humph, Beiger and the rest are already 'born'…" Pangon whispered to himself.

By the side, a companion glanced at him. "We've been out for several months. What are you planning to do?"

Pangon's eyes flashed coldly.

"With just our strength, it's too early to take revenge against the advanced civilizations. Now that Beiger's group has attracted the attention of the universe, we should secretly develop our forces. Once we have accumulated enough power, we'll head to the three Universal Civilizations for revenge… Before that, we have to hide our hostility and even pretend to cooperate with the three Universal Civilizations to stab them at the right time."

As he spoke, Pangon took out a communicator and showcased the life history of someone. It was actually the EsGod!

He pointed toward EsGod's data and spoke.

"Just like this junior of ours, there's a lot of learning value. We can consider his methods…"

Chapter 1263: Undercurrents move once again

In one of the deep secondary dimensions, there was a piece of verdant land, full of greenery, mountains, and rivers. At its center was a beautiful and prosperous tower. The surrounding buildings were laid around it in a circular layout, their heights gradually decreasing the further outward they were situated. From one's line of sight, it looked like a city built to guard this tall tower.

The streets were bustling, and life forms of various appearances lived in harmony there. Most of them were species that existed in the main universe, but there were also a small number of native races that belonged to the Secondary dimension.

If there were any Beyond Grade A Supers present, upon gazing at the sun, moon, and thousands of stars in the sky, they would discover magic lines flickering in subtle places. These scenes were all illusions that were carved out through magic circuits, with none of them being real.

There was a beautiful brown wooden table placed on the top of the tower, of which was made from the core of the Devil Pith, an extremely precious material in magical alchemy. There were four ivory-colored tea cups on the table, which were filled with tea of an amber color. The steam emitted from tea filled the surroundings with fragrance, allowing people to feel calm. Obviously, the tea leaves were also a precious material.

Seated at the table, four figures looked at the boundless city whilst elegantly drinking the tea leisurely.

At this moment, an almost invisible phantom appeared beside the table, as though this space had suddenly distorted.

"My messenger is back…"

One of the old men in gorgeous mage robes pressed on the center of his brows, his mana absorbing the phantom.

He shut his eyes for a moment, as though savoring the taste, but his brows suddenly jerked.

"It seems like something major has happened in the main universe."

Hearing this, the rest placed down their teacups, looking over curiously.

"What happened?"

"See for yourself."

The elderly mage waved his hand, a thread of spiritual force shooting out. It sank into the heads of the other three, allowing them to share his memories. The news was about the changes in the Beyond Grade A Association, shown in the galactic news.

"Primordial Ones were revived? Sanctum Revival?"

"There's actually such an event?"

The few of them revealed expressions of surprise.

"The changes in the main universe are really progressing rapidly with each passing day. Things that I never dared to imagine are all coming true. Such are the tides of time…" The elderly mage sighed.

"It doesn't matter how they change. This doesn't matter to us anyway. We've isolated ourselves from the world. Wasn't it just to avoid such storms?" The other person shook his head.

Even for an advanced civilization, they could not supervise the birth of every Beyond Grade A. Everyone pursued different things. Sometimes, there were Beyond Grade As who were unwilling to fight for power, unwilling to show their skills and change with the times, so they chose to seclude themselves after reaching the Beyond Grade A realm, hiding their hard-earned strength.

Because those who could be promoted to the Beyond Grade A realm were generally people with strong ambitions and desires, there were relatively few of them who had no ambitions and yet could still advance. These were usually attributed to luck and were not recorded by the advanced civilizations.

These four were Beyond Grade As who had retired from the universe a long time ago. They were like-minded individuals, staying away from the main universe and settling deep within the secondary dimensions, forming a cooperative front to take care of each other.

This secondary dimension named 'Land of Four Gods' was not naturally formed. The four of them had selected a suitable dimension before putting in the elements stolen from the main universe such as materials and people, transforming it into a prosperous world much like a utopia. At the same time, everybody's mind was wiped, so they would think that this dimension was an entire world. The population thus proliferated down from generation to generation.

The residents could stay free from war and enjoy the tranquility of the world. The majority of people there could all live to the end of their lifespan and worshipped the four as their 'Gods of Creation'.

The elderly mage shook his head. "That being said, the Sanctum Revival is worthy of our attention. Sooner or later, we'll also experience a time when we decay. If we can obtain a second life, we can continue to exist."

"That time when we left the place, we never had any intentions to return. Are we going to break this intention now?" one of them said in a hesitant voice. They had gotten used to staying in this place and had some fear of going back out.

The mage stroked his long beard, only replying after a while. "Let's wait and see again. Now's not a good time to go back. We can wait till the dust settles before we have a chat with the younger lad known as Black Star."

Even for those Beyond Grade As that avoided public scrutiny, they could not help being drawn in by the Sanctum Revival offered. Not only were the four of them affected, but similar issues were also happening in the many corners of the secondary dimensions.

The Sanctum Revival was akin to a deep water mine, stirring up the mud and sand in the depths of the seabed, causing the hidden existences to reenter the range of sunlight, surging as undercurrents in corners that no one knew about.

Within the Arcane Church's Temple of Ten Thousand Gods, numerous statues of gods in all shapes and sizes stood. Some were majestic and heroic, some detached from the mortal dust, and some indescribable. The only thing in common was that each statue appeared lifelike. They were gods of various religions circulating in the universe.

The [God's Chosen] Wuornos stood in the center of the main hall, his head bowed as he prayed. The silvery-gray sacrificial priest's robes fluttered even without a wind, as colorful and peculiar auras flew around his body vigorously. If one were to observe the interior of these auras, they would see that it seemingly contained lines of divine words.

At this moment, a priest led an upper echelon of the Arcane Church to enter the temple.

"Your Excellency, God's Chosen, the Pope requires your assistance."

The upper echelon of the Arcane Church saluted as he spoke with a respectful attitude.

Wuornos stopped his prayers, indifferently speaking without even turning his head. "Speak."

"Because of the Sanctum Revival, we have reached a new cooperation agreement with both the Crimson Dynasty and the Federation of Light, planning to form a joint scientific research team to conduct research of our own to obtain the Sanctum Revival. We're preparing to establish a secret research institute in the desolate universe belt in the middle of the three territories, and the Pope would like you to hold the fort there, God's Chosen."

"Sure."

Wuornos turned his head, pointing to an angel wielding a sword next to him. This was one of the deities worshipped by a large religious school named 'Barbaroy'. Based on the school's system, this deity governed over 'combat' itself.

At this moment, an invisible energy spread, and the statue suddenly shook. A golden-white aura shot out from within, separating itself from the statue. At the moment the light left the shell, the lifelike feeling of the statue dissipated.

This golden-white aura suffused into Wuornos' body. The next moment, a crash was heard as an illusory figure suddenly grew out from his back.

This phantom had a pair of glowing wings and held a gorgeous long sword. It was surprisingly in the same outfit as the deity, except that its size and appearance were similar to Wuornos instead, as though they had combined.

At this moment, the phantom was holding Wuornos' shoulders with its hands, attempting to pull itself out of Wuornos' body inch by inch.

In just a few seconds, the sword-wielding angel had succeeded in separating itself, flapping its wings and floating into the air, splashing a pale, golden energy all over as it quickly transformed from a phantom into a physical entity with a strong aura. It stopped when the energy fluctuations reached the level of an upper-tier Beyond Grade A.

The two figures stood side by side, looking like different versions of the same person.

At this moment, Wuornos slowly spoke.

"One deity is enough. Barbaroy is good enough for this task. Take him there."

"Alright, I'll escort him over. Thank you for your gift."

The upper echelon of the Arcane Church nodded and saluted.

No matter how many times he witnessed this, he could not help but secretly marvel and admire this scene.

This was the guardian of the Arcane Church, the person recognized in the universe as the strongest for many years now, the legendary God's Chosen who could 'summon' the gods…

This one person could take on the persona of all the gods!

This was not just his personal ability but one of the core Universal Treasures of the Arcane Church, which was integrated into Wuornos' body, creating the title of God's Chosen.

At this moment, Wuornos saw that the other party had yet to leave and lightly asked, "Is there anything else?"

The person in question recovered his senses and hurriedly said, "There's another matter. The Pope asked me to ask this question…"

"Ask."

The upper echelon paused before carefully continuing. "The Pope wishes to know, do you have a guarantee of being able to get rid of Black Star?"

Hearing this, Wuornos finally turned to look at him. He frowned.

"I cannot guarantee that."

"… Alright. I apologize for intruding; I'll be off now."

The person could only bid farewell.

Sending him off with his eyes, Wuornos lowered his head to continue praying. From the start to the end, he did not leave his spot at all, as though he was also a statue of a deity that was fixed in place.

The news of the Sanctum Revival quickly rose to a fever pitch in a few days, with no sign of fading even after half a month. The major news channels found a new entry point, beginning to count the Revivors and their identities, which attracted the curiosity of the people, allowing their ratings to remain high.

At the same time, the Wayne Card company announced that they would work overtime in order to produce all related card decks of the Revivors, formulating several new genres of gameplay based on the Sanctum Revival, further inflaming the level of popularity.

And among the various classes of society, the Calamity Grades reacted the most fiercely.

The Calamity Grades already had the strength to occupy a territory, so many of them would rather be a big fish in a small pond than join in under the lead of a Beyond Grade A organization. However, the existence of the Sanctum Revival changed their plans.

Generally speaking, those who were Calamity Grades would join Beyond Grade A organizations either to obtain shelter or to seek guidance. But some people were aware of their own potential, understanding that they were unqualified to enter the Beyond Grade A realm. Thus, they did not have much motivation to cultivate. Many of them chose to come to a standstill, indulging in the luxury brought about by their power.

But now, almost no one could refuse the attraction that was a second life. Even those who had accepted their mediocrity early could not help but feel their passion rekindled.

This was especially so for the Beyond Grade A seeds!

Initially, most of the Beyond Grade A seeds had a sense of arrogance, and not everyone would seek guidance from a Beyond Grade A. Even if they knew that this would be beneficial to them, they did not wish to work for others.

Some of the Beyond Grade A seeds practiced the lone wolf method, aiming to complete the sublimation of life level on their own.

However, the situation had changed. They would not be able to enjoy the Sanctum Revival if they did not step into the Beyond Grade A realm. Thus, these potential stocks that were one step away from the Beyond Grade A realm would gradually have their mentality fluctuate, beginning to think of plans to join under the Beyond Grade A organizations, obtaining guidance to achieve the qualifications for Sanctum Revival as soon as possible.

Those who could even become Beyond Grade A seeds were decisive people. Once they had come to a decision, they immediately put it into action. For a period of time, many of the seeds stopped roaming around, adjusting their schedules to turn toward the Flickering World.

Those who had abilities could afford to be arrogant, but for the majority of the time, the reason they behaved so was only because the benefits offered to them were not enticing enough. This was the law of the universe.

Chapter 1264: Feidin's Card, Adventure Trigger

In a place near Blackhole Edge, a small fleet was moving toward the border of the Star Field, in the direction of the Flickering World.

Within the command room of the foremost spaceship, many of the operators bustled at their posts, reporting parameters from time to time.

"Reporting to the Captain, we've left the Haite Civilization's territory. Entering the low security area infested with galactic pirates. The alert level has been raised to Level 7. In about fifty-four hours, the fleet will arrive at the joint neutral area and enter the range of the inter-star field stargate."

"Ok. Expand the range of the unmanned reconnaissance fleet. We have to be cautious. The next section of the journey is not safe," Kevin replied as he sat in the captain's seat.

He was slender and had a fair complexion with a handsome appearance. He was dressed in a set of elegant casual clothes, coupled with a black wide-brimmed hat adorned with a feather. His shirt was unbuttoned, revealing a smooth, white chest. A slender saber hung sheathed on his waist, engraved with magic patterns that gave away its identity as a magic weapon.

'White Wave' Kevin was one of the recorded Beyond Grade A seeds in the universe. He did not belong to any organization but rather travelled freely within the universe.

This sort of neutral Beyond Grade A seed had always been an important target for the advanced civilizations, and Kevin was no exception. The three Universal Civilizations, the Super Star Cluster Alliance, and advanced civilizations in Blackhole Edge had handed him olive branches.

However, Kevin had never expressed his stance, not only because he did not wish to work under others, but also because he wished to leave himself some room to maneuver.

Originally, the price set by the three Universal Civilizations had moved him, and he was thinking about joining them, but the recent news about the Sanctum Revival made him dismiss such thoughts.

Even though the three Universal Civilizations had greatly increased their offers after this incident, it was no longer the same; Kevin remained unmoved. Suddenly, he no longer felt that the promised resources by the three Universal Civilizations were attractive, and he did not even wish to bargain. He directly decided to turn around and join the Beyond Grade A organizations, leading his fleet to the Flickering World.

He had even chosen his target. Black Star controlled the Sanctum Revival, so he had to join the Black Star Army. As long as he got to the Beyond Grade A realm in the future, he would be able to enjoy the benefits of a favorable position.

Kevin casually swiped through his communicator, browsing the latest news events on the local network channels. He soon noticed an article with an interesting title.

'The three Universal Civilizations claim to know of the phenomenon behind the Sanctum Revival. They have always been researching it, and now they have also produced results.'

Seeing this in the headlines, Kevin could not help but sneer with a disapproving expression.

"Tsk, in order to soothe the hearts of the public, the three Universal Civilizations have started to produce fake news…"

In the near future, similar news would appear from time to time due to the impact of Sanctum Revival to the galactic community. This had triggered a chain reaction, even shaking the direct descendants of the advanced civilizations. In Kevin's view, the three Universal Civilizations were doing this to placate the public and make the ordinary people believe that the three Universal Civilizations could also use such technology.

While such rumors were groundless, they could not be said to be completely ineffective. There would always be certain citizens in the Galactic Society who followed simple and crude logic, which made them believe that the three Universal Civilizations were involved in every field. Even if the Sanctum Revival was an unheard of technology, they would believe that the three Universal Civilizations had long known about it but kept it a secret.

However, these people were mainly only those in the lowest social strata. People like Kevin would naturally not believe it.

"The three Universal Civilizations are greatly pressured now. This is not a bad thing. Only when there's competition between the major factions will people like us get noticed. In order to win us over, they will have to come out with better welfare. If not for the three Universal Civilizations feeling the pressure, they would not have suddenly increased the chips to win me over."

Kevin scratched his jaw as he muttered to himself.

Reading on, he realized that the comment section was a little strange. There were many negative comments and curses directed at the Supers, with people feeling irritated about the privileges enjoyed by the Supers. Some were even furious about the unequal treatment. These comments all received a lot of likes and praise from the lurkers on the web.

Kevin carefully looked through the comments before helplessly shaking his head.

Toward the strength, status, and privileges that Supers enjoyed, the majority of the ordinary people both admired and feared them, but they also envied and hated them. Supers were one of the most active social classes in the universe, but they only accounted for a very small part of the total population of the universe. Compared to the ordinary people who were the mainstream, both sides had been plagued with conflicts for a long time.

Most people in the universe were destined not to have the potential to become Supers since they were born, doomed to be mediocre their whole lives. The more they admired these Supers, the more they would hate themselves for not having such a life and their unfair destiny. Thus, this hate would also pass to the surrounding matters related to Supers. Using reasoning could not tame the hearts of these people, thus forming a stubborn social contradiction between both classes.

On the universal scale, Supers and ordinary people were not just a matter of social class, not even of the same 'biology' make up. Supers represented the direction of evolution, whilst the ordinary people represented the low-level life forms. Even if the galactic society did not promote such a perception, many people thought of it as the truth.

The ordinary people who occupied the mainstream of the population were unwilling to accept their innate position as the 'eliminated of the evolutionary process', so conflict was doomed to happen.

In reality, most galactic residents did not dare make trouble in front of the Supers, but they would not hesitate to go on the quantum network to attack and vent their emotions. The Sanctum Revival seemed to have become a detonator for the grievances of the galactic residents, leading to many more of these ordinary residents becoming angry and shouting about injustice.

In such herd venting places, emotions would naturally outweigh one's rationality. Even if many of the people knew that the strength a Super had was a result of hard training, it was meaningless. They would only stop the scolding when all Supers in the universe were dead or when they became Supers themselves.

While Kevin was not surprised at this, he felt that the eruption behind the class conflicts had been too violent. He would not believe there was nobody manipulating the thoughts of people behind the scenes.

"Dark clouds keep accumulating, and heavy rain will arrive sooner than scheduled. I always feel that if this continues, it will be bad for the future of our Galactic Society…"

Kevin shook his head.

Boom!

At this moment, the spaceship suddenly shook, and its radar buzzed in alarm.

"Warning! Warning! Detected a space jamming device nearby, exiting hyperdrive. An unknown spaceship is fast approaching!"

Kevin looked up in surprise, hurriedly switching to the outside field. He soon saw a small fleet surrounding him. They were a galactic pirate group active in this area, with the leader seeming to be a Calamity Grade.

The next moment, the shouts of the galactic pirate group sounded in the wide area communication channel.

"Quickly stop your spaceship and open the hatch. Allow my people to board the ship. Otherwise, we will open fire!"

"It turns out they're here to loot…"

Kevin breathed a sigh of relief, and his expression turned cold.

"Captain, what do we do?" the pilot next to him asked. He believed in Kevin's strength, so he was not nervous at all.

"Humph, let them board. Since they're looking for death, then we'll give it to them. I'll finish them off quickly."

Kevin's eyes flashed.

Very quickly, the fleet stopped in place according to his instructions. Seeing this, the galactic pirates quickly approached, connecting their spaceships.

The hatch opened in a flash, and a galactic pirate stepped into the spaceship with a gun. Everyone onboard was waiting in front of the passage.

"Where's the captain? Tell him to come out and see me!" The galactic pirate looked around.

At this moment, there was a loud shout from the crowd.

"You messed with the wrong person!"

Kevin, who was hidden in the crowd, suddenly attacked. He drew out his long, slender saber, cutting out a splendid sheen as a sharp cold light shot out.

The galactic pirate leader was shocked, hurriedly raising his arm wrapped in Pugilist aura to block the surprise attack.

Swoosh!

The next second, blood spewed, and the galactic pirate leader screamed in pain as the blade cut through his aura and into his arm, deeply embedding within.

Kevin gripped the blade in both hands as his feet spun. A wave of white blade light suddenly lit up, leaving a remnant flash on everyone's retinas.

Shua!

The arm of the pirate leader fell on the ground. The incision was smooth, and the blood seemed to not have kept up with the speed of the blade as there was a split second of pause before it sprayed out, staining the spaceship corridor.

Both of them were in the Calamity Grade, but Kevin's Energy rank was much higher, so he maimed his opponent in a single blow. As a Pugilist of the War Soldier Branch, Kevin was extremely lethal, having long reached the master level in swordsmanship.

Right at this moment, a sudden change occurred!

In the team of galactic pirates, seven to eight of them released the aura of a Calamity Grade and attacked Kevin at the same time, like hunters who had been stalking their prey for a long time!

"What!" Kevin's pupils shrank, his eyes changing drastically.

These people definitely did not belong to the galactic pirates. If there were so many Calamity Grades, they would have been famous, and he would not be surprised like this.

To be so close and yet unable to sense their auras, these assailants were not simple!

Kevin did not have time to think about the origins of this group. He hurriedly dodged and blocked, but the attack was too sudden, leaving him to withstand most of the heavy blows. Blood spurted out as he suffered a heavy injury. The Pugilists of the War Soldier Branch were not famed for their defense.

"They're not ordinary Calamity Grades. They're all masters!"

Kevin was horrified, and while coughing blood, he slashed out wide, smashing through the bulkhead of the spaceship to flee into the universe, attempting to approach another spaceship.

At this moment, the seven to eight Calamity Grades chased after him, intercepting and cooperating to destroy all the spaceships while entangling Kevin, leaving no path of retreat.

Seeing that his path of retreat was cut off, Kevin could only resist desperately. With every exchange between him and the group, he was put in more and more danger.

Even with his status as a Beyond Grade A seed, he could not withstand the siege of seven to eight Calamity Grades. After all, not everyone had the frightening ability of Black Star.

"You guys are not galactic pirates. Who are you people‽" Kevin yelled in the wide area communication channel. Through his senses, he could vaguely feel the resolute killing intent of these Calamity Grades, as though they were there purposely for him.

Could it be that this group allied with the galactic pirates to plot against me?

But his question was destined to never be answered. These Calamity Grades were silent, only answering with their attacks, unscrupulously releasing their cold killing intent.

Seeing this, Kevin gritted his teeth, unwilling to sit still as he called out for help on the wide area communication channel while still trying his best to break out from the siege. Even knowing that his chance of escape was slim, he would not give up.

As his injuries grew more severe, he gradually burned out and started to lose his consciousness.

"It took me such a long time to gain my strength and to set foot in the Beyond Grade A field. Could it be that I'll have to die like this here?"

Kevin tried his best to persevere as a strong unwillingness surged in his mind.

At this point, everyone's attack suddenly halted. They looked up, seeing a shuttle-shaped spaceship appearing in their sight not far away, approaching as it seemed to have discovered the abnormal energy response there.

"There are eyewitnesses. What should we do?"

"Ignore them. Kill the target first."

The few people exchanged words before increasing the intensity of the offensive, abandoning all defenses, fighting tooth for tooth.

This became the last straw. Kevin's wounded body could no longer bear the offensive surge and shattered into pieces. His life quickly fled from his body.

One of the Calamity Grades was about to deliver the final fatal blow, but at this moment, something strange happened!

Buzz!

A holy golden light shot out from the spaceship, approaching quickly and shining on Kevin's tattered body.

The next moment, as though a miracle happened, Kevin's body returned to its intact state in the blink of an eye. All his injuries disappeared without a trace. He opened his eyes in confusion.

"This is…"

The pupils of those Calamity Grades shrank, and they all turned to the spaceship where the beam of light came from.

At the same time, Aurora retracted her hand from within the spaceship, her eyes flashing with excitement and curiosity.

"It's really fun to go out with you. I always encounter strange things."

By the side, Feidin helplessly shook his head.

If it was not for him being volunteered, he would not have wanted to accompany Aurora to travel everywhere. To put it nicely, he was a 'bodyguard', but in fact, he was just being used as an event trigger to make her journey more interesting and fun.

Chapter 1265: Snatched

Ever since she stepped into the Beyond Grade A realm half a year ago, Aurora had won the approval of Han Xiao and Hila, allowing her to leave the camp and wander around the universe. According to her words, it was no easy feat to have reached this level, so why would she not enjoy her time outside?

During her first few months, Aurora travelled around alone to view the scenery and experience different cultures, but she soon discovered that such a journey was too dull, not as exciting as she had imagined it to be.

Thus, after Han Xiao returned from the Sanctum, Aurora borrowed the handyman Feidin from him, asking Han Xiao to use the King to teleport him to her.

The effect of this move was significant, suddenly turning her journey into an exciting one. According to definitely inaccurate and incomplete statistics, the duo had been involved in more than a dozen incidents, be it large or small in just the past two months.

Aurora was now satisfied, but Feidin felt completely helpless as he was dragged around by Aurora to continue his career as a handyman.

He could not help regretting the fact that he had managed to separate Chen Xing's soul, otherwise he could pass time by talking to her, not being just a mascot like he was now.

The spaceship they operated was specially crafted by Black Star. The hyperdrive engine, energy shield, detection radar, Cloaking Devices, and other miscellaneous devices were all top tier. Not too long ago, the spaceship had detected the abnormal energy fluctuations there and concluded that a battle was taking place. The special interference device of Black Star's broke through the channel interference and saw Kevin's call for help.

At the same time, Aurora's ability also sensed multiple Calamity Grade life signals and immediately knew that there was excitement to be discovered there. Thus, she turned to take a look, chancing across this scene.

While she was not aware of the events that had transpired, throughout her months of wandering, she had long developed her own style of doing things… Regardless of why they were trying to kill each other, until she got the bottom of it, none of them were allowed to die!

With the limitless power provided through her 'milk', she could be that arrogant!

Seeing that Kevin was on the verge of death, Aurora did not waste her time, immediately drawing out a portion of healing energy. With her current Beyond Grade A strength, healing a Calamity Grade completely was as easy as taking a breath. In a moment, Kevin was reconstructed perfectly, and he even felt as though he was stronger.

"… I'm not dead?"

Kevin lowered his head, staring at his undamaged body. For an instant, he had faced death straight ahead, thinking that he was about to die, but the sudden infusion of 'milk' caught him off guard. He could no longer tell if he was in reality or an illusion.

At the same time, the faces of the besieging Calamity Grades twisted, and they suddenly dispersed.

"These are Beyond Grade A fluctuations. Run!"

The group split up and fled without hesitation. Enchantment tattoos lit up on their bodies, showing magic circuits of short-range teleportation being inscribed on them. With only slight fluctuations in space, all of their teleportation skills were activated.

"Thinking of running after beating me up‽"

Kevin recovered to his senses, rushing toward the nearest enemies. A strong aura condensed on his blade, slashing out as a sharp blade light.

The teleportation procedures of three of the enemies were interrupted as they avoided the attack.

However, a small vortex had already been created in front of the others, which was still rapidly expanding. It would only take them a few seconds to complete their preparations, allowing them to teleport and escape from there.

Seeing that the teleportation technique had been successfully engaged, the few of them were about to sigh in relief. However, a unique spatial fluctuation suddenly spread out from Aurora's spaceship.

Buzz!

This fluctuation acted like an iron, directly smoothing all the space folds within the battlefield. The portals that were on the verge of forming shattered and disappeared.

On the spaceship, Aurora pouted.

"Humph, do you take my spaceship as a decoration‽"

Her spaceship contained a lot of black technology, which included what Han Xiao had obtained from Jayz's technological treasure. The powerful spacetime anchoring was just one of the minor abilities her spaceship possessed.

Seeing this situation, the faces of the Calamity Grades turned pale. They glanced at each other, resoluteness flashing in their eyes.

The next moment, the group of people gave up on running away, turning their heads and rushing toward the shuttle-shaped spaceship, as though they wished to end up in mutual annihilation.

Feidin narrowed his eyes, about to take action. However, Aurora tapped on his shoulder.

"It's okay. Let me do it."

Her eyes flashed, and the energy levels in her body surged, instantly transforming her into her 'mature' version. The Mark of the Underworld on the back of her hand also lit up.

With a wave of her hand, Life and Death Energy combined to form the Resurrection Energy. The energies entangled with each other, weaving out bones, muscles, and blood vessels, transforming into the temporary mortal shells of ten different species.

Under the power of the Resurrection Energy, the temporary shells were quickly materialized, their outlines almost the same as the owners' previous physical bodies. The only difference was that these temporary bodies all emitted a faint fluorescence light and retained certain characteristics of an Energy Life form.

With a flick of her finger, ten Calamity Grade Hero Spirits flew out from the Mark of The Underworld, merging into the shells. The next moment, their bodies all burst forth with Calamity Grade energy fluctuations.

The Hero Spirits descend, reincarnating from the Earth!

These series of actions were fluidly performed, which hinted at the ceaseless practice. At this moment, the Hero Spirits had become complete life forms, possessing the actual combat power of their previous lives.

"Go, take them down." Aurora laughed.

The ten Calamity Grades nodded and immediately rushed out of the spaceship, intercepting their opponents and fighting them. Kevin saw this but was not surprised, quickly joining the battle.

The Hero Spirits did not care about death at all, so they did not even bother to defend. For them, an aggressive style of play was nothing more than a tactic. It might be unscrupulous, but it allowed them to operate above their combat levels, showing more power than before their original deaths.

Even though she completely controlled the Holy Light Particle, Aurora's frontal lethality was still weak. She had thus become completely accustomed to the Summoning style but still stuck to only summoning up to Calamity Grade Hero Spirits. The physical consumption of summoning the Beyond Grade A Hero Spirits was too large. Plus, she had promised Han Xiao that she would not easily allow the Beyond Grade As to come out for a walk.

A Beyond Grade A would naturally bully the Calamity Grades, and without any suspense, these Calamity Grades of unknown origin soon retreated hastily.

Seeing that they were about to be captured alive, the group of people clenched their teeth, crazily compressing the energies in their bodies. Their bodies were soon covered with glowing cracks.

"They're planning to implode!"

Kevin was shocked, subconsciously drawing back.

He did not expect this group of people to be so decisive, opting to blow themselves up than be caught alive.

Boom!

The next instant, the bodies of the several people burst into flames. A huge shock wave blasted outward.

However, this self-detonation had only just started when a holy light shot out from the spaceship again. Sweeping past, the fragmenting bodies of this group of people re-bonded and were restored to their original state.

The pupils of these people shrank, and they once again imploded without hesitation, only to have the same scene occur again. The moment they felt the pain of their bodies tearing apart, another light would shoot out and heal their injuries.

After trying a few times, the results remained unchanged. The faces of these people were now filled with despair as they understood that their lives were no longer theirs to control.

They could not live how they wanted, but they could not die when they wanted to either!

"That's enough. Don't fool around with them anymore. I'll do it."

Feidin shook his head in resignation.

He took out the Soul Swapper, replacing the souls of a few of them into prepared containers of animals.

In this period, Feidin had also reached the rank of a Beyond Grade A seeds. With this weird Soul Swapper, it could be said that it was rare for him to meet an enemy that could threaten him in the Calamity Grade.

The bodies of those whose souls were transferred turned into empty husks, collapsing where they stood and were easily captured. The Hero Spirits set about cleaning up the battlefield.

Seeing this scene, Kevin finally relaxed. He was full of joy at being able to escape from the dead and quickly broadcast through the wide area communications channel.

"My name is Kevin. Esteemed ones, you have saved my life. May I know if I may have the honor of thanking you face to face?"

After a few seconds, a voice sounded from the channel.

"Let's talk on the spaceship."

Kevin was energized. As he approached the spaceship, the door opened, letting him fly in.

After following the guiding robot to the command room, he saw the eye-catching Aurora at a glance. He did not hesitate to salute in excitement and surprise.

"Turns out that it's the new Deputy Army Commander of the Black Star Army, the Goddess of Life, Aurora. It's my blessing to be able to meet you!"

When Aurora had made a move, Kevin had vaguely guessed her identity, but only now did he dare confirm it when he saw the person in flesh.

Kevin's happiness only grew.

Fortunately, he had met Aurora, who was a master of life. If it were someone else, they would probably not have been able to pull him back from death.

In the vast universe, I actually managed to encounter a Beyond Grade A that could save me. What sort of probability was this?

My luck is too good!

"Eh, when did I get this moniker?" Aurora actually intended to act high and mighty like Hila, but hearing this, she stopped in shock.

"Don't you know?" Kevin said. "This is because you're the sister of the 'Goddess of Death' and hold the exact opposite powers, so the world has started calling you this."

"Not bad, I'm also someone with a moniker now." Aurora giggled.

While it was only one compared to the multitude Hila had, it was a good start. Sooner or later, she would be able to defeat her sister and crush her under her own feet proudly!

Fantasizing about this scene, Aurora's emotions were surging with joy.

Glancing over, Feidin immediately guessed that Aurora was distracted again, so he could only take the reins. "Anyway, we received your call for help, so we came over just in time. Could you please explain what exactly happened?"

"It's like this. I was actually journeying but suddenly came across a bunch of galactic pirates…"

Kevin explained the whole process truthfully without hiding anything.

After hearing this, Feidin squeezed his perfectly shaped chin as he guessed, "It seems more than meets the eye. These people are by no means just galactic pirates. I think they specifically aimed at you. Could it be a vendetta?"

"It doesn't make sense. I'm typically a do-gooder and have avoided any struggles of the factions. Even if I have to kill, I make sure I get rid of the roots as well. I have also never provoked an organization that could release seven or eight Calamity Grades at once."

Kevin drew a blank.

Hearing this, Feidin was lost in thought for a while before he muttered, "If it's not a vendetta, then it's likely related to the current storm."

"What is it about?" Kevin was curious.

"Oh, I'm still not sure, but we managed to capture a few live ones, so some interrogation will reveal everything…"

Feidin shook his head, but he suddenly paused, and his words grew sharp.

"You just mentioned that you were journeying over to the Flickering World to join the Black Star Army?"

"That's right…"

"Great!" Feidin's eyes lit up. "You don't need to travel so far to the Flickering World. The Deputy Army Commander is right in front of you and is definitely qualified to accept newcomers. You could just stay and become part of her Guard Corps."

"Huh?"

"This…"

Kevin paused for a while.

His original objective was to become a Black Star Guard, to enjoy the benefits of a favorable position, but Aurora had practically saved his life. While she was a new Beyond Grade A, her Esper Ability was unique, which would guarantee the safety of his life under most circumstances.

Even if he went over to the Flickering World, he might still encounter more dangers. Temporarily staying by Aurora's side was not too bad.

"Yes, yes, yes, come under my command. As long as you come, I can give you the position of Guard Captain!" Aurora's eyes lit up.

While she was the Deputy Army Commander, fully qualified to employ her own Guards regiment, she had been busy travelling ever since she was promoted. She had not recruited anyone, and thus, she had no Guards under her.

The talents in the army had mostly been divided by Black Star and Hila, so even if she tried recruiting from the inside, it would be difficult to find any masters. She had always envied the Guards that Hila had.

Now that she had encountered a Beyond Grade A seed in trouble, Aurora immediately had this thought.

Kevin struggled for a while before being tempted.

"… Alright, I'm willing to be the Captain of your Guard Corps."

He had also done some research on the organizational structure of the Black Star Army. From his point of view, there were three factions, each with the respective Beyond Grade A as the leader.

Black Star was undoubtedly the ruling faction, but there were too many talents within, and there was no opportunity to show off, which made his chances of standing out remote. Hila's faction was mainly comprised of women and had already been formed with no intention of expanding. Furthermore, Hila was also not known to be a good leader. In contrast, Aurora's faction had just been established, so if he became one of her early followers when she had a shortage of people, his status would naturally be extraordinary.

While Kevin's original intention was to obtain the Sanctum Revival, since he had decided to join an organization, he would not be satisfied with being a marginal person without any sense of existence.

"That's great. I'll help you register for your army authority! Phillip, come out!"

Aurora was overjoyed, immediately summoning Phillip. She could not wait to register Kevin as her Guards Captain.

Why is she even more excited than me?

Kevin felt a sinking feeling, but he had no choice but to cooperate.

However, this feeling of being appreciated by his boss made him feel more moved.

Seeing this, Feidin did not bother them, simply walking to the side and entering the spiritual realm to interrogate the prisoners.

After a while, Aurora had completed the procedures for Kevin, and the Hero Spirits had also cleaned up the battlefield.

At this moment, the two saw Feidin walk back with a solemn expression.

"You're done interrogating? How's the situation?" Aurora was curious.

"… The situation has exceeded our expectations. The matter is more serious than we thought."

Feidin shook his head, speaking in a steely tone.

"Immediately report to the Army Commander. This matter is out of our league!"

Chapter 1266: Travelling Feidin

"Oh? You're saying that someone is hunting down the Beyond Grade A seeds?"

In his personal machinery factory in Black Star Palace, Han Xiao looked with surprise at the communication screen where Feidin was speaking to him.

He had been too busy digesting his technology recently. Only when Feidin called him and told him that they had captured a hunting team that specifically targeted the Beyond Grade A seeds did he then notice.

"Speak in detail, I want to know everything." Han Xiao put down the parts in his hand, his expression turning solemn.

"It's like this…" Feidin explained the entire process.

After capturing these assailants, he had dug up the amazing intelligence through interrogation and reading of memories. All the Calamity Grades that attacked Kevin were acting on orders and had quietly controlled the galactic pirates that had been wandering nearby, waiting to intercept Kevin.

"Do you know which organizations they belong to?" Han Xiao was curious.

Feidin nodded. "I've already checked. These Calamity Grades did not leave any information within the universe. At the same time, they have no relevant memories, and they do not know which organization they work for, only unilaterally accepting direct orders from an account. The account for tasks for each person is also different. When I reviewed their memories, I discovered that they had been receiving some sort of thought-shaping training since young, specially to create warriors with weak self-awareness.

"Death warriors without any history? To be able to train up eight Calamity Grades as Death warriors from an early age, this is no small organization. The thought training should be a form of brainwashing that can maintain a long-term effect on the Calamity Grades. This should be technology at or above the Star Cluster level."

Han Xiao furrowed his brows, pondering silently for a while before he asked, "Any other clues?"

"I've found some safe houses and codewords, as well as their activities. When I finish sorting them out, I'll send you the report containing the top-secret accounts of these people for receiving tasks. It may be useful to you."

Han Xiao's brows rose. "To think you're placing so much importance in this matter. It seems like you also know the problem in this."

Feidin sighed. "If I could not guess the potential ramifications, then I would not have called you at first notice… People who can cultivate so many Calamity Grade Death Warriors will not be a small organization, and this team might not have been sent to only kill one person. Add that to the Sanctum Revival issue, this situation is obviously not simple."

Han Xiao nodded. "That's right. Organizations who have the motivation and the abilities to do such a thing are few and far between. The Super Star Cluster Alliance is also suspicious."

While he did not manage to get their origins, through the analysis of different factors, Han Xiao first thought of the three Universal Civilizations as well as the Super Star Cluster Alliance, both of whom intended to do such a thing.

The former wished to reduce the impact of Sanctum Revival, secretly reducing the source of new Beyond Grade As joining the association in the future. The latter had more hidden motives, mainly to aggravate the situation and pin the blame on others, creating opposition and forcing the three Universal Civilizations and the association to turn hostile.

Of course, he could not ignore the possibility that there was someone fishing in the muddied waters, so Han Xiao did not immediately jump to a conclusion. Rather, he only assumed it to be the secret operation of the three Universal Civilizations or the Super Star Cluster Alliance.

As inferred, there was a high probability that there existed more than one hunter team. At present, there were many Beyond Grade A seeds rushing to the Flickering World from each Star Field, so the orchestrators behind the scenes were likely to deploy interception troops. These Beyond Grade A seeds would be at risk, as not all of them would be so lucky to run into the top milkmaid of the universe.

Feidin scratched his head in puzzlement. "Forget about the Super Star Cluster Alliance, but the three Universal Civilizations… would they really do such a thing? Conducting such a crazy plan, are they not afraid of facing the backlash of all Supers? It's too radical."

Han Xiao shook his head, not looking surprised at all.

"This sort of behavior is crazy but effective. The Beyond Grade A seeds in the entire universe are not many to begin with, and the cost of them going hands-on is not high. Even if all these people disappear, the backlash can be easily suppressed.

"Moreover, the three Universal Civilizations were clear that they had lost the monopoly advantage of having Ultimate Knowledge. The association can give whatever they can give, and with the addition of the Sanctum Revival, it will be difficult for them to attract new talents. On the other hand, the association did not even require any advertisement to attract new talents. If they do nothing, the situation will only get worse, so instead of sitting and watching, it's better to send these Death Warriors to kill people and ruin what they can't get.

"As for the methods… as with the Tragedy of the Pinnacles, the three Universal Civilizations have never been good people. Don't be mistaken. As winners of the exploration era, none of them would have survived if they were not cruel. Once they panic, they can do anything."

Feidin pursed his lips. "Aren't they afraid of being revealed?"

Han Xiao stroked his chin. "I feel that they would be afraid, but I can't be sure since I have to look at their overall picture."

There was no Beyond Grade A Association in his previous life, and Sanctum Revival was kept under wraps, so the Beyond Grade A seeds were not intercepted. This was the first time Han Xiao had encountered such a situation, without knowing what the three Universal Civilizations would even do.

Han Xiao was also helpless to the fact that the Beyond Grade A seeds were targeted. He could only treat it as collateral damage.

"This storm is getting bigger and bigger." Feidin's expression was worried. "What do you intend to do?"

"The purpose of the association is mainly to solve the conflicts between the Beyond Grade As, so the Calamity Grade is not within our scope. Nominally, it is not suitable for us to cross the boundary and provide assistance…"

Han Xiao stroked his chin as he thought aloud.

"However, if we don't stop this, the seeds will suffer great casualties, which is not conducive to our recruitment of new Beyond Grade As. How about this? Don't they wish to join the various Beyond Grade A organizations? We'll ask those organizations to secretly send people to protect and escort them. This can be justified in name."

"Alright." Feidin paused for a moment. "However, this response force will encounter battles with the hunting squad. Do we wish to spread the news and make the seeds vigilant, at the same time giving a warning to the person behind the scenes?"

Han Xiao thought for a while but finally shook his head.

"Secretly spreading it to the seeds is enough. This news should not be spread out on a large scale… If we expose it now, the happiest would be the Super Star Cluster Alliance. I don't wish to tear off all pretenses with the three Universal Civilizations, nor do I want to be used as a weapon by the Super Star Cluster Alliance. Let's focus on protection first. For the time being, we will avoid conflict if possible."

While the Sanctum Revival was in name his, the Holy Accord had yet to be able to collect the second set of keys, so Han Xiao did not have much to rely on for now. Causing trouble was not his favorite action; it was better to be low-key.

"I understand. What else do you need me to do?" Feidin asked.

"For you guys… how about you search for more Beyond Grade A seeds in the vicinity. They will be safer with Aurora around them. Then, we can just bring all of them back."

As he spoke, Han Xiao smiled in a praising manner.

"You've earned yourself a great merit this time. Without your warning, we might have had to wait till many seeds went missing before we realized something was wrong. My decision to have you go along with Aurora was a good move!"

He felt that Feidin was the perfect intelligence officer. Most people had to search for things, but it was the exact opposite for Feidin. Even if he were only to lie down every day, he would still be able to run into key intelligence, as though it was an automated process for him.

This Feidin is really useful!

Feidin showed a helpless expression. He had already resigned to the fact that he was a tool to be used.

"By the way, what should I do with the captives after the interrogation? They could serve as evidence."

"What else can we do? Send them to the Underworld."

Han Xiao waved his hands casually.

The two further discussed the details before hanging up. At this moment, Han Xiao suddenly noticed that his interface was blinking.

_____________________

You have triggered the mission [Stop the Hunting]!

Mission Introduction: For some reason, some unknown organizations are trying to hunt down talents who wish to join you. As a well-known organization, protecting the personal safety of your candidates is a basic requirement.

Mission Objective: Try to prevent the hunting of the Beyond Grade A seeds.

Remarks: The reward depends on the Mission Rating, which is correlated to the number of people successfully rescued.

Basic Reward: 8 billion Experience, +20 Favorability of rescued targets, 2 Random Rewards, 1 Blank Character Summon Card.

_____________________

"The experience is a little stingy, but the blank Character Summon Card is pretty good stuff."

Han Xiao closed the interface. The level of this mission was not enough to excite him any longer. At present, he paid more attention to the matter itself.

"The three Universal Civilizations have quite the strong reaction to this. Being able to coexist in harmony is a pipe dream… Anyway, the version update has gone on for almost fifty years, so the players should be back soon. I'm afraid that will cause another explosion."

Han Xiao rubbed his brows, his thoughts wandering before he suddenly thought of something.

"By the way, since someone is hunting Beyond Grade A seeds, this will also be my chance to poach people. I don't know how Karlot is doing now. He should at most be a normal Calamity Grade, not taken seriously yet. I can just knock him out and bring him over."

Han Xiao had a sudden urge to do so.

In the past, because he was worried about the possibility of a premature death of Karlot due to dramatic changes in the plot, he did not insist on poaching him. However, now that someone was targeting the Beyond Grade A seeds, they could not blame him for doing tit for tat.

Originally, Karlot was supposed to become the pillar of the dynasty, but now that they had started this fiasco, they should not blame him for it!

Unlike the orchestrator behind the scenes, Han Xiao knew exactly who would become future Beyond Grade As. While it might have been difficult to poach them in the past, this was now a different matter.

"If they were to learn the truth, they would have to thank me. For the safety of the universe, I'll go all out to protect them. Maybe this is the so-called love has no boundaries. I admire myself so much. How could there be such a majestic person in this world?"

Han Xiao was so moved by himself that his shamelessness levelled up.

Chapter 1267: Pre-Judgment

Somewhere in the Endless Nebulae Star Field, a small fleet hovered in a transportation hub. Around it were continuous streams of light, but the fleet remained in place, as though it was waiting for someone.

In the command room of the main ship, Morgan paced back and forth in front of the porthole, his expression both solemn and anxious. The crew in the room merely watched him in silence.

After a short while, he paused and gravely said, "Urge them again and ask when the people from the Black Star Army will arrive."

By his side, his aide-de-camp could not help but speak up. "… Boss, you just asked them two minutes ago. The other party said that they were already rushing over. It's not too good to keep pressing them."

"Bullsh*t, I asked you to urge them, so do it! Else I'll dock your pay!" Morgan's eyes flashed, "Who knows when the enemies will appear? Would you know? You don't, so why are you spouting so much nonsense! You don't need to be responsible for my life, so of course, you don't care! But I can't possibly fight off seven or eight Calamity Grades at once, so if my little life is gone, I'll make sure you accompany me in my burial!"

The aide-de-camp was speechless. However, he did not take it seriously, having followed Morgan for a long time. He knew this guy's character too well. He was scared of dying, indecisive, calculative, petty, and stingy… Sometimes, the aide-de-camp wondered to himself, how could such a person become a Beyond Grade A seed?

Morgan Panselm, a senior Beyond Grade A seed, ran a small organization in the Endless Nebulae Star Field. He only cared about the convenience of his daily life, not seeking to expand, keeping a thin sense of existence.

The moment the Sanctum Revival matter was revealed, he did not speak another word, merely packing up and preparing to throw himself toward the Beyond Grade A Association. His top choice was the Black Star Army. Other than benefitting from close relations to an influential person, he also had some connections with Hadavy since both of them were hardcore gamblers.

It was just that, when he was about to take his team to leave the territory, he received a private notice from the Black Star Army, stating that some mysterious organizations were currently sending Death Warriors to kill off Beyond Grade A seeds. There could be up to seven or eight of them within a troop, so the army had sent out a few protective fleets to escort them and also reminded each person to be cautious.

This almost scared Morgan to death, and he immediately halted his departure, prepared to wait until the army's escort fleet arrived before leaving. Not only that, but he also parked his fleet in the most bustling area, staying within the crowd for fear of being murdered.

Of all the Beyond Grade A seeds who had received this notice, he was the one who behaved the most cowardly.

At this moment, his spaceship communicator rang, and a tender young face appeared on the screen.

"Hello, hello, this is Nero from the Black Star Army. I've arrived and spotted your ship. Please come over to make contact."

Hearing this, Morgan was overjoyed. He rushed to the porthole, seeing another fleet with the Black Star Army insignia stop not far away from him.

"The reinforcements are here! Listen to my order. Full speed ahead. Immediately rendezvous with them!" Morgan revealed an excited look.

"We're in such close range. Just dozens of seconds is enough to reach them through normal cruising. What full speed…" The aide-de-camp secretly cursed.

The two fleets quickly merged, and Nero took his men into Morgan's spaceship.

Just as he walked into the cabin, Nero saw Morgan waiting at the door of the passageway. Without a word, he rushed up and grabbed onto his hands with an emotional expression.

"My family, you're finally here. Do you know how I spent the last few days‽ I was in fear every single day, and now I can finally feel relieved!"

"There's no need to be so excited. It's all part and parcel." Nero's mouth twitched, and he applied some strength to forcibly extricate himself.

If not for the fact that Morgan had kept repeatedly pinging him, he would have arrived another two days later.

Morgan, however, did not seem to mind. He excitedly glanced behind Nero, "May I know how many experts the army has sent to meet me this time?"

"Experts? If we had to force it, I guess it's only me." Nero scratched his head a little in embarrassment.

Morgan's eyes widened, and he stammered, "Only one… er, it's not that I don't believe in your strength, but I heard that there'll be seven or eight Calamity Grades moving together. It's just two of us. I think there will be some danger…"

"There's no choice. At the moment, there are too many Beyond Grade A seeds who wish to join the Black Star Army. Our manpower is not enough any longer. We can only send out Grade Bs to escort. This sort of job would be best for the Immortals, but they have all disappeared fifty years ago, so the army has no experts left," Nero explained.

"Then… the safety issue…"

"Relax, all of the escort teams have a machinery squad from Black Star's Mechanical Army, as well as Her Excellency Aurora's special life potions, to ensure our safety."

Morgan finally relaxed. He asked, "Then, can we leave now for the Flickering World?"

Nero shook his head. "That's not necessary. We just need to go to the main army subdivision of each Star Field. Every location has a Throne that Godfather has placed. We can use that to teleport you straight to the main base.

Han Xiao initially did not wish to use this method, but after discovering the hunters, he could only lift the restrictions, allowing the Beyond Grade A seeds to utilize the King suits to warp, saving them from the dangers in their journey.

As for those Beyond Grade A seeds that wished to join other organizations, Han Xiao did not reject them either. He rendered the same help, albeit with a token sum. This was also one of the uses of the association, allowing the Beyond Grade As to integrate their resources. As the President, he naturally had to lead by example at this critical juncture.

Both of them walked to the command room while talking, and the fleet finally set off and began its journey.

At this moment, Morgan seemed to have thought of something. He curiously commented, "That's right, you mentioned that there were a lot of Beyond Grade A seeds at the moment. Have they met with the hunters? Was anyone hit?"

Hearing this, Nero's expression sank, and he lightly nodded.

"It was a smart choice for you to remain waiting here. Some Beyond Grade A seeds were nonchalant despite receiving the notice, thinking that they could continue their journey as long as they remained vigilant. In the end, even before the reinforcements could arrive, they encountered an assault and were killed.

"Because of distance issues, some people had long assembled with their escort teams. We're one of the later ones. Before us, some of our colleagues crossed hands with the hunters and turned out fine. However, other organizations have done the same but have been annihilated by the hunters themselves."

Morgan shuddered. "Who dares lay their hands on so many of the Beyond Grade A seeds? This is too frightening."

Nero sighed. "While the Army Commander has not specified who is responsible, it's not hard to guess… Since the enemy can discover the whereabouts of so many Beyond Grade A seeds, their intelligence network is no trivial matter. To also be able to send so many Death Warriors, the likelihood is that they are from an advanced civilization.

"While this was supposed to be a secret operation, the outside world would soon notice that all of these Beyond Grade A seeds had disappeared. This would inevitably scare some of people from joining the Beyond Grade A Association. Like this, the orchestrator's goal would be achieved."

"Oh, this is hard." Morgan sighed as well, pulling a long face.

Nero patted him on the shoulder. "Don't worry, with me here, you won't get into trouble."

Morgan nodded before suddenly asking, "That's right, with so many Beyond Grade A seeds also joining the army, how are our positions going to be arranged?"

"I'm not too sure. I think only a small portion will become part of the Guards Corps. The rest will hold various positions within the army, replenishing the gap in our high-ranked combatants. The main thing is to see what you want. The army will not force anyone to take up a position."

Morgan's eyes lit up. "Then, does that mean I can choose which Beyond Grade A to follow?"

"That's right, everyone can send in their application, but it will depend on the Excellencies to choose you." Nero nodded. "Who do you wish to choose? Is it His Excellency Black Star? The competition for my Godfather is quite fierce, and there's a possibility of losing."

Morgan immediately denied it and embarrassedly said, "No, no, I don't want to follow Black Star. I wish to follow Her Excellency Aurora."

Nero sized him up before coming to an understanding.

Ah, I understand now, this man must be afraid of death to the extreme, so if he is able to enjoy the healing from Aurora, it would be difficult for him to die in the future!

The phrase 'good for nothing' really describes you to a tee!

…

"Reporting, six of our Death Warriors have lost contact and might have been captured by the enemy. We have severed all related links."

"Reporting, the attack on Target #45 has failed. Three Death Warriors were sacrificed. The rest escaped with difficulty."

In a certain secret intelligence processing center, a large number of intelligence personnel were sitting in front of a set of instruments, constantly reporting on the situation. The room was full of noise.

On the wall of the room was an ultra large screen, made up of many smaller surveillance screens. A single chair was placed underneath it, with a tall, thin figure seated on the chair looking up at the screens, his back facing the crowd.

This place was a secret area jointly created by the Super Star Cluster Alliance many years ago. They had no specific name, shrouded in mystery yet having great authority. They only answered to the leaders of the various civilizations.

This secret department was responsible for managing black ops and cultivating Death Warriors. Various Super Star Cluster civilizations secretly selected talented children and sent them to such training bases to conduct cruel training from an early age before allowing them to specialize in performing tasks that could not be revealed.

Their training method was designed to squeeze out all potential, and coupled with their technological and magical advancements, it allowed them to effectively increase the rate of Calamity Grades being produced at the cost of a high mortality rate.

These Death Warriors would never know who they worked for, from the training period up till they performed their missions in the future. To this end, this department had even specially trained a group of Death Warriors who believed that they worked for the three Universal Civilizations. Many methods had been used to ensure that outsiders would not be able to trace the Death Warriors back to the Super Star Cluster Alliance.

Everyone within this department was a special member who was not recorded in any internal files. They were all referred to by codes. The tall and thin figure in the room was the person in charge of the department, with only his title known to people—'Skeletal'.

After listening to the reports of his subordinates, Skeletal leaned forward as he slowly spoke.

"It seems like the Beyond Grade As are aware of our hunting actions and have equipped all our targets with guards… The chain of suspicion has been formed; our goal is achieved. It will be a waste of manpower if we continue. Stop the operation. Have everyone withdraw."

"Understood!"

Everyone immediately followed orders without asking.

Skeletal bit on his nails as he narrowed his eyes.

"Hehe, the reaction of the Beyond Grade A Association is indeed not far from our hypothesis…"

…

In the conference room of the three Universal Civilizations, the virtual projections of Marbruce, Louis, and the Pope appeared.

"Tsk, the situation has changed. The cleanup plan cannot continue."

Marbruce frowned, and the other two had unsightly expressions as well.

While they had begun researching the Sanctum Revivals, the three Universal Civilizations also had plans to hunt down the Beyond Grade A seeds. Even if they managed to master the Sanctum Revival method in the future, since this large number of Beyond Grade A seeds would have gone to the association, they would not be able to transfer them over in the future. Both parties were destined to enter a long period of fighting for talents, so they would rather return to the problem of the excessive number of non-Beyond Grade As, making it such that it would be easier to contain the Beyond Grade A level in advance.

But before they could move, the three Universal Civilizations discovered that all of their targets were heavily protected.

At the beginning, the trio were a little dazed, thinking that Black Star had predicted their actions, flipping over the boat of trust they were on.

However, after careful investigation, they discovered that another unknown organization had first acted and alerted everyone.

This totally messed up their plans, causing them to feel a disgusting aftertaste.

Such a dumb way of doing things was not their style at all. If they wished to do it, they had to catch everyone in one fell swoop.

While they had not found out who had acted, the three Universal Civilizations did not even need to think to know that it was likely the Super Star Cluster Alliance.

"The Super Star Clusters purposely decided to create a commotion, leaving the association time to react, spoiling our operations." Louis was fuming.

"Unexpectedly, this makes sense." The Pope was expressionless.

From the perspective of the trio, the intentions of the Super Star Cluster Alliance were obvious. This served to intensify the suspicion between the association and the three Universal Civilizations.

The Beyond Grade A Association was only protecting them in the dark and had not publicly come out to accuse anyone. If the three Universal Civilizations took the initiative to state their innocence, it might backfire on them. Even if they tried to pin the blame on the Super Star Cluster Alliance, it would just look like their customary attitude of throwing shade at the other party.

With the current relationship of the three Universal Civilizations and the association, this was akin to having mud on the back of one's pants. Even if it was not sh*t, people would naturally assume it to be. No matter what, it would be difficult to gain their trust unless they could provide hard evidence.

The Super Star Clusters had been pitted against so many times; they already had experience in this matter. Since their reputation was in the gutters, they could just go for broke.

I'll pull you along with me as I fall from the cliff. If I'm going to die, then you have to come along!

In their current situation, the Super Star Cluster Alliance had nothing to be afraid of from the three Universal Civilizations any longer.

Since they no longer had any chances with the Flickering World, they would just stay cooped up at home.

If you have the ability, come and have an all-out war with us. Did you think you could really destroy us?

The trio present did indeed feel that the Super Star Cluster Alliance was a thorny problem.

If they had managed to kill off all the Beyond Grade A seeds that were trying to join the association, it might still have been a fair trade to get suspected, but now, they had become the scapegoats when only a few had been killed off. This was placing them in a disadvantage!

"Cancel the cleansing operation for the Beyond Grade A seeds. They're all protected now. There's no chance now."

The trio were not in a very good mood.

Chapter 1268: All Heroes in the World Enter My Squad

With the withdrawal of the Super Star Cluster Alliance and the abandonment of the plan by the three Universal Civilizations, the heavily protected Beyond Grade A seeds did not encounter any more hunting teams in the following journeys. All of them successfully arrived at a subdivision of the Black Star Army before teleporting to the base camp of the Black Star Army in the Flickering World by using the King suits.

The large-scale movement of the Beyond Grade A seeds also aroused the attention of the universe. Everyone soon learned about the fact that a large number of Beyond Grade A seeds had congregated in the association during the recent period. There was also news that specially drew out the areas at which they travelled, converging from various Star Fields into the Flickering World, which seemed as though they were migrating.

The number of Beyond Grade A seeds within a Star Field typically numbered more than one hundred, with the remote Star Fields having fewer while the Central Galaxy and the areas of the Super Star Cluster Alliance would be the most densely distributed. This total number had been trending upward, and with years of accumulation, the total number of seeds measured in the explored universe was about three thousand. This was almost twenty times the number of Beyond Grade As of the same generation.

Excluding the allies and direct descents of each civilization, as well as the people in existing factions, the current number of neutral Beyond Grade A seeds would be about two fifths the total, around 1,200. For this collective defection, roughly five hundred people, or almost half of the total number of neutral seeds, went over to join a Beyond Grade A faction, of which the number of people joining the Black Star Army was the highest!

This was equivalent to the association harvesting most of the top talent pool accumulated over the years of the explored universe. It was unknown how long it would take for the next batch of talents to grow!

Be it a Beyond Grade A or a Beyond Grade A seed, they were both top figures of the power pyramid and naturally possessed the attributes of a leader. Since both sides had merged on a large scale, the quantitative change has turned into a qualitative change. It was not just a simple matter such as the attitude of the Beyond Grade A seeds letting them choose where to rely on, but more of a signal and influence for many of the Supers, even the other Beyond Grade A seeds. This made everyone think that joining the Beyond Grade A Association at this time would be a wise choice!

The large-scale migration of the Beyond Grade A seeds caused a huge ripple effect over the next few months. A large number of Supers rushed to follow in their footsteps… As part of the strong at the apex of the power pyramid, their every word and action affected the people below. This was the meaning of a role model.

This matter was regarded as a 'movement' with special significance, nicknamed the 'Scattered Stars Return' by the galactic citizens. They likened the Beyond Grade A seeds to new stars that were scattered everywhere finally returning to their homes. A large group began to worship the members of the association, completing the cycle of Pioneers and Legacy holders.

Regarding the 'Scattered Stars Return', the entire Galactic Society was also analyzing the impact of this event from every angle. Gradually, a rumor spread that the function of the Beyond Grade A Association would change, their influence radiating to all Supers. A day would come when the association would no longer be a solely Beyond Grade A group; it would become the new organization that would lead all the Supers, becoming another pole independent of the three Universal Civilizations and turn into another ruler of the universe!

This statement was accepted and endorsed by a large number of Supers. Many Supers cheered, excited as they faintly waited in anticipation. In the eyes of most people, the Beyond Grade A Association was naturally qualified to lead them.

While there were so-called regional associations for Supers in the universe, the masters behind the scenes were the three Universal Civilizations, which used these associations as nothing more than tools for managing the Supers. The nature of those regional associations was inherently problematic.

In the eyes of the people, if the Beyond Grade A Association would one day evolve to become the guild for all Supers, it would truly be the organization that served the Supers. Their goals would naturally not be the same as the three Universal Civilizations.

The mentality of the Supers came from the fact that there had not been a unified voice to speak for them for too long, and they desperately wished to have a 'home'. To put it simply, it was the sense of them finally finding an organization to which they belonged.

However, this sort of argument was not born naturally. Someone was behind it fueling the flames, pushing the Beyond Grade A Association to the forefront and igniting public opinion.

Just as the universe raged with rumors and speculation, Han Xiao was busy welcoming the Beyond Grade A seeds in Black Star Palace.

Black Star Palace's Great Hall was huge but practically empty, with only the 300 seeds huddled in the middle. They either stood or hovered in the air, chatting as they eyed the doors leading into the hall, keeping a watch for Han Xiao.

"Everyone should be here now. Is Black Star still not coming? We've been waiting for almost half an hour."

"Tsk, you want to see a pinnacle Beyond Grade A, but you don't even have that much patience. You think people will come over to see you just because you want to see them?"

"Just be patient. Maybe His Excellency Black Star is actually watching us in the dark, observing our patience."

Everyone chatted casually, turning around to glance at others occasionally. There was a slight wariness in many of their eyes.

Many of them were familiar with each other, having fought together or against each other before, and they regarded each other as whetstones. Everyone knew that the number of slots around Black Star and the other Beyond Grade As were limited. With so many people in the army now, there was a high probability that they would have to compete for places, so everyone here was technically a competitor.

At this moment, the door suddenly opened. Han Xiao stepped in with his officers following behind.

Upon seeing this, the hundreds of Beyond Grade A seeds subconsciously stopped talking, straightening their postures as they exercised the etiquette of their respective cultures, expressing basic respect to one of the top powerhouses of the universe.

"We pay respects to Your Excellency Black Star!"

"Welcome to the army. We'll be family from now on, so there's no need to be this courteous."

Han Xiao waved his hand, putting on a warm smile.

Seeing the hundreds of seeds hailing from different areas, Han Xiao could not help but feel a little excited. This large number of experts meant a great replenishment for the army's advanced combatants.

This number was too exaggerated. It seemed as though he had underestimated the impact the Sanctum Revival would cause on the lower levelled Supers. If there was no such thing, the general resources being offered would not even shake a single one of them.

At this moment, Han Xiao felt a kind of pride. Of course, he felt more of the joy of being able to harvest such a bountiful crop of leeks.

Scanning the group, Han Xiao noted the burning gazes of everyone present and smiled. "I know why you're here. The threshold for the Sanctum Revival is a Beyond Grade A realm. I'll definitely try my best to help you get promoted, but as for whether or not you can succeed in the end, it will all depend on your own destinies…"

Everyone nodded, their eyes gleaming.

Han Xiao said a few more ceremonial words before arranging for everyone to come forward and accept his inspection according to the practices of the army. He then browsed through the attributes of each person.

The Beyond Grade A seeds were not mediocre people; all of them were masters in their fields. However, from Han Xiao's point of view, most of them had almost exhausted their potential, with only a handful having the chance to be promoted. He had a set of criteria for judging one's potential, mainly their expertise and skills. Their differences were graded by him, and those with potential were silently selected and kept in his mind.

After completing this step, Han Xiao had a rough gauge in his heart, so he took two steps back and loudly spoke. "Everyone, I now have a basic understanding of your level. I'll arrange positions according to your own personal abilities. Of course, you can send me your applications regarding your desired posts, and I'll consider your thoughts and wishes.

"But I must state in advance that some slots are extremely limited. If there are too many applicants, you may have to compete for the same position. For example, the Guard Corps of the two Deputy Army Commanders and I can be challenged each time, with the winners rotating in the position. Everyone should be mentally prepared for this."

When faced with an influx of people, a normal person's treatment of them would be to fairly distribute them out. However, with these masters, Han Xiao deliberately adopted a competitive format to avoid dissatisfaction. At the same time, he would be giving those unsuccessful people the opportunity to challenge successful applicants again to stimulate everyone's motivation to cultivate…

While this method was not useful to most of the people present, those in the Pugilist class felt their fighting spirit being strengthened.

Everyone glanced around subconsciously, their fighting intent sharpening.

At this moment, someone suddenly said, "Many thanks, Army Commander, for your protection. If not for your help, we would all have died mid-journey. I would like to ask, do you know the origins of the hunter squad?"

The moment his voice sounded, the entire room suddenly turned quiet.

Everyone's expression showed at least some suspicion. They did not mention this just now, but no one would be so carefree as to not get to the bottom of this matter when it involved their lives.

Han Xiao stopped smiling. He paused before saying a meaningful tone, "You already have the answer in your heart, don't you?"

Hearing this, the expressions of the crowd grew more complicated, and a slight commotion sounded.

"It's time to throw aside your fantasies and illusions. It seems like this was done by the advanced civilizations, and they wish to claim our lives."

"Has the relationship between the association and the advanced civilizations reached this point already? It's only been such a short time. What will happen in the future?"

"Sigh, the targets during the Tragedy of the Pinnacles have been passed down to us now. The Sanctum Revival is also a double-edged sword."

"If I'd known about this situation earlier, I might have already been frightened into retreating."

Those present sighed in low voices. Facing the hostile attitude of the three Universal Civilizations, they were all a little frightened.

Before they chose a side, they did not expect the advanced civilizations to retaliate so strongly. There was no way for them to show regret anymore.

"Alright, don't ponder about it any longer. You have already chosen your path, so all you have to do is to continue walking forward."

Han Xiao clapped his hands as he comforted everyone. His officers then took the crowd to their rooms to rest and wait for his orders.

As he sent everyone off with his gaze, a flash shone in Han Xiao's eyes. He then turned his head and left the great hall, walking for a while before arriving at the secret room.

Pushing the door open, this room was filled with bunks, but most of them were empty, with only one occupied.

Han Xiao walked forward, pressing the button to stop the hibernation program. With a hiss, the hatch slid open to reveal the figure inside. It was Karlot, who was lying down with a peaceful expression.

Karlot's brows trembled as he slowly opened his eyes. At first glance, he immediately saw Han Xiao standing in front of him, causing him to be taken aback.

"Your Excellency Black Star?"

Karlot was stunned.

In the past, he was young and immature, and he did not know of the identity of Black Star. As he grew up, he understood what kind of opportunity Black Star had offered him back then, and he became a fan of Black Star. However, he knew that their statuses in the universe were vastly different, so it would be difficult for them to have a chance to meet in the future. He felt that Black Star might have forgotten about him a long time ago, so he merely followed Han Xiao's deeds in silence.

But he did not expect his idol would actually appear all of a sudden in front of him.

The next moment, Karlot remembered what happened to him before he went into hibernation, and his expression changed.

"Was it you who knocked me out and brought me here? Where am I?"

"This is my base camp." Han Xiao smiled.

Right now, his relationship with Karlot was stiff, so it took him some energy to track down Karlot's whereabouts. However, Karlot had never realized his talent, so he was never taken seriously, and his capture had been smooth.

"You…" Karlot hesitated. "Why did you bring me here? Do you still remember me?"

If it was someone else, he would have long struggled to break free, but this was Han Xiao, who held a special position in his heart. Thus, he found it hard to be angry.

"Of course I do, and my impression was deep." Han Xiao sized up Karlot with an approving gaze. "We parted many years ago. You've already become an adult now, not bad."

Hearing this, Karlot could not help but feel moved. He did not expect Han Xiao to remember him so firmly.

Thinking about how Han Xiao had been optimistic about him, Karlot suddenly felt a little ashamed and embarrassedly said, "I'm sorry that I let you down. My potential doesn't seem to be as good as you thought."

He had managed to successfully enter the Calamity Grade in forty years, but after that, he seemed to stagnate. It seemed as though his potential had been exhausted, stopping at the ordinary Calamity Grade level.

Karlot did not care about the thoughts of outsiders, but in front of Black Star, he could not help but feel frustrated, thinking that he had failed the expectations the latter had of him.

"Are you saying that I was wrong?" Han Xiao spoke out with a smile that was not like a smile on his face.

Karlot did not speak, merely acquiescing to it.

Han Xiao laughed, raising his hand to pat Karlot's chest. "Don't look down on yourself. The dynasty does not value you because they have no foresight. I've always believed in your potential."

Hearing this, Karlot again felt moved and ashamed.

"Aren't you curious why I brought you over? This is the reason." Han Xiao narrowed his eyes, "Actually, I've always been paying attention to you. The dynasty has never seen your talents, so they never assigned resources to you, which has affected your growth. I cannot bear to see a talent being buried, so I brought you here to help you stimulate your potential!"

"… so, you've always been observing me?"

Karlot had an expression of wonderment. He was deeply touched on how he could be so favored by Black Star.

Han Xiao smiled as he poked Karlot.

"Don't underestimate the huge potential in your body. You might think that the Calamity Grade is your limit, but let me tell you, Calamity Grade is far from your end!"

"You think that I can become a Beyond Grade A?" Karlot's eyes widened.

"Not only that… I think that you might even reach the pinnacle Beyond Grade A realm, becoming one of the foremost experts in the universe!"

Han Xiao's tone was full of passion and also provocative.

"Do you really see me this way?" Karlot mumbled.

Seeing that he was close to tipping, Han Xiao turned solemn as he said in a deep voice, "Then tell me now. Are you willing to remain here and accept my help?"

Karlot hesitated a little. He had also followed the news and knew of the current storm that was brewing. He whispered, "You wish for me to stay here, meaning I have to leave the dynasty and enter the army?"

"The situation has changed now. The dynasty and I are going against each other. Only by remaining by my side can I give you the most detailed guidance. However, this will make it such that you can no longer stay in the dynasty." Han Xiao did not deny anything.

Karlot fell silent, seemingly conflicted. After a while, he slowly raised his head as his expression grew determined.

"I understand. I'm willing to stay by your side and receive your guidance!"

Karlot might have worked in the dynasty for decades, but in his eyes, it was just a job. It did not determine that he had to be shackled to the dynasty forever. With his family having passed on years ago, he was a lone wolf floating in the cold universe without any concerns.

The dynasty had never placed any importance in him. Although they allowed him to enter the secret training base, that was because Black Star had shown interest in him, or else they would not have given him this special treatment. They eventually still kicked him out of the camp… All his fortune had been given to him by Black Star—this much, he understood.

Furthermore, Karlot felt that Black Star did not need to scheme against him. He just wished to repay Black Star for whatever grace the latter had shown, so even if Black Star was wrong about him, he would still reach the Beyond Grade A realm!

Hearing this, Han Xiao breathed a sigh of relief.

"I knew you wouldn't let me down."

Thanks to the good relationship formed decades ago, setting the impression to become the role model of Karlot, the difficulty in recruiting him had been reduced by dozens of times.

This is the importance of information…

Han Xiao secretly smirked. He finally got his hands on a coveted golden leek.

Chapter 1269: Activation

After successfully persuading Karlot, Han Xiao got his subordinates to take him down to rest. He then left the room with satisfaction in his heart.

When he poked the other party, he had seen Karlot's attributes. Karlot had now obtained his core talent, [Everlasting Martial Path]. It was an overpowered growth-type talent.

To put it simply, [Everlasting Martial Path] could evolve once every grade with the requirement being a new realization of the martial path. Before the evolution of the talent, the user's leveling speed would be lowered by ninety percent. After the evolution, the user's leveling speed would follow an inverted parabolic arc with the peak being at a thousand percent. It also provided an all-rounded boost to the user's combat capability.

Ordinarily speaking, the stronger an individual, the greater the number of bottlenecks. However, Karlot was different. All of his bottlenecks would be during his pre-growth phase, and he would face fewer and fewer bottlenecks the stronger he grew. Past a certain point, his combat strength would snowball until he reached the peak of the grade. If he entered a new grade, he would have to restart the entire process again.

Karlot's growth after every evolution in grade would be excruciatingly slow, and this also resulted in a firm foundation. In Han Xiao's previous life, Karlot was an extremely famous Pugilist. His status within the Pugilist world was like the Mechanic Emperor's status within the Mechanic world.

This little brat's nickname in his previous life was the one and only 'Martial Deity'!

Furthermore, [Everlasting Martial Path] could also strengthen all of Karlot's Pugilist skills. It did not only increase the level of his skills but also adjusted his skills in a subtle manner as though the skills were tailor made for him. [Everlasting Martial Path] was a one-of-a-kind talent that could meld all kinds of Pugilist theories and school of thoughts together into one.

Han Xiao had never seen this talent in any other Pugilist before. If not for the lack of a suffix, Han Xiao would have thought that it was a talent unique to Karlot.

However, although the talent was extremely overpowered, it was useless to Han Xiao since he was not a proper Pugilist.

"I still need to find a teacher for him. Although there are plenty of Pugilists in the army, they are all of the Calamity Grade and a little too weak…" A few figures flashed through his head. "It'd be best if I find a Beyond Grade A to teach Karlot. Of all the people I know, the most suitable one should be Silver Shadow. These two individuals were good friends in my previous life and should have pretty good chemistry with each other. Silver Shadow should be a good teacher for him."

Han Xiao stroked his chin.

After thinking for a while, he realized that he still had a few other backup choices. For example, he could hire some Pugilist teachers from the Underworld or let Gorutan out temporarily to teach Karlot.

With his current strength, Gorutan would not be too much of a threat to him. Furthermore, he should also let Gorutan out for fresh air once in a while, lest Gorutan ended up dying in the Spacetime Amber.

Karlot was the first individual who he poached from the three Universal Civilizations, and he would not be the last. Although the others did not have as much potential as Karlot, Han Xiao would not let go of them either.

He pondered while walking back to the office. After reaching the office, Han Xiao temporarily placed the matter aside and summoned Phillip to settle the affairs of the army.

He needed to arrange the posts of these Beyond Grade A seeds. There was another large group of Supers joining the army, and the HR department was currently filtering through the applicants.

After settling all these matters, Han Xiao took out his communicator to surf the net and let out a soft snort.

"There are definitely some high-grade Civilizations fanning the flames, hoping that the entire world will fall into chaos."

There were rumors on the net that the Beyond Grade A Association would eventually unite the Super community and become the fourth ruler of the universe apart from the three Universal Civilizations. These rumors were intentionally created to push the association to the peak before finding an opportunity to kick them down back into the ravine.

Although the method was old fashioned, the effect was pretty good. As long as they could mislead the general public, this simple method would be extremely effective.

The current rumors surrounding the association were not a good sign for them. Being in the spotlight would put them on the opposite side of the three Universal Civilizations. Together with words like 'the fourth ruler of the universe', it was akin to grilling them over fire.

With the heated discussion on the net, it was not an appropriate time for Han Xiao to make a stand. Furthermore, even if the mastermind continued to fan the flames, the galactic residents would have a limited attention span toward a single event and be attracted by something else eventually.

Han Xiao knocked on the desk and pondered.

"The Beyond Grade A seeds have already entered the association and the high-grade civilizations gave up on the plan to cleanse the universe. The status quo should be maintained for the time being… I need some time to reorganize the association and collect keys. The three Universal Civilizations also need time to study the Sanctum Revival method and probably won't do anything in the short run. Furthermore, they also have to prevent the Super Star Cluster Civilizations from creating trouble. Everyone needs time and will thus choose to maintain the current peace…"

Before having sufficient confidence, the three Universal Civilizations would not adopt extreme measures against the association and would only deal with Beyond Grade A seeds. The way Han Xiao saw it, the universe would still be peaceful for a while.

This peace would probably be maintained until the players returned.

"It has already been fifty years, and Version 5.0 is about to be activated. Because of my influence, the current situation is different from the Calamity of the Supers in my previous life. I wonder what the players will do."

Han Xiao stroked his chin and fell into thought.

…

In the Central Galaxy, within the Crimson Dynasty Science Institute's Wormhole Position Project Office, the research team leader walked into the conference room, where the researchers were waiting for him.

Compared to a couple of decades ago, most of the researchers had either retired or been transferred out. Thus, it was a set of new faces.

The team leader then looked around slowly and said, "The dynasty has issued an internal document to push forward technological research and provide information to the Sanctum Revival team. Every department will be receiving a large increase in funds."

Upon hearing that, all the researchers were excited.

Research was extremely capital intensive, and the wormhole project was not as important as the other research projects. Ever since the start of the Flickering War, this project had been trying to sustain itself on a low budget.

When the cooperation between Han Xiao and the dynasty was in the honeymoon phase, the dynasty listened to Han Xiao's suggestion and stopped the research on the wormhole coordinates to focus on dealing with the Super Star Cluster Alliance.

After the war, the wormhole project should have been back on track, but something went wrong along the way.

After the war, the dynasty was busy tying up loose ends, and the upper echelons did not continue the project. Perhaps because they forgot or wanted to be on the safe side, the project was never continued after that. After all, the location of the wormhole was only a small matter to the dynasty. Apart from the officials and researchers in charge of the project, there was almost no one who paid any attention to the project.

It was extremely normal for subordinates to follow the attitude of their superiors. With the attitude of the upper echelons being unclear, the researchers had plenty of apprehensions and did not dare take a risk. As such, they would rather play it safe. They did not ease up on the wormhole project, which resulted in a large amount of data that was still at the approval phase.

Such a situation had continued for a few years because of the ambiguous attitude from the upper echelons.

After a few decades, most of the original research staff had been transferred to other departments with the new research staff being inexperienced newcomers.

Throughout the Science Institute, the wormhole project was not the only team facing such a situation. There were projects being cancelled every year and also new projects being set up.

It was not uncommon for there to be factions within the Science Institute, relying on connections to obtain funding. As an organization grew larger, such occurrences were common, and the three Universal Civilizations were no exception.

The research team leader then gave out some instructions before leaving, leaving behind a room of excited researchers.

"We finally don't have to be a team on the periphery."

"Hurry up and report all the backlog data. We can finally make some proper progress in our research."

"We have not submitted our equipment procurement list for this year yet. Quickly change it and purchase more long-distance space detection needles."

…

Just as what Han Xiao had predicted, after failing to ambush the Beyond Grade A seeds, the three Universal Civilizations and Super Star Cluster Alliance showed some restraint. At Han Xiao's orders, the association also did not openly announce the truth behind the Beyond Grade A seeds affair. It was as though they intentionally forgot about it.

Apart from fanning the flames on the web, the three parties maintained their current equilibrium and did not engage in open conflict. They were currently accumulating their strength and preparing various different means to deal with their enemies.

Perhaps the Super Star Cluster Alliance had thought about creating trouble but was not able to find the appropriate opportunity.

Although both parties had not erupted in open hostility, in the eyes of the public, the three Universal Civilizations and the association were on opposite sides with the thick smell of gunpowder ready to be ignited at any time.

Although the Super Star Cluster Alliance was frequently on the losing end, they were pretty professional at fanning flames. This was just like the saying of a prolonged illness making the patient a good doctor.

Under the calm silence of the universe was the raging undercurrent. The three Universal Civilizations gradually stopped their cooperation with the various Beyond Grade A organizations and also came up with some business strategies to suppress the association. Under Han Xiao's reorganization, the association also gradually became more independent.

With the Super Star Cluster Civilizations fanning the flames from the background, practically the entire universe knew that the conflict between the three Universal Civilizations and association would not be settled peacefully.

A year slowly passed.

On Galaxy Calendar Year 782, Version 5.0 was activated again, and the players were back online!